{"1": {"1": "suffer", "2": "suffers", "3": "suffering", "4": "suffered", "answer": "suffered", "question": "The assets of Marble Faun Publishing Company ___ last quarter when one of their main local distributors went out of business."}, "2": {"1": "him", "2": "his", "3": "himself", "4": "he", "answer": "his", "question": "lndie film director Luke Steele will be in London for the premiere of ___ new movie."}, "3": {"1": "full", "2": "complete", "3": "all", "4": "total", "answer": "all", "question": "Laboratory employees are expected to wear a name tag and carry identification at ___ times."}, "4": {"1": "method", "2": "guide", "3": "staff", "4": "role", "answer": "guide", "question": "The latest training ___ contains tips on teaching a second language to international students:"}, "5": {"1": "qualified", "2": "qualifications", "3": "qualify", "4": "qualifying", "answer": "qualifications", "question": "Once you have your resume with references and ___ , please submit it to the Human Resources Department on the 3rd floor."}, "6": {"1": "soon", "2": "shortly", "3": "recently", "4": "yet", "answer": "recently", "question": "Ursa Major Corp. has ___ negotiated a deal with a Russian competitor in surveying the Kamchatka Peninsula."}, "7": {"1": "having", "2": "will have", "3": "was having", "4": "has", "answer": "was having", "question": "Ms. Cho relayed her concerns about the company's financial situation while she ___ a meeting with the manager."}, "8": {"1": "necessary", "2": "necessarily", "3": "necessitate", "4": "necessity", "answer": "necessary", "question": "Whether it is ___ to register for a student discount card depends on the needs of the individual."}, "9": {"1": "materials", "2": "sessions", "3": "experiences", "4": "positions", "answer": "sessions", "question": "Even experienced clerks are encouraged to attend training ___ to keep them updated on new ideas in the world of banking."}, "10": {"1": "they", "2": "them", "3": "their", "4": "themselves", "answer": "themselves", "question": "Workers are advised not to operate certain machines by ___ ."}, "11": {"1": "construct", "2": "constructive", "3": "construction", "4": "constructed", "answer": "construction", "question": ". The ___ of a discount department store was delayed by the protests of several members of the community."}, "12": {"1": "large", "2": "largely", "3": "largest", "4": "larger", "answer": "largely", "question": "Ms. Maria Perreira is ___ responsible for some of our company's most successful marketing campaigns."}, "13": {"1": "estimates", "2": "sponsors", "3": "deliverance", "4": "relocations", "answer": "estimates", "question": "Mr. Singh requested ___ from several catering companies before making his decision."}, "14": {"1": "despite", "2": "due to", "3": "provided that", "4": "because", "answer": "due to", "question": "Our apartment building's occupancy increased ___ the efforts of our knowledgeable and friendly rental agent, Ms. Gova."}, "15": {"1": "among", "2": "since", "3": "within", "4": "whereas", "answer": "within", "question": "Those employees wishing to change departments ___ the company may send their inquiries to Mr. Alvarez."}, "16": {"1": "procedure", "2": "layer", "3": "accessory", "4": "quality", "answer": "quality", "question": "The New Economic Quarterly criticized the ___ of all new products produced by Yun Sung Industrial Co., Ltd."}, "17": {"1": "led", "2": "leads", "3": "leader", "4": "leading", "answer": "leading", "question": "One of the ___ international research facilities in botany is located at the Hoskin Museum of Natural History."}, "18": {"1": "instituted", "2": "proved", "3": "decided", "4": "resembled", "answer": "instituted", "question": "In order to ensure customer safety, the government has ___ a new set of guidelines for pharmaceutical companies."}, "19": {"1": "allowing", "2": "allows", "3": "allowance", "4": "allowably", "answer": "allowing", "question": "Welton Textiles Inc. made a net profit of $ million, ___ it to fund its expansion across the continent."}, "20": {"1": "comparative", "2": "envious", "3": "pleased", "4": "ambitious", "answer": "ambitious", "question": "Our ___ production goals will be directed by a skilled team of qualified managers."}, "21": {"1": "increasingly", "2": "increasing", "3": "increased", "4": "increase", "answer": "increasingly", "question": "Prattchet Co. has ___ turned to making most of its products from recycled materials."}, "22": {"1": "Bringing", "2": "Helping", "3": "Maintaining", "4": "Promoting", "answer": "Maintaining", "question": "___ our financial goals for this year may require cutting back on some overhead costs."}, "23": {"1": "of", "2": "for", "3": "with", "4": "to", "answer": "with", "question": "Heidelberg Publishing Co. offers employees ___ performance bonuses to encourage success."}, "24": {"1": "gradually", "2": "nearly", "3": "exclusively", "4": "precisely", "answer": "exclusively", "question": "An anniversary dinner was held ___ for high-ranking officials in the corporation."}, "25": {"1": "During", "2": "Until", "3": "After", "4": "When", "answer": "When", "question": "___ contacting our Human Resources Department by phone, please include your contact information."}, "26": {"1": "satisfied", "2": "spacious", "3": "considerable", "4": "capable", "answer": "spacious", "question": "Because of the added guests from our allied financial firm, a more ___ meeting room had to be used than usual."}, "27": {"1": "energy", "2": "energize", "3": "energetic", "4": "energetically", "answer": "energetic", "question": "Ms. Richards has been an exceptionally ___ member of the marketing team, providing Billingsgate Enterprises with great service for nine years."}, "28": {"1": "Subsequently", "2": "However", "3": "Meanwhile", "4": "Despite", "answer": "Despite", "question": "___ his falling out with his former employer, Mr. Lee still meets with some of his old co-workers from time to time."}, "29": {"1": "appreciation", "2": "appreciative", "3": "appreciating", "4": "appreciates", "answer": "appreciation", "question": "The chief financial officer of Waterhouse Inc. is expressing ___ concerning his predecessor's informative advice."}, "30": {"1": "competed", "2": "became", "3": "continued", "4": "thought", "answer": "became", "question": "Since opening last year, Savannah Safari Park quickly ___ one of the leading recreational spots in the region."}, "31": {"1": "will", "2": "is", "3": "was", "4": "has been", "answer": "was", "question": ". Ms. Gamble, who ___ an influential literary critic in the s, is now a contributing writer to the National Gazette newspaper."}, "32": {"1": "arbitrarily", "2": "separately", "3": "definitely", "4": "mutually", "answer": "separately", "question": "Remember to list fixed expenses ___ from variable expenses."}, "33": {"1": "probable", "2": "probability", "3": "probably", "4": "probabilities", "answer": "probable", "question": "The loss of our foreign manufacturing plants may be a ___ outcome of the new plans being implemented."}, "34": {"1": "environments", "2": "environmentalists", "3": "environmentally", "4": "environmental", "answer": "environmentally", "question": "New government regulations concerning the chemicals in cleaning solutions mean that the solvents must be as ___ safe as possible."}, "35": {"1": "consult", "2": "make", "3": "invite", "4": "request", "answer": "consult", "question": "Ms. Stanhope always tries to ___ her colleagues on the budget."}, "36": {"1": "originator", "2": "original", "3": "originally", "4": "originality", "answer": "original", "question": "Rosalind Media Ltd. came up with the idea to hire artists to create ___ artworks for the purpose of marketing."}, "37": {"1": "approximate", "2": "important", "3": "uncertain", "4": "intended", "answer": "uncertain", "question": "The CEO of Lawrence United Co. is still ___ about opening company branches in Mexico."}, "38": {"1": "intention", "2": "intended", "3": "intentional", "4": "intending", "answer": "intention", "question": "The ___ of Mr. Alex Hartham was to initiate a merger with Culford International."}, "39": {"1": "throughout", "2": "against", "3": "next", "4": "near", "answer": "near", "question": "The staff lounge is ___ the meeting room, across the hall from the computer lab."}, "40": {"1": "implemented", "2": "induced", "3": "surprised", "4": "granted", "answer": "granted", "question": "The manager ___ Mr. Karnes a promotion because of his successful handling of the company's accounting for the past two years."}, "41": {"1": "ceremony", "2": "advice", "3": "product", "4": "invention", "answer": "ceremony", "question": "The awards ___ will begin at approximately 6:00 this evening, at which time winners are requested to be present to receive their awards."}, "42": {"1": "replace", "2": "cause", "3": "interfere", "4": "return", "answer": "replace", "question": "For defective merchandise, we will gladly ___ the product or give you a full refund."}, "43": {"1": "contract", "2": "contracts", "3": "contracted", "4": "contracting", "answer": "contract", "question": "At the same time, the company also won a two-million-dollar ___ for maintenance of the trains for the next seven years."}, "44": {"1": "revising", "2": "revision", "3": "revise", "4": "revised", "answer": "revised", "question": "We are planning to implement a ___ paper-recycling program for all branch offices effective next month."}, "45": {"1": "ours", "2": "these", "3": "us", "4": "his", "answer": "his", "question": "Mr. Ken O'Hara, Chief Executive of ESB, after more than 40 years service with the company, has announced ___ decision to retire in July ."}, "46": {"1": "subjected", "2": "restored", "3": "recommended", "4": "opened", "answer": "recommended", "question": "Dieting during pregnancy is never ___ , as it can limit the nutrition available to the baby."}, "47": {"1": "enormously", "2": "financially", "3": "exceptionally", "4": "generously", "answer": "generously", "question": "Open Society Institute has ___ offered to sponsor a number of participants from developing countries for attendance at the OA Workshop."}, "48": {"1": "along", "2": "during", "3": "of", "4": "into", "answer": "of", "question": "If you would like a demonstration ___ the new product, just ask the BKM staff at the booth."}, "49": {"1": "discussion", "2": "goal", "3": "group", "4": "happening", "answer": "discussion", "question": "The sales manager has been asked to lead a ___ of the Asian market's future outlook during the board meeting tonight at 7 p.m."}, "50": {"1": "subsequent", "2": "subsequent to", "3": "subsequently", "4": "subsequence", "answer": "subsequently", "question": "NDRC is the national authority that is in charge of setting guidance tariffs that are ___ implemented by the local authorities."}, "51": {"1": "While", "2": "Yet", "3": "Rather", "4": "As though", "answer": "While", "question": "___ the CEO was giving a speech to the newly hired employees at the training session, a secretary took a picture of him."}, "52": {"1": "will begin", "2": "had begun", "3": "has begun", "4": "is beginning", "answer": "had begun", "question": "The company ___ working on the project for the main office even before it chose the land to build on."}, "53": {"1": "plain", "2": "public", "3": "subject", "4": "general", "answer": "subject", "question": "Reservations are made on a first-come, first-served basis and are ___ to room availability."}, "54": {"1": "sharp", "2": "sharply", "3": "sharpen", "4": "sharpness", "answer": "sharply", "question": "We expect our sales to rise ___ to around $ million over the next 24 months."}, "55": {"1": "hers", "2": "herself", "3": "her own", "4": "she", "answer": "her own", "question": "Ruth Akorful is a baker and has been managing ___ business for several years."}, "56": {"1": "depend", "2": "dependable", "3": "dependent", "4": "dependence", "answer": "dependent", "question": "The Leighton Group is a service-based organization and our success is ___ on the quality of the service we offer."}, "57": {"1": "specialty", "2": "composition", "3": "priorities", "4": "negotiations", "answer": "negotiations", "question": "After months of ___ , we are pleased to announce that the company and your union have reached an agreement that resolves 9 out of 1Opending grievances."}, "58": {"1": "acquainted", "2": "acquainting", "3": "acquaintance", "4": "acquaintances", "answer": "acquaintances", "question": "Michael, the former CEO of the company, is looking forward to seeing many friends and ___ at next year's show in August."}, "59": {"1": "fluently", "2": "currently", "3": "considerably", "4": "originally", "answer": "originally", "question": "The building built by Emaar Properties was ___ scheduled to be completed at the end of this year but the target date has been changed due to revisions in the building's design."}, "60": {"1": "will create", "2": "was created", "3": "having created", "4": "had been creating", "answer": "will create", "question": "Following the visit to your production facility in Hong Kong next week, we ___ a comprehensive factory automation program to meet your company's needs."}, "61": {"1": "among", "2": "up", "3": "at", "4": "of", "answer": "at", "question": "Either the marketing director or the sales manager will represent Centum Construction Inc. ___ the Bexco Architecture Conference."}, "62": {"1": "instruct", "2": "instructing", "3": "instructions", "4": "instructional", "answer": "instructions", "question": "Your new coffee machine comes with detailed ___ which will help you use it more effectively."}, "63": {"1": "When", "2": "Before", "3": "Whereas", "4": "Since", "answer": "Since", "question": "___ she joined our company three years ago, Mrs. Mashimo has greatly expanded our customer base."}, "64": {"1": "universe", "2": "universal", "3": "universally", "4": "universality", "answer": "universally", "question": "Neobucks has more than 3, stores in the United States and 25 other countries, and its logo is ___ recognizable."}, "65": {"1": "complete", "2": "completion", "3": "completed", "4": "completely", "answer": "complete", "question": "If you would like to comment on a recent experience with us, please ___ a customer satisfaction survey before leaving your room."}, "66": {"1": "approve", "2": "express", "3": "register", "4": "record", "answer": "register", "question": "As space is limited, be sure to contact Bill in the personnel department a minimum of three days in advance to ___ for a workshop."}, "67": {"1": "environment", "2": "participation", "3": "reaction", "4": "incident", "answer": "environment", "question": "As a manager, you are also responsible for maintaining a work ___ that is comfortable and ergonomically safe."}, "68": {"1": "heavy", "2": "forceful", "3": "steep", "4": "strict", "answer": "steep", "question": "The tree-lined trails and ___ slopes make Whistler Mountain a dangerous place to ride, even for experienced cyclists."}, "69": {"1": "any of", "2": "each", "3": "all", "4": "every", "answer": "all", "question": "Many people prefer to shop at The Bay Department Store as it offers a lifetime warranty on ___ purchases."}, "70": {"1": "act", "2": "progress", "3": "chance", "4": "number", "answer": "act", "question": "In an unprecedented ___ of generosity, Patty DeDominic, the founder of DeDominic & Associates, pledged a $1-million donation that will help local charities."}, "71": {"1": "calendar", "2": "intention", "3": "deadline", "4": "admission", "answer": "deadline", "question": "Satyam Computer Services Ltd. has extended the ___ for submitting applications for the marketing manager position to April 13th."}, "72": {"1": "later", "2": "recent", "3": "further", "4": "following", "answer": "later", "question": "If mechanical problems occur at the time of your scheduled trip, alternatives will be discussed with you whether to reschedule the trip for a ___ time."}, "73": {"1": "estimate", "2": "estimates", "3": "estimated", "4": "estimating", "answer": "estimate", "question": "All work will be discussed in detail before a written ___ is given to any client."}, "74": {"1": "recalled", "2": "collaborated", "3": "provided", "4": "employed", "answer": "collaborated", "question": "We have ___ with community groups and business partners to support local economic development projects."}, "75": {"1": "approached", "2": "detailed", "3": "probable", "4": "loyal", "answer": "detailed", "question": "All sales representatives should know ___ information about the product they are selling and be able to answer any questions."}, "76": {"1": "making", "2": "make", "3": "makes", "4": "made", "answer": "make", "question": "Mountain Equipment Co-op. has deeply discounted their winter items to ___ room for the new spring merchandise."}, "77": {"1": "in", "2": "through", "3": "with", "4": "along", "answer": "in", "question": "While ___ a foreign country, it would be wise to take only what you will absolutely need during the day and leave anything else in the safe in your hotel room."}, "78": {"1": "those", "2": "them", "3": "whose", "4": "which", "answer": "those", "question": "At the annual stockholders' meeting, large printed material will be made available on request for ___ with visual impairment."}, "79": {"1": "what", "2": "that", "3": "which", "4": "those", "answer": "that", "question": "A recent survey indicates ___ young women in particular are showing a strong preference for online shopping."}, "80": {"1": "responsibility", "2": "responsibilities", "3": "responsible", "4": "responsibly", "answer": "responsible", "question": "The office manager is ___ for supporting staff members and ensuring that their work is done efficiently."}, "81": {"1": "her", "2": "hers", "3": "herself", "4": "she", "answer": "she", "question": "After Rachel had worked for the company for more than 10 years, ___ was finally promoted to a managerial position."}, "82": {"1": "between", "2": "both", "3": "either", "4": "rather", "answer": "both", "question": "Mr. Jackson expressed a strong desire to increase ___ the company's revenue and the number of employees."}, "83": {"1": "produce", "2": "produces", "3": "product", "4": "producing", "answer": "produces", "question": "Kelvin Video System's most recent model ___ vivid images on its screen."}, "84": {"1": "From", "2": "Of", "3": "For", "4": "By", "answer": "For", "question": "___ further information, please don't hesitate to call our customer service center at 1-."}, "85": {"1": "Enter", "2": "Entries", "3": "Being entered", "4": "Entering", "answer": "Entries", "question": "___ for the annual GRR contest should be submitted by no later than December 1st."}, "86": {"1": "easily", "2": "easy", "3": "easing", "4": "ease", "answer": "easily", "question": "Clients of Bank of America can ___ gain access to their accounts 24 hours a day throughout the year."}, "87": {"1": "excellent", "2": "interested", "3": "grateful", "4": "absolute", "answer": "excellent", "question": "The president of the company gave credit for the increased number of sales to the ___ work done by his staff."}, "88": {"1": "where", "2": "when", "3": "there", "4": "why", "answer": "there", "question": "Although the owner of the company wasn't able to attend the meeting, his secretary was ___ to take important notes for him."}, "89": {"1": "even though", "2": "because of", "3": "since", "4": "besides", "answer": "because of", "question": "The Wall Street banks collapsed ___ the uncertainty that investors had about the American economy."}, "90": {"1": "begin", "2": "hurry", "3": "prevent", "4": "enhance", "answer": "prevent", "question": "Wiping out the company's data on retiring workers' computers may ___ any leak concerning crucial information aboutthe company."}, "91": {"1": "once", "2": "far", "3": "yet", "4": "still", "answer": "still", "question": "After a long speech about the importance of working hard, Mr. Glenn ___ reminded his workers to work hard every day."}, "92": {"1": "arranges", "2": "arranged", "3": "arranging", "4": "arrangements", "answer": "arrangements", "question": "EMI requires all of its employees to make their own ___ for their business trips."}, "93": {"1": "numerical", "2": "numbers", "3": "number", "4": "numerous", "answer": "number", "question": "The ___ of flood victims temporarily residing in the government-supplied camps has just exceeded a thousand."}, "94": {"1": "license", "2": "licensor", "3": "licensing", "4": "licensed", "answer": "license", "question": "Before obtaining a ___ , applicants are required to complete 40 hours of driving with an adult over 21."}, "95": {"1": "slowly", "2": "nearly", "3": "primarily", "4": "variously", "answer": "primarily", "question": "My application was to be reviewed ___ because I attended the company's summer internship course."}, "96": {"1": "them", "2": "their", "3": "those", "4": "they", "answer": "they", "question": "All the temporary workers are supposed to keep track of the hours that ___ work."}, "97": {"1": "quickly", "2": "quicken", "3": "quickened", "4": "quickness", "answer": "quickly", "question": "Ms. Hong was forced to resign as CEO of the company ___ since investors weren't pleased with her recent performance."}, "98": {"1": "at", "2": "with", "3": "on", "4": "over", "answer": "on", "question": "All the employees at SEI Corporation are invited to the meeting ___ the new internal communications system that the company is about to bring in."}, "99": {"1": "is editing", "2": "was editing", "3": "will be editing", "4": "has been edited", "answer": "has been edited", "question": "Although the marketing department submitted the initial proposal, it ___ many times since then."}, "100": {"1": "unwilling", "2": "unfavorable", "3": "opposing", "4": "reluctant", "answer": "unfavorable", "question": "The president has just realized that the launch of our new product must be postponed owing to ___ conditions in the market."}, "101": {"1": "picks up", "2": "hangs up", "3": "turns down", "4": "breaks down", "answer": "breaks down", "question": "The contract indicates that if your car ___ on the road, you can get immediate roadside service within one hour."}, "102": {"1": "immediacy", "2": "immediate", "3": "immediateness", "4": "immediately", "answer": "immediately", "question": "The general manager made it clear before the meeting that employees can ask questions ___ after the meeting, but they must remain quiet throughout the meeting."}, "103": {"1": "sketches", "2": "solutions", "3": "stylists", "4": "studios", "answer": "studios", "question": "Ms. Kempbell runs a company that builds ___ in both professional music agencies and people's houses."}, "104": {"1": "concern", "2": "concerns", "3": "concerned", "4": "concerning", "answer": "concerned", "question": "Although Jack was ___ that his coworker would be very nervous on his first day of work, he was in fact quite confident, which surprised Jack."}, "105": {"1": "among", "2": "throughout", "3": "while", "4": "toward", "answer": "throughout", "question": "The CEO addressed the future of the company so passionately ___ the conference that he didn't even realize that he was losing his voice."}, "106": {"1": "personal", "2": "personalities", "3": "personally", "4": "personalize", "answer": "personalities", "question": "Job interviewers generally evaluate the applicants' working abilities rather than their ___ ."}, "107": {"1": "thought", "2": "based", "3": "resulted", "4": "developed", "answer": "developed", "question": "As much as the Korean economy has ___ - tremendously in a short period of time, there are still many problems that our nation is facing."}, "108": {"1": "effective", "2": "total", "3": "raised", "4": "complete", "answer": "effective", "question": "The manager's speech on hard work was not ___ because he is not considered a hard worker to the audience."}, "109": {"1": "will be published", "2": "will publish", "3": "are publishing", "4": "publishes", "answer": "will be published", "question": "The new novel by Steven Kim ___ no later than the 18th of November according to a reliable source."}, "110": {"1": "exactly", "2": "jointly", "3": "hardly", "4": "consistently", "answer": "consistently", "question": "As we have had workers who quit after working for a short period of time, we need someone who can work ___ for at least a year."}, "111": {"1": "attraction", "2": "attractive", "3": "attracted", "4": "attractively", "answer": "attractive", "question": "While Jason found the proposal from the other company ___ , he ultimately turned it down to keep the relationship with his original partner company."}, "112": {"1": "standards", "2": "guides", "3": "documents", "4": "precautions", "answer": "standards", "question": "Maverick Manufacturers has maintained the highest safety ___ of any company in its industry."}, "113": {"1": "urgent", "2": "urgency", "3": "urgently", "4": "urgencies", "answer": "urgent", "question": "Peter had to work during my vacation because the matter was so ___ - that it couldn't wait for my return."}, "114": {"1": "full", "2": "fully", "3": "fuller", "4": "fullness", "answer": "fully", "question": "It is very difficult for the head of a company to ___ understand the different characteristics of each employee."}, "115": {"1": "reaching", "2": "submitting", "3": "extending", "4": "offering", "answer": "extending", "question": "Most workers agree that ___ the number of work hours is not going to increase the company's revenue because it actually results in lower work efficiency."}, "116": {"1": "conclusive", "2": "financial", "3": "beneficial", "4": "regulated", "answer": "beneficial", "question": "Although the company had a tight budget, they invested more money in their new product because they believed it was ___ in the long run."}, "117": {"1": "so far", "2": "so that", "3": "as much", "4": "as long as", "answer": "as much", "question": "Although Jackson Inc. invests a large amount of money in advertising, its competitor, James Inc. doesn't invest ___ in it."}, "118": {"1": "surplus", "2": "indication", "3": "forecast", "4": "obligation", "answer": "obligation", "question": "Due to the contractual ___ , the company had to keep supplying the raw material for a cheap price even though there has been a rise in the overall market price."}, "119": {"1": "meticulously", "2": "considerably", "3": "enormously", "4": "compatibly", "answer": "meticulously", "question": "Because the head executive of YIB Inc. checks every single condition on contracts ___ -, he never makes a mistake when signing the final copy."}, "120": {"1": "receivable", "2": "receiving", "3": "receive", "4": "receives", "answer": "receive", "question": "We have been working on updates for the program, and you should ___ the updated information in January ."}, "121": {"1": "but", "2": "or", "3": "and", "4": "neither", "answer": "or", "question": "Frank Truner who was interviewed on Friday will be assigned to either the research department ___ the marketing department."}, "122": {"1": "she", "2": "hers", "3": "herself", "4": "her", "answer": "her", "question": "The author's comments are considered ___ own and are not necessarily reflective of the view of the magazine publisher."}, "123": {"1": "almost", "2": "every", "3": "regularly", "4": "recently", "answer": "regularly", "question": "All equipment in the gym is checked ___ to ensure that it is safe to use."}, "124": {"1": "clean", "2": "cleanliness", "3": "cleanly", "4": "cleanest", "answer": "cleanliness", "question": "The Calgary Inn attaches importance to the ___ of its rooms and always offers good service at reasonable prices."}, "125": {"1": "exhibited", "2": "donated", "3": "offered", "4": "passed", "answer": "offered", "question": "The management course will be ___ on Monday, October 17, from 9 a.m. to 4 p.m., while the law course will be taught on Tuesday, October 18, from 9 a.m. to 4p.m."}, "126": {"1": "easy", "2": "easily", "3": "ease", "4": "easiness", "answer": "easily", "question": "Giessen is centrally located in Germany and can ___ be reached by plane, train, and car."}, "127": {"1": "onto", "2": "off", "3": "out", "4": "at", "answer": "off", "question": "To cut down on electricity wastage, we use energy-saving light bulbs and remind employees to turn ___ their computers when they leave the office."}, "128": {"1": "allowance", "2": "allows", "3": "allowing", "4": "allowable", "answer": "allows", "question": "Our online service ___ you to view your information, make address changes, review account history, and request documents."}, "129": {"1": "should", "2": "that", "3": "upon", "4": "to", "answer": "that", "question": "It is important ___ managers draw in the best sales people to sell the products."}, "130": {"1": "whatever", "2": "whom", "3": "what", "4": "whose", "answer": "whose", "question": "Eli Clare, ___ latest book was published by Local Home Press, is nominated for the  Lambda Literary Award."}, "131": {"1": "place", "2": "schedule", "3": "show", "4": "introduce", "answer": "show", "question": "Holders of old-style CIV tickets are required to ___ their tickets to a staff member before boarding the train."}, "132": {"1": "supplies", "2": "supplied", "3": "supplier", "4": "supply", "answer": "supplies", "question": "Office ___ are ordered through the central purchasing department and are typically delivered the next business day."}, "133": {"1": "in", "2": "from", "3": "between", "4": "by", "answer": "by", "question": "If students are unable to arrive ___ the date specified on their visa documents, they will be sent home and will have to restart the application process."}, "134": {"1": "overwhelming", "2": "overwhelmingly", "3": "overwhelm", "4": "overwhelmed", "answer": "overwhelmingly", "question": "Barbuda's economy remains ___ dependent on tourism and on visitors who fly to the islands from all over the world."}, "135": {"1": "chapters", "2": "sides", "3": "phases", "4": "times", "answer": "phases", "question": "We encourage frequent customer visits during all ___ of the project to facilitate communication and to ensure that the project goals are being attained successfully."}, "136": {"1": "However", "2": "Despite", "3": "Because", "4": "Therefore", "answer": "Because", "question": "___ storage space is limited, please notify Benjamin Hatton if you no longer need your locker."}, "137": {"1": "exhibition", "2": "admission", "3": "lesson", "4": "speech", "answer": "admission", "question": "Our employees can receive free ___ to the Joslyn Art Museum as well as discounts to the museum's gift shop."}, "138": {"1": "confident", "2": "obvious", "3": "noticeable", "4": "intelligent", "answer": "confident", "question": "Considering her ability, dedication, and expertise, I am ___ that Ms. Yoko will be the most suitable person for the position of marketing manager."}, "139": {"1": "effectively", "2": "effect", "3": "effective", "4": "effectiveness", "answer": "effectively", "question": "The advisory committee ___ addressed the president's concerns about the new building project."}, "140": {"1": "inception", "2": "anniversary", "3": "origin", "4": "date", "answer": "anniversary", "question": "Nicholas Sarkozy, president of the organization, is hosting an event on May 4, to mark the 90th ___ of the founding of the Red Cross."}, "141": {"1": "considerable", "2": "tangible", "3": "receivable", "4": "eligible", "answer": "eligible", "question": "Temporary and part-time employees are not ___ for paid holidays; if they work on a holiday, such employees will receive their regular wages."}, "142": {"1": "outsourced", "2": "employed", "3": "joined", "4": "delivered", "answer": "outsourced", "question": "The Department of Parks and Recreation has ___ the maintenance of public restroom facilities to Advance Management Inc."}, "143": {"1": "in", "2": "of", "3": "at", "4": "out", "answer": "of", "question": "Although Mr. Broadwater was the most qualified ___ all the applicants for the position, the job was given to another."}, "144": {"1": "closing", "2": "seeing", "3": "keeping", "4": "joining", "answer": "keeping", "question": "In ___ with company policy, protective clothing must be worn at all times during your visit to our plant."}, "145": {"1": "Though", "2": "Due to", "3": "Because", "4": "As of", "answer": "Due to", "question": "___ growing seasonal demand, the store owner decided to hire five additional sales clerks."}, "146": {"1": "impressively", "2": "impressive", "3": "impress", "4": "impressiveness", "answer": "impressive", "question": "With more than 34 years of designing some of the most ___ buildings in Calgary, the reputation of the firm is well deserved."}, "147": {"1": "hesitant", "2": "urgent", "3": "unexpected", "4": "apprehensive", "answer": "unexpected", "question": "Should an ___ delay in shipping occur, we will notify you by email of the new projected shipping date and provide you with an opportunity to keep your order or cancel it."}, "148": {"1": "honor", "2": "honors", "3": "honored", "4": "honoring", "answer": "honoring", "question": "In celebration of National Volunteer Appreciation Day, Betsy Johnson Regional Hospital will host a luncheon ___ its  hospital volunteers tomorrow."}, "149": {"1": "Produced", "2": "Settled", "3": "Established", "4": "Arranged", "answer": "Established", "question": "___ two decades ago with the vision of providing cost-effective office equipment, we are today one of the world's leading manufacturers in the field."}, "150": {"1": "completes", "2": "completely", "3": "complete", "4": "completing", "answer": "completely", "question": "Once the application is complete, our office staff can check your application to ensure everything is filled in ___ and all documents are included."}, "151": {"1": "In order to", "2": "Even as", "3": "Since", "4": "Unless", "answer": "In order to", "question": "___ process a refund or exchange, you must notify us within two weeks of receiving your shipment."}, "152": {"1": "have been", "2": "would be", "3": "are being", "4": "is being", "answer": "would be", "question": "One of our service department staff ___ glad to assist you with the maintenance of your vehicle."}, "153": {"1": "as for", "2": "between", "3": "within", "4": "because", "answer": "within", "question": "There are two distinct business units ___ Glocell, each focusing on different customers and their needs."}, "154": {"1": "led", "2": "told", "3": "held", "4": "found", "answer": "held", "question": "Manufacturers who make products available to the public are ___ responsible for the injuries their products cause."}, "155": {"1": "identify", "2": "identifies", "3": "identity", "4": "identifiable", "answer": "identifiable", "question": "The TIPH employees are ___ by their distinctive khaki uniforms and the special emblem on their uniforms and vehicles."}, "156": {"1": "relied", "2": "designed", "3": "notified", "4": "progressed", "answer": "designed", "question": "Britax's new infant car seat offers a host of comfort and safety features ___ to keep your child secure while traveling in the car."}, "157": {"1": "Some", "2": "Anyone", "3": "Those", "4": "Whoever", "answer": "Anyone", "question": "___ applying for the position of marketing director is asked to submit a resume along with two letters of reference."}, "158": {"1": "witness", "2": "bearer", "3": "founder", "4": "you", "answer": "bearer", "question": "The enclosed coupons will entitle the ___ to a ten percent discount on any of our products."}, "159": {"1": "foreseeable", "2": "enforceable", "3": "durable", "4": "comfortable", "answer": "durable", "question": "Ideal Safes & Solutions, with its seven years of experience, provides reliable and ___ safes and cabinets."}, "160": {"1": "is revising", "2": "will revise", "3": "revises", "4": "revised", "answer": "revised", "question": "After Jonathan ___ the proposal for the project more than five times with his colleague, he finally handed it over to his boss."}, "161": {"1": "I", "2": "me", "3": "my", "4": "mine", "answer": "me", "question": "Since Carol, my boss, was not satisfied with my work, she fired me and gave ___ one month's notice."}, "162": {"1": "group", "2": "winner", "3": "title", "4": "ceremony", "answer": "ceremony", "question": "The company's ___ only took an hour and a half because they skipped the boring opening speech and some unnecessary  formalities."}, "163": {"1": "In", "2": "Of", "3": "At", "4": "On", "answer": "In", "question": "___ the past two years, the number of car accidents has gone up by 15%."}, "164": {"1": "heaviness", "2": "heavy", "3": "heavily", "4": "heaviest", "answer": "heavy", "question": "Due to ___ traffic, John has to wake up early every morning in order to make it to work on time."}, "165": {"1": "renovation", "2": "renovate", "3": "renovating", "4": "renovated", "answer": "renovated", "question": "Max complained to his boss that it's been 10 years since the office has been ___ and it needs some changes in order to promote a better work environment."}, "166": {"1": "already", "2": "later", "3": "further", "4": "once", "answer": "already", "question": "Although Peter hurried up and called Kevin to tell him that the meeting was canceled, Kevin was ___ waiting for the representatives from the partner company."}, "167": {"1": "attend", "2": "attended", "3": "to attend", "4": "is attending", "answer": "to attend", "question": "BWS Corporation's employees were advised ___ the training session because only those who completed the session would be considered for the promotion."}, "168": {"1": "either", "2": "neither", "3": "yet", "4": "nor", "answer": "either", "question": "When you invest your money, you have to choose ___ to invest in high-risk opportunities or low-risk ones."}, "169": {"1": "appoint", "2": "appointed", "3": "appoints", "4": "appointment", "answer": "appointment", "question": "Peter was glad when he received a text message from the hospital reminding him of his ___ on Thursday because he almost forgot about it."}, "170": {"1": "because", "2": "until", "3": "not only", "4": "so that", "answer": "because", "question": "Jane could not apply for the job she desperately wanted ___ it required a high level of English."}, "171": {"1": "it", "2": "its", "3": "them", "4": "they", "answer": "its", "question": "Jason attempted to utilize some new equipment at the factory, but he had trouble figuring out even where ___ start button was."}, "172": {"1": "center", "2": "central", "3": "centrally", "4": "centered", "answer": "centrally", "question": "Because the store was ___ located, it had a huge advantage in exposing its goods to the public, which had an impact on its increase in sales."}, "173": {"1": "or", "2": "and", "3": "but", "4": "if", "answer": "but", "question": "The company announced that it would merge with Tyrell Incorporated, ___ it said the opposite only two days later."}, "174": {"1": "occasionally", "2": "occasional", "3": "occasion", "4": "occasions", "answer": "occasionally", "question": "Justin's Packaging company ___ receives returned products because the new machine that they purchased has been creating problems for the past couple of months."}, "175": {"1": "release", "2": "delivery", "3": "transportation", "4": "resource", "answer": "delivery", "question": "While Kim was waiting for the ___ of the product that she ordered a month ago, she realized that what she ordered was actually not the one that the company needed."}, "176": {"1": "high", "2": "broad", "3": "whole", "4": "round", "answer": "high", "question": "According to the interviewer, the position requires a ___ familiarity with marketing theory."}, "177": {"1": "accepted", "2": "helped", "3": "entered", "4": "produced", "answer": "helped", "question": "Jason's colleagues were jealous of him because his boss ___ him with the work so much that he nearly had nothing to do but handed in the completed work."}, "178": {"1": "relatively", "2": "closely", "3": "normally", "4": "jointly", "answer": "relatively", "question": "Although people often believe that coffee has too much caffeine, in reality, it's ___ low in caffeine compared to some energy drinks such as Redbull, Monster and Rockstar."}, "179": {"1": "informing", "2": "informative", "3": "informed", "4": "informally", "answer": "informative", "question": "Carl thought that the conference was very ___ and actually learned a lot more than he'd learned at university."}, "180": {"1": "evaluate", "2": "evaluates", "3": "evaluated", "4": "evaluation", "answer": "evaluation", "question": "It is necessary for superiors to give a fair ___ of their workers because it has a huge impact on their future career."}, "181": {"1": "involved", "2": "served", "3": "regarded", "4": "conducted", "answer": "served", "question": "Because Jack had ___ the company as the general manager for more than 20 years, there was not one employee who didn't know him."}, "182": {"1": "Within", "2": "Onto", "3": "Along", "4": "For", "answer": "For", "question": "___ the first three months, Tim's boss couldn't find any flaws in him, but he realized that Tim actually has a very hot temper when he got into an argument with his co-worker."}, "183": {"1": "low", "2": "lower", "3": "lowered", "4": "lowering", "answer": "lowering", "question": "Although the company aimed for a greater number of sales by ___ the price of their products, it faced a huge loss in revenue because they couldn't reach their expected number of sales."}, "184": {"1": "satisfied", "2": "preventable", "3": "experienced", "4": "competitive", "answer": "competitive", "question": "A professional soccer player, Jinsu became so ___ in the game that he ended up earning himself a yellow card for his actions."}, "185": {"1": "after", "2": "instead", "3": "during", "4": "beyond", "answer": "after", "question": "Kate was hoping that Harry would correct his mistakes on the proposal before submitting it ___ she told him which mistakes she had found while going over it."}, "186": {"1": "supplies", "2": "supplier", "3": "supplied", "4": "supplying", "answer": "supplier", "question": "The factory wasn't able to produce as many products as it was supposed to because the ___ couldn't deliver the raw materials on time."}, "187": {"1": "cautious", "2": "previous", "3": "supportive", "4": "deliberate", "answer": "previous", "question": "Because the head of the company was obsessed with the company's profits from the ___ year, he couldn't focus on its profits for the current year."}, "188": {"1": "obligate", "2": "afford", "3": "promote", "4": "participate", "answer": "promote", "question": "In order to ___ the purchase of its new products, the company spent a great deal on advertising."}, "189": {"1": "continuing", "2": "continually", "3": "continued", "4": "continual", "answer": "continually", "question": "Noticing that the stock value was ___ decreasing, the biggest shareholder sold all of his stocks for a reasonably low price."}, "190": {"1": "persuade", "2": "to persuade", "3": "persuasiveness", "4": "persuasive", "answer": "persuasive", "question": "With the strong visual effects of the presentation, the general manager sounded very ___ in his meeting held with the partner company."}, "191": {"1": "extremely", "2": "adversely", "3": "dramatically", "4": "retroactively", "answer": "dramatically", "question": "Because of the sudden death of the CEO, the company's stock value dropped ___ and didn't recover for several years."}, "192": {"1": "immense", "2": "enthusiastic", "3": "calculating", "4": "impending", "answer": "immense", "question": "There are still ___ job opportunities in the Unites States because there are many small businesses around the country."}, "193": {"1": "Despite", "2": "Whatever", "3": "Although", "4": "Whenever", "answer": "Although", "question": "___ some customers claimed that the company's customer service providers are impolite, HISL Corporation totally ignored the claims."}, "194": {"1": "agreement", "2": "array", "3": "acclaim", "4": "appeal", "answer": "array", "question": "As a result of working for 14 hours continually, I was able to create an ___ of products in different colors."}, "195": {"1": "whatever", "2": "whose", "3": "which", "4": "who", "answer": "whose", "question": "HIB Investment Bank, ___ shareholders were passionate about getting a new CEO, has been going through some chaotic changes recently."}, "196": {"1": "distinguished", "2": "connected", "3": "specified", "4": "employed", "answer": "specified", "question": "The head of the department has ___ that all employees are required to hand in their vacation plans before the end of the month."}, "197": {"1": "by far", "2": "once again", "3": "very much", "4": "for long", "answer": "once again", "question": "Jim ___ made the same mistake by misspelling the names of the people who were supposed to attend the conference."}, "198": {"1": "so much", "2": "well", "3": "very", "4": "mostly", "answer": "very", "question": "The president seemed ___ upset when the interviewer asked him a very sensitive question about his family history."}, "199": {"1": "receptor", "2": "operator", "3": "contractor", "4": "indicator", "answer": "indicator", "question": "When the acid ___ turned red, Tony realized that he should not touch it without any protection on his hands."}, "200": {"1": "recommends", "2": "recommendation", "3": "recommended", "4": "recommending", "answer": "recommendation", "question": "Dr. Braun will write ___ letters only for interns who master every task expected of a junior copy editor."}, "201": {"1": "appoint", "2": "appoints", "3": "appointed", "4": "appointment", "answer": "appointment", "question": "The ___ of a new chief financial officer at Veracore Industries was announced on April 6."}, "202": {"1": "beneficial", "2": "eligible", "3": "convenient", "4": "relevant", "answer": "eligible", "question": "After a six-month probationary period, city employees are ___ to take vacation days."}, "203": {"1": "required", "2": "requiring", "3": "requires", "4": "will require", "answer": "required", "question": "Ms. Larensky is applying with several different agencies to obtain the permits ___ for the outdoor art event."}, "204": {"1": "confirm", "2": "confirmed", "3": "confirmable", "4": "confirmation", "answer": "confirmation", "question": "This letter serves as ___ that we have received and processed your credit-card cancellation request."}, "205": {"1": "we", "2": "us", "3": "our", "4": "ourselves", "answer": "us", "question": "Many people at the company have industry experience, but only a handful of ___ can see the future importance of current trends."}, "206": {"1": "hardly", "2": "comfortably", "3": "early", "4": "eagerly", "answer": "early", "question": "The new furniture for the conference room is scheduled to be delivered ___ on Tuesday."}, "207": {"1": "visited", "2": "returned", "3": "occurred", "4": "related", "answer": "returned", "question": "After working in Canada for ten years, Cha Joon has ___ to Seoul to plan the opening of an upscale restaurant."}, "208": {"1": "automate", "2": "automatic", "3": "automated", "4": "automatically", "answer": "automatically", "question": "Toucan Database System is designed to perform a detailed financial analysis ___"}, "209": {"1": "statement", "2": "permission", "3": "project", "4": "ability", "answer": "project", "question": "The city council approved the bill to increase funding for Its road improvement ___"}, "210": {"1": "for", "2": "who", "3": "those", "4": "as", "answer": "who", "question": "The Neighborhood Involvement Program honors residents ___ volunteer their time to help Egin City."}, "211": {"1": "proposing", "2": "proposed", "3": "proposal", "4": "proposals", "answer": "proposed", "question": "Several architects ___ intriguing design plans for the Hadler Building's addition."}, "212": {"1": "within", "2": "until", "3": "during", "4": "since", "answer": "within", "question": "The updated training program is limited to site supervisors ___ the Casey Medical Care system."}, "213": {"1": "will leave", "2": "leaves", "3": "leaving", "4": "left", "answer": "leaves", "question": "Mr. Koizumi must complete the cost estimate before he ___ for the conference."}, "214": {"1": "similar", "2": "likable", "3": "reflected", "4": "considerate", "answer": "similar", "question": "Although the new X printer is ___ to other models, it costs only half as much."}, "215": {"1": "promote", "2": "declare", "3": "obtain", "4": "benefit", "answer": "promote", "question": "To address budget deficits, Lunere County plans to limit spending and ___ tourism."}, "216": {"1": "consecutively", "2": "standardly", "3": "namely", "4": "easily", "answer": "easily", "question": "Operating instructions are posted above the printer so you can ___ refer to them."}, "217": {"1": "will begin", "2": "has begun", "3": "beginner", "4": "beginning", "answer": "beginning", "question": "The Vickwell Historical Museum will be closed for renovations ___ on Monday, September 10."}, "218": {"1": "so", "2": "more", "3": "very", "4": "much", "answer": "very", "question": "Finley Plant Nursery implements the ___ latest agricultural techniques."}, "219": {"1": "before", "2": "how", "3": "why", "4": "either", "answer": "before", "question": "According to the compensation guidelines, employees who regularly complete their work ___ it is due may receive bonuses."}, "220": {"1": "participant", "2": "participation", "3": "participate", "4": "participated", "answer": "participation", "question": "Thank you for your ___ in the Foxdale Apartments community enhancement survey."}, "221": {"1": "factor", "2": "position", "3": "instructor", "4": "composition", "answer": "factor", "question": "Solar energy has become a key ___ in the development of additional energy resources throughout the region."}, "222": {"1": "excluding", "2": "during", "3": "following", "4": "regarding", "answer": "regarding", "question": "The LPN auto company has issued a special report to address concerns ___ the fuel efficiency of its vehicles."}, "223": {"1": "create", "2": "creative", "3": "creativity", "4": "creatively", "answer": "creatively", "question": "This year's company retreat will focus on techniques that help people think more ___"}, "224": {"1": "apply", "2": "submit", "3": "vacate", "4": "oppose", "answer": "submit", "question": "Employees must ___ requests for time off to Ms. Cheung for approval."}, "225": {"1": "themselves", "2": "theirs", "3": "their", "4": "they", "answer": "themselves", "question": "Board members are free to discuss the issues among ___ before the formal votes are taken."}, "226": {"1": "clear", "2": "clearly", "3": "clearer", "4": "clearing", "answer": "clearly", "question": "Judging by ticket sales, Fen Jiang's first attempt at directing a film was ___ a success."}, "227": {"1": "While", "2": "When", "3": "For", "4": "But", "answer": "While", "question": "___ the Nolan Credit Union parking area is now open to the public, a section has been reserved for credit union employees."}, "228": {"1": "as well as", "2": "as soon as", "3": "in regard to", "4": "in addition to", "answer": "as soon as", "question": "Pharmacy technicians are responsible for verifying and processing prescriptions ___ they are requested by a physician."}, "229": {"1": "activation", "2": "fulfillment", "3": "compliance", "4": "indication", "answer": "compliance", "question": "All laboratory personnel must attend the clinical safety workshop to ensure ___ with new regulations."}, "230": {"1": "document", "2": "documents", "3": "documented", "4": "documenting", "answer": "documents", "question": "The travel ___ will be processed as soon as they are received."}, "231": {"1": "For", "2": "Across", "3": "With", "4": "To", "answer": "To", "question": "___ change your seating assignment, visit the reservations page on our Web site."}, "232": {"1": "he", "2": "him", "3": "his", "4": "himself", "answer": "his", "question": "The president of Somchai Bank rides ___ bicycle to work every day, except when it rains."}, "233": {"1": "closely", "2": "formerly", "3": "nearly", "4": "immediately", "answer": "immediately", "question": "Agents who have not yet registered for next week's Insurance Excellence Forum must do so ___ ."}, "234": {"1": "different", "2": "differently", "3": "difference", "4": "differences", "answer": "different", "question": "Matos Realty has developed two ___ methods of identifying undervalued properties."}, "235": {"1": "training", "2": "fulfillment", "3": "specialization", "4": "requirement", "answer": "requirement", "question": "Wearing lab coats and safety goggles is a ___ for all laboratory workers."}, "236": {"1": "remembers", "2": "recognizes", "3": "recommends", "4": "registers", "answer": "recommends", "question": "The manufacturer ___ that the filter be cleaned at least once a month for optimal performance."}, "237": {"1": "careful", "2": "caring", "3": "carefully", "4": "cares", "answer": "carefully", "question": "Before selecting a Dagle steel door, measure the door opening ___ ."}, "238": {"1": "if", "2": "soon", "3": "only", "4": "then", "answer": "if", "question": "Okpara employees should contact their supervisors by 10:00 A.M. ___ they expect to miss a day of work."}, "239": {"1": "comparable", "2": "comparison", "3": "compared", "4": "comparative", "answer": "comparison", "question": "The director has requested a ___ of the costs of short and long-term rental agreements."}, "240": {"1": "able", "2": "numerous", "3": "sure", "4": "enough", "answer": "enough", "question": "Ms. Yi of Lakesview Catering says that five trays of appetizers are more than ___ for fifty guests."}, "241": {"1": "transport", "2": "transporting", "3": "transports", "4": "transported", "answer": "transporting", "question": "Canada's Pan Rail Corporation will no longer ___ freight into the United States."}, "242": {"1": "exceptionally", "2": "exceptional", "3": "exception", "4": "exceptions", "answer": "exceptionally", "question": "According to experts, Flash Maxe dishwashing detergent consistently delivers ___ results."}, "243": {"1": "process", "2": "analysis", "3": "proof", "4": "basis", "answer": "proof", "question": "When picking up identification badges, employees need to show ___ of employment at Ekmekci Associates."}, "244": {"1": "actively", "2": "activity", "3": "active", "4": "activate", "answer": "actively", "question": "Roxy Koenig is ___ seeking a new venue for her summer concert since the Hazelton Music Hall is being renovated."}, "245": {"1": "too", "2": "in addition", "3": "moreover", "4": "along with", "answer": "along with", "question": "Prospective tenants must provide at least two references ___ their application."}, "246": {"1": "extensive", "2": "clever", "3": "considered", "4": "eager", "answer": "extensive", "question": "While Ms. Molinsky has little experience in technical support, her knowledge of computer systems is ___ ."}, "247": {"1": "support", "2": "attention", "3": "division", "4": "statement", "answer": "division", "question": "Please refer to the attached flowchart, which describes the ___ of responsibilities among the various leadership positions."}, "248": {"1": "to enhance", "2": "enhances", "3": "is enhancing", "4": "enhanced", "answer": "to enhance", "question": "A good project manager strives ___ communication between departments whenever possible."}, "249": {"1": "expectedly", "2": "necessarily", "3": "preventively", "4": "permanently", "answer": "necessarily", "question": "Same-day appointments can usually be scheduled, although not ___ with your usual doctor."}, "250": {"1": "credited", "2": "scored", "3": "agreed", "4": "relied", "answer": "credited", "question": "Mr. Vieira is ___ with introducing several changes that have helped stacatti Stationery increase business."}, "251": {"1": "from", "2": "reverse", "3": "opposite", "4": "distant", "answer": "opposite", "question": "In the photograph, President Tang can be seen standing ___ Dr. Dervishi."}, "252": {"1": "access", "2": "accessibly", "3": "accessible", "4": "accessibility", "answer": "accessible", "question": "The new location of the Bentler Company is easily ___ by car or bus."}, "253": {"1": "its", "2": "which", "3": "whose", "4": "more", "answer": "whose", "question": "Arise in energy prices will mostly affect businesses ___ energy consumption is high."}, "254": {"1": "assured", "2": "arranged", "3": "disclosed", "4": "committed", "answer": "assured", "question": "City officials have ___ Harmon Avenue businesses that street repairs will be completed within 48 hours."}, "255": {"1": "can attend", "2": "must have attended", "3": "should attend", "4": "would have attended", "answer": "would have attended", "question": "Our department ___ the policy meeting last Monday, but we had a scheduling conflict."}, "256": {"1": "Since", "2": "Given", "3": "Among", "4": "Upon", "answer": "Given", "question": "___ the effectiveness of Maisey Stanton's leadership on the town council, she will likely win next week's mayoral election."}, "257": {"1": "initiative", "2": "initiating", "3": "initiation", "4": "initiator", "answer": "initiative", "question": "Barner Corporation's record profits resulted from the recent ___ to identify operating efficiencies."}, "258": {"1": "as if", "2": "so that", "3": "in case", "4": "even though", "answer": "even though", "question": "Customers still tend to place short notices in the classified section ___ there is no longer a mandated word limit."}, "259": {"1": "full", "2": "fully", "3": "fuller", "4": "fullest", "answer": "fully", "question": "All shelves in the holiday merchandise section need to remain ___ stocked."}, "260": {"1": "Access", "2": "Accessed", "3": "Accessing", "4": "Accessible", "answer": "Access", "question": "___ to the exercise room is included with your stay at the Bay land Hotel."}, "261": {"1": "he", "2": "his", "3": "him", "4": "himself", "answer": "he", "question": "Mr. Okello's promotion means that ___ will supervise a larger team."}, "262": {"1": "changing", "2": "attending", "3": "holding", "4": "turning", "answer": "changing", "question": "Juniper Worldwide, Inc., will be ___ payroll service providers on January 1."}, "263": {"1": "between", "2": "along", "3": "below", "4": "apart", "answer": "along", "question": "The Valletta Visitor Centre offers da ly boat rides ___ the City's historic waterfront"}, "264": {"1": "that", "2": "any", "3": "one", "4": "either", "answer": "one", "question": "Ultrora Action's T-Pro tennis shoe is the lightest ___ on the market right now"}, "265": {"1": "negotiating", "2": "negotiates", "3": "negotiated", "4": "negotiate", "answer": "negotiate", "question": "Duram Biscuit Corp, is able to ___ good deals with its wholesale suppliers."}, "266": {"1": "plenty", "2": "each", "3": "very", "4": "many", "answer": "many", "question": "At Razani Marketing, there are ___ opportunities for professional advancement."}, "267": {"1": "so that", "2": "as a result", "3": "in order to", "4": "because of", "answer": "because of", "question": "Parking on Dahakno Street will be prohibited for the next few days ___ emergency repairs to water lines"}, "268": {"1": "referring", "2": "referred", "3": "referral", "4": "refer", "answer": "referral", "question": "Accountants applying for the training must obtain a ___ from their supervisor"}, "269": {"1": "when", "2": "only", "3": "still", "4": "most", "answer": "only", "question": "The evaluation report will be completed ___ after the auditors inspect the laboratory."}, "270": {"1": "necessitating", "2": "necessary", "3": "necessarily", "4": "necessities", "answer": "necessary", "question": "In light of our recent expansion, it will be ___ to hire another administrative assistant by June 1."}, "271": {"1": "until", "2": "onto", "3": "since", "4": "all", "answer": "until", "question": "Due to low registration, the communications workshop scheduled for July 2 will be postponed ___ further notice."}, "272": {"1": "fairness", "2": "fairest", "3": "fairly", "4": "fair", "answer": "fairly", "question": "The initial response to the beta version of the software allows US to be ___ optimistic about future product sales."}, "273": {"1": "wealth", "2": "height", "3": "labor", "4": "fame", "answer": "wealth", "question": "Orvale School's business mentors are retired executives with a ___ of expertise across a wide range of industries."}, "274": {"1": "update", "2": "updated", "3": "updates", "4": "updating", "answer": "updated", "question": "Thank you for your interest in our ___ line of compact refrigerators."}, "275": {"1": "how", "2": "nor", "3": "now that", "4": "whether", "answer": "now that", "question": "The judges may begin to review the entries ___ the deadline for submitting slogans has passed."}, "276": {"1": "analysis", "2": "analyzer", "3": "analyzes", "4": "analyzing", "answer": "analyzes", "question": "On his daily radio show, Trade Biz, Antonio Kosior ___ business news from all over the globe."}, "277": {"1": "in", "2": "again", "3": "positions", "4": "ultimately", "answer": "in", "question": "The purchase of The New Lagos Reporter will not lead to changes ___ editorial staff."}, "278": {"1": "surprised", "2": "surprise", "3": "surprisingly", "4": "surprising", "answer": "surprisingly", "question": "Professor Reginald Layke's proposal for an additional course in business management was approved in a ___ short time."}, "279": {"1": "aware", "2": "current", "3": "serious", "4": "alert", "answer": "aware", "question": "Carideli Science Museum trustees are expected to be ___ of all the museum's operations."}, "280": {"1": "economical", "2": "economic", "3": "economize", "4": "economy", "answer": "economy", "question": "With the completion of its airport, Honokai Island's tourism ___ has improved dramatically."}, "281": {"1": "personify", "2": "magnify", "3": "specify", "4": "testify", "answer": "specify", "question": "Brock's Bistro has requested that we ___ the number of dinner guests by Monday."}, "282": {"1": "toward", "2": "throughout", "3": "regarding", "4": "aboard", "answer": "throughout", "question": "Doi Textiles, Inc., is well-known ___ the fashion world as being a trendsetter for young women's clothing."}, "283": {"1": "appoint", "2": "appoints", "3": "appointed", "4": "appointing", "answer": "appointed", "question": "{D) solicitation  A reception will be held to introduce the newly ___ director of marketing to the employees of Kaulana Industries."}, "284": {"1": "seeking", "2": "is seeking", "3": "are sought", "4": "have been sought", "answer": "is seeking", "question": "To fill two vacant positions on its benefits committee, Adidion Labs ___ employees who are ready for a challenge."}, "285": {"1": "haltingly", "2": "intimately", "3": "permissibly", "4": "markedly", "answer": "markedly", "question": "The software for tracking orders has been ___ successful as it has greatly decreased time spent on the task."}, "286": {"1": "inasmuch as", "2": "the reason being", "3": "because of them", "4": "most of whom", "answer": "most of whom", "question": "Lately the community sports program has had a surplus of volunteers, ___ are students."}, "287": {"1": "knowledgeable", "2": "considerable", "3": "enjoyable", "4": "available", "answer": "enjoyable", "question": "Please use the attached survey to let US know how ___ your recent stay at the Copper Mine Inn was."}, "288": {"1": "their", "2": "they", "3": "theirs", "4": "them", "answer": "they", "question": "Sales clerks at Sylla Bazaar receive additional pay when ___ work in the evening."}, "289": {"1": "inexpensive", "2": "unhappy", "3": "incomplete", "4": "undecided", "answer": "inexpensive", "question": "The use of high-quality yet ___ machine parts led to a decrease in costs for Mr. Kim's factory."}, "290": {"1": "damage", "2": "damaging", "3": "damaged", "4": "damages", "answer": "damage", "question": "Because humidity can ___ wood, the climate in furniture storage units must be controlled."}, "291": {"1": "so", "2": "and", "3": "both", "4": "for", "answer": "for", "question": "The updated safety manual includes guidelines ___ the entire factory."}, "292": {"1": "value", "2": "record", "3": "amount", "4": "setting", "answer": "amount", "question": "A limited ___ of time for questions will be granted following Mr. Tanaka's speech."}, "293": {"1": "continual", "2": "continues", "3": "continue", "4": "continually", "answer": "continually", "question": "At Correia Electronics, we are ___ researching appliance technology."}, "294": {"1": "since", "2": "to", "3": "against", "4": "within", "answer": "within", "question": "At Imprint Eyewear, most prescription eyeglasses can be made ___ two business days."}, "295": {"1": "excel", "2": "excelled", "3": "excellent", "4": "excellence", "answer": "excellence", "question": "The first prize presented was the Kozar Award for ___ in educational toy design."}, "296": {"1": "previously", "2": "typically", "3": "almost", "4": "well", "answer": "typically", "question": "Ms. Ling is not here today, but she ___ attends every library board meeting."}, "297": {"1": "as much", "2": "as many", "3": "so much", "4": "so many", "answer": "as many", "question": "Investing in ___ -- properties as possible can be risky but is often lucrative"}, "298": {"1": "finalized", "2": "designed", "3": "hosted", "4": "created", "answer": "finalized", "question": "After interviewing Ms. Garcia personally, the company president ___ the committee's decision to hire her as chief financial officer."}, "299": {"1": "postpones", "2": "has been postponed", "3": "will have postponed", "4": "is postponing", "answer": "has been postponed", "question": "Construction of the Yukimura Building ___ because of modifications in the architectural plans."}, "300": {"1": "announcements", "2": "conversions", "3": "adjustments", "4": "commitments", "answer": "adjustments", "question": "Please inform Ms. Montgomery of any ___ to your office supplies order before 2:00 P.M."}, "301": {"1": "except", "2": "through", "3": "instead of", "4": "according to", "answer": "instead of", "question": "All Buehler Energy customers are encouraged to sign up for electronic statements ___ paper ones."}, "302": {"1": "admiration", "2": "admiring", "3": "admire", "4": "admirable", "answer": "admirable", "question": "In her letter of reference, Ms. Eisner indicates that Mr. Patel's ability to work well with others is his most ___ quality."}, "303": {"1": "either", "2": "nor", "3": "because", "4": "unless", "answer": "unless", "question": "This Friday, all employees may depart two hours before closing ___ their manager requires them to stay."}, "304": {"1": "recruit", "2": "recruiting", "3": "recruitments", "4": "recruiters", "answer": "recruiters", "question": "The Science Career Fair is an exciting opportunity for job seekers to meet with ___ from major companies in the field."}, "305": {"1": "beside", "2": "over", "3": "among", "4": "upon", "answer": "among", "question": "The songs on Sophia Vestra's new album are ___ the most innovative musical arrangements of her career."}, "306": {"1": "tourists", "2": "tours", "3": "tourism", "4": "toured", "answer": "tourism", "question": "The research indicates that ___ in Chestnut Valley has remained stable over the past two years."}, "307": {"1": "while", "2": "until", "3": "despite", "4": "whether", "answer": "while", "question": "Online orders are handled by Mr. Clark's team, ___ regular mail orders are overseen by Ms. Adauto's group."}, "308": {"1": "suggest", "2": "suggested", "3": "suggesting", "4": "suggests", "answer": "suggested", "question": "After the ___ upgrades have been implemented, the production process should run more efficiently."}, "309": {"1": "stored", "2": "stayed", "3": "based", "4": "moved", "answer": "based", "question": "Panjan Air, an airline ___ in Singapore, is offering budget flights to Bangkok and Jakarta."}, "310": {"1": "specifics", "2": "specifies", "3": "specific", "4": "specify", "answer": "specific", "question": "Mesmio, provider of premium television content, welcomes ___ ideas for improving our service."}, "311": {"1": "directing", "2": "directly", "3": "directs", "4": "direct", "answer": "directly", "question": "The conclusions from our analysis turned out to be ___ applicable to the budget problem."}, "312": {"1": "to transform", "2": "transformation", "3": "is transforming", "4": "transformed", "answer": "to transform", "question": "The proposal ___ the vacant land on Spring Street into a community garden will be voted on this Monday."}, "313": {"1": "affect", "2": "replace", "3": "certify", "4": "associate", "answer": "certify", "question": "After quality control inspectors ___ that all specifications are met, the product can be shipped."}, "314": {"1": "ethical", "2": "vast", "3": "absolute", "4": "economic", "answer": "vast", "question": "The ___ meadowlands surrounding the museum are designated as wildlife habitat."}, "315": {"1": "All", "2": "Others", "3": "Their own", "4": "Each one", "answer": "Each one", "question": "___ of Mitesh Sandu's international performances was filmed for the documentary."}, "316": {"1": "will", "2": "when", "3": "that", "4": "if", "answer": "that", "question": "New tax incentives reward local businesses ___ decrease their water consumption."}, "317": {"1": "conspicuously", "2": "marginally", "3": "regrettably", "4": "intriguingly", "answer": "marginally", "question": "Based on new data, Min-Soo Trucking's proposal to expand its business to Southeast Asia would be only ___ successful."}, "318": {"1": "high", "2": "higher", "3": "highly", "4": "highest", "answer": "highly", "question": "Mr. Ashburton has been ___ recommended by all three of his references."}, "319": {"1": "he", "2": "his", "3": "him", "4": "himself", "answer": "his", "question": "Mr. Choi wants to know when the illustrations will be ready for ___ review."}, "320": {"1": "in", "2": "by", "3": "out", "4": "for", "answer": "for", "question": "The project meeting has been rescheduled ___ tomorrow because of the bad weather."}, "321": {"1": "easy", "2": "easily", "3": "easier", "4": "ease", "answer": "easier", "question": "Smooth Tek's newest software makes it much ___ for business owners to create newsletters."}, "322": {"1": "opening", "2": "opened", "3": "opens", "4": "open", "answer": "opening", "question": "By ___ offices in London, Paris, and Madrid, Sedgehill Ltd. has continued its growth into markets overseas."}, "323": {"1": "So", "2": "Lf", "3": "But", "4": "Why", "answer": "Lf", "question": "___ the kiln's heat is set too high, the ceramic objects inside may be ruined"}, "324": {"1": "wide", "2": "widen", "3": "most widely", "4": "more widely", "answer": "most widely", "question": "The National Overview is the fourth ___ distributed newspaper in the northeastern region."}, "325": {"1": "invented", "2": "exceeded", "3": "supervised", "4": "communicated", "answer": "invented", "question": "Dr. Lin, the keynote speaker at this years Southeast Dentistry Convention, ___ several groundbreaking dental devices."}, "326": {"1": "expenses", "2": "functions", "3": "customers", "4": "occasions", "answer": "expenses", "question": "Rose s Bistro will close next month due to escalating operating ___ ."}, "327": {"1": "congratulations", "2": "congratulate", "3": "congratulating", "4": "congratulatory", "answer": "congratulations", "question": "During yesterday's meeting, Ms. Milne offered her ___ to the sales team for their excellent results this quarter."}, "328": {"1": "important", "2": "likely", "3": "probable", "4": "recent", "answer": "likely", "question": "The employee satisfaction survey results are ___ to differ among departments."}, "329": {"1": "either", "2": "those", "3": "which", "4": "whom", "answer": "those", "question": "The course taught by Prof. Brennink is intended for ___ interested in medical or health-related careers."}, "330": {"1": "separates", "2": "separately", "3": "separating", "4": "separation", "answer": "separately", "question": "Starting September 1, the accounting department will issue travel reimbursements ___ from biweekly paychecks."}, "331": {"1": "lengthy", "2": "plenty", "3": "sizable", "4": "durable", "answer": "sizable", "question": "The planned construction of several new office buildings in Newbury has created a ___ demand for skilled workers."}, "332": {"1": "monitoring", "2": "monitors", "3": "monitored", "4": "monitor", "answer": "monitor", "question": "The new computer security program allows users to ___ any suspicious activity on their account."}, "333": {"1": "expansion", "2": "expanded", "3": "expanse", "4": "expand", "answer": "expansion", "question": "The ___ of the Kawagoe factory has had a significant impact on Inagi Technology employees' productivity."}, "334": {"1": "then", "2": "while", "3": "ever since", "4": "as soon as", "answer": "as soon as", "question": "Please review the repair estimate carefully ___ it has been received from the maintenance department."}, "335": {"1": "Promotions", "2": "Offerings", "3": "Productions", "4": "Responsibilities", "answer": "Responsibilities", "question": "___ of the marketing assistant include coordinating focus groups and writing detailed reports."}, "336": {"1": "considered", "2": "considering", "3": "considers", "4": "consider", "answer": "considering", "question": "The product development team for Herbeve Cosmetics is ___ a package redesign to try to increase sales."}, "337": {"1": "Because of", "2": "Instead of", "3": "Rather than", "4": "Such as", "answer": "Because of", "question": "___ an increase in small, individual furnaces, glassblowing has become a more accessible and popular art medium."}, "338": {"1": "factor", "2": "role", "3": "basis", "4": "agency", "answer": "factor", "question": "Our investment in solar energy was a key ___ in achieving energy independence."}, "339": {"1": "reflected", "2": "reflects", "3": "reflecting", "4": "reflect", "answer": "reflected", "question": "Payments made to your account after the invoice was generated are not ___ in the balance shown."}, "340": {"1": "pending", "2": "regarding", "3": "among", "4": "throughout", "answer": "regarding", "question": "See our media kit for facts and information ___ our line of lighting equipment."}, "341": {"1": "as well as", "2": "overall", "3": "thanks to", "4": "even if", "answer": "thanks to", "question": "The lawyers report that the merger was successfully concluded ___ last-minute negotiations."}, "342": {"1": "confiding", "2": "confides", "3": "confidential", "4": "confidentially", "answer": "confidential", "question": "Mr. Hong will outline the procedures for handling customers' ___ information."}, "343": {"1": "expressed", "2": "specialized", "3": "signaled", "4": "established", "answer": "established", "question": "Last year, the Fromley Company ___ an internship program for trade school students studying electrical technology."}, "344": {"1": "Less", "2": "Enough", "3": "Apart", "4": "Seldom", "answer": "Seldom", "question": "___ in the news, the Honorable Cynthia Rengle is now making headlines with her proposal to drastically reduce local taxes"}, "345": {"1": "furthermore", "2": "without", "3": "nevertheless", "4": "neither", "answer": "nevertheless", "question": "Despite being the audience's least favorite film at the star Film Festival, Lost Dog ___ won the critics' award for best animation."}, "346": {"1": "cooperative", "2": "deliberate", "3": "extensive", "4": "adequate", "answer": "extensive", "question": "We found the staffplex payroll management system to be the only one ___ for our needs."}, "347": {"1": "arguably", "2": "reportedly", "3": "productively", "4": "incrementally", "answer": "productively", "question": "Ms. Mills has correctly predicted that sales would increase ___ as the company's radio advertisement continues to air."}, "348": {"1": "he", "2": "him", "3": "his", "4": "himself", "answer": "his", "question": "The newspaper editor, Mr. Lim has invited a distinguished architect to write about ___ famous buildings."}, "349": {"1": "when", "2": "both", "3": "which", "4": "some", "answer": "both", "question": "All employees are required to attend ___ the morning and the afternoon sessions of the training workshop on Friday."}, "350": {"1": "collaborative", "2": "collaborate", "3": "collaborated", "4": "collaboration", "answer": "collaboration", "question": "This course provides students with the tools for thinking about ways to enhance ___ among races, ethnic groups and social classes."}, "351": {"1": "promptly", "2": "prompt", "3": "promptness", "4": "prompts", "answer": "promptly", "question": "The new employee orientation will be held in one of the Training Facility classrooms and it will begin ___ at 8:00 a.m."}, "352": {"1": "conclusive", "2": "absolute", "3": "completed", "4": "exhausted", "answer": "completed", "question": "Employees who wish to participate in the FSA Program must submit their ___ paperwork to the Human Resources Department by Dec. 16."}, "353": {"1": "deliverable", "2": "deliverer", "3": "deliver", "4": "delivery", "answer": "delivery", "question": "UPS guarantees the ___ of your important shipments from the U.S. to more than  international cities."}, "354": {"1": "out", "2": "on", "3": "to", "4": "for", "answer": "on", "question": "Old magazines and important papers are stored ___ the top shelf in labeled files."}, "355": {"1": "service", "2": "serve", "3": "will serve", "4": "servings", "answer": "service", "question": "The Sharp Hotel has decided to offer a free shuttle ___ to the beach every day from 8 a.m. to 9 p.m., leaving every hour."}, "356": {"1": "proceeding", "2": "remarking", "3": "developing", "4": "persuading", "answer": "developing", "question": "The committee recommended ___ more systematic procedures for the management of employee performance evaluations."}, "357": {"1": "necessity", "2": "necessitate", "3": "necessarily", "4": "necessary", "answer": "necessary", "question": "It will be ___ to develop an updated employee manual incorporating the many changes that have occurred over the past twelve years."}, "358": {"1": "presentation", "2": "determination", "3": "preparation", "4": "administration", "answer": "preparation", "question": "In ___ for the Christmas shopping season, the local fire department has started inspecting malls and other business establishments in the Busan area."}, "359": {"1": "ease", "2": "easy", "3": "easily", "4": "eased", "answer": "easily", "question": "Mr. Lim could solve the problem with the Sonya  Software ___ after reading the enclosed manual."}, "360": {"1": "exceptionally", "2": "personally", "3": "essentially", "4": "commonly", "answer": "personally", "question": "When you initiate conversations with your new employees, greet them ___ to make them feel comfortable and listen with interest."}, "361": {"1": "in promoting", "2": "for the promotion", "3": "by promoting", "4": "as a promotion", "answer": "in promoting", "question": "Infosys Technologies Ltd. has instituted an annual award of $5 million for Korean scientists who have achieved excellence ___ research in biotechnology."}, "362": {"1": "When", "2": "While", "3": "Instead", "4": "During", "answer": "During", "question": "___ the meeting, agenda items are discussed by the board of directors and minutes are taken by the secretary."}, "363": {"1": "as", "2": "out", "3": "up", "4": "from", "answer": "from", "question": "Please forward the message ___ the advertising agency in Busan to Mrs. Hwang's office directly."}, "364": {"1": "pursue", "2": "fasten", "3": "reduce", "4": "refrain", "answer": "reduce", "question": "The automobile industry is becoming increasingly reliant on computers to improve efficiency and ___ costs."}, "365": {"1": "increase", "2": "increasing", "3": "increases", "4": "increasingly", "answer": "increasingly", "question": "An ___ large number of our customers prefer the payment convenience of debit cards."}, "366": {"1": "is overseeing", "2": "was overseen", "3": "has been overseeing", "4": "be overseen", "answer": "was overseen", "question": "Ms. Kennedy was given the responsibility for managing the downtown building project, which ___ by the board of directors."}, "367": {"1": "while", "2": "after", "3": "then", "4": "but", "answer": "but", "question": "Recommendations for the prize will be considered by the committee, ___ are not necessarily required to receive it."}, "368": {"1": "need", "2": "idea", "3": "cause", "4": "time", "answer": "time", "question": "When renting a car, it is important to take ___ to inspect the car thoroughly and document any damage including minor scratches."}, "369": {"1": "pleasure", "2": "please", "3": "pleasing", "4": "pleased", "answer": "pleased", "question": "Ms. Jespersen is ___ to accept your invitation to become a member of the Washington Community Reinvestment Association."}, "370": {"1": "retrieve", "2": "grant", "3": "donate", "4": "require", "answer": "grant", "question": "The Family and Medical Leave Act requires employers to ___ employees up to 12 weeks of unpaid leave a year for family medical emergencies."}, "371": {"1": "care", "2": "careful", "3": "carefully", "4": "more carefully", "answer": "carefully", "question": "Since pension benefits may be a major source of your retirement income, you should ___ consider the following options before making your decision."}, "372": {"1": "across", "2": "under", "3": "for", "4": "down", "answer": "for", "question": "The marketing team members are supposed to be on time ___ tomorrow's advertising planning meeting."}, "373": {"1": "inaccuracy", "2": "inaccurately", "3": "inaccurate", "4": "inaccuracies", "answer": "inaccurately", "question": "Because the number of staff registering for the seminar was ___ estimated, Mr. Kim had to book a larger meeting room."}, "374": {"1": "agree", "2": "agreed", "3": "agrees", "4": "agreeing", "answer": "agreeing", "question": "Before ___ to the terms of use, please know that membership is not free, but, we do offer many different membership rates."}, "375": {"1": "on the other hand", "2": "as well as", "3": "instead of", "4": "as soon as", "answer": "as soon as", "question": "We are planning to launch the new product throughout the country ___ a reliable distributor and a wholesale dealer are found."}, "376": {"1": "what", "2": "which", "3": "where", "4": "whose", "answer": "which", "question": "The North East is one of the best regions in ___ to start a new business, according to Business and Enterprise North East statistics."}, "377": {"1": "construction", "2": "movement", "3": "output", "4": "research", "answer": "output", "question": "The affordable land prices, good drainage and excellent soil conditions have been conducive to the high agricultural ___ of our region."}, "378": {"1": "even though", "2": "in order to", "3": "in addition to", "4": "whether", "answer": "in addition to", "question": "While the supervisor is responsible for preventing injuries, each worker must be attentive to their personal safety, ___ the safety of their coworkers."}, "379": {"1": "confide", "2": "confides", "3": "confidential", "4": "confidentially", "answer": "confidential", "question": "Pioneer Steel guarantees that all information gathered through this website is strictly ___ and used only by Pioneer Steel."}, "380": {"1": "if", "2": "where", "3": "how", "4": "so", "answer": "how", "question": "No matter ___ busy they are, all workers at the factory are encouraged to take short breaks every 50 minutes."}, "381": {"1": "pictured", "2": "informed", "3": "sampled", "4": "exposed", "answer": "pictured", "question": "The pockets are a bit different than the ones ___ in the catalog, as the zipper is on the side of the pocket, not in the center of the pocket."}, "382": {"1": "next to", "2": "ahead of", "3": "down", "4": "aboard", "answer": "ahead of", "question": "It is important to arrive at the airport 45 to 90 minutes ___ your scheduled departure time."}, "383": {"1": "cautiously", "2": "accidentally", "3": "equally", "4": "tightly", "answer": "cautiously", "question": "Korean information technology firms are ___ predicting an economic upturn in the fourth quarter despite concerns over a strong won and surging oil prices."}, "384": {"1": "predict", "2": "predicted", "3": "predicting", "4": "prediction", "answer": "predicted", "question": "The quarterly sales report indicated that the company's profits were 11 percent higher than previously ___ ."}, "385": {"1": "presented", "2": "healthy", "3": "physical", "4": "immediate", "answer": "healthy", "question": "The new spring menu at Outback Restaurant features fresh salads made with ___ blends of Asian and European ingredients."}, "386": {"1": "location", "2": "transition", "3": "cooperation", "4": "suspension", "answer": "transition", "question": "The city of Calgary has made a successful ___ from an industrial town to a bustling tourist destination, with the creation of shops, restaurants, and hotels."}, "387": {"1": "arranging", "2": "approaching", "3": "setting", "4": "declaring", "answer": "approaching", "question": "The deadline for registration is rapidly ___ , so contact our office immediately if you are interested in attending."}, "388": {"1": "accessory", "2": "design", "3": "store", "4": "notice", "answer": "store", "question": "Russell Jewels is opening a new ___ in Rowland this Saturday."}, "389": {"1": "is sending", "2": "sending", "3": "sent", "4": "send", "answer": "send", "question": "Ms. Rosebush must ___ her application form to Beal City University by September 5."}, "390": {"1": "himself", "2": "his", "3": "him", "4": "he", "answer": "him", "question": "Mr. Cline requested his boss to authorize ___ to organize the event."}, "391": {"1": "went", "2": "prepared", "3": "began", "4": "started", "answer": "went", "question": "Some of the administrative staff ___ on a business trip to conclude a contract with a business partner."}, "392": {"1": "beneficiary", "2": "benefits", "3": "beneficial", "4": "beneficially", "answer": "benefits", "question": "To receive the full ___ of this coupon, please register the serial number at our shop's official website."}, "393": {"1": "form", "2": "tell", "3": "create", "4": "take", "answer": "take", "question": "Judy Arnold volunteered to ___ on a new research project in cooperation with senior researcher Fred Ferguson."}, "394": {"1": "experiencing", "2": "experience", "3": "experienced", "4": "experiences", "answer": "experienced", "question": "As an ___ teacher, Mr. Grant gave a speech on the importance of fostering the habit of reading."}, "395": {"1": "off", "2": "with", "3": "among", "4": "through", "answer": "with", "question": "Cellist Irene Hudson is arranging an accompanied performance ___ the Toronto Philharmonic Orchestra."}, "396": {"1": "about", "2": "during.", "3": "from", "4": "before", "answer": "before", "question": "All workers must be equipped with safety devices such as helmets ___ entering the construction site."}, "397": {"1": "their", "2": "them", "3": "they", "4": "theirs", "answer": "they", "question": "Guests must show the invitation ___ received at the entrance to be escorted to their seats."}, "398": {"1": "nearly", "2": "probably", "3": "clearly", "4": "finely", "answer": "nearly", "question": "The Caldwell Bridge was around ___  years before it was demolished due to safety concerns."}, "399": {"1": "create", "2": "creative", "3": "creating", "4": "creativity", "answer": "creative", "question": "Wagner Computers is looking for ___ ideas from employees that could contribute to the development of some new software."}, "400": {"1": "in", "2": "above", "3": "from", "4": "on", "answer": "on", "question": "A doubled remittance charge is placed ___ international money transfers compared to domestic ones."}, "401": {"1": "what", "2": "which", "3": "where", "4": "whom", "answer": "which", "question": "Winn Furniture ___ has been in business for more than  years strives to provide our customers with functional and durable furniture."}, "402": {"1": "later", "2": "like", "3": "but", "4": "for", "answer": "but", "question": "Navarro Paper Company devised a new manufacturing system ___ due to technological difficulties it has not yet been implemented."}, "403": {"1": "clarify", "2": "clearly", "3": "clear", "4": "clarity", "answer": "clear", "question": "According to a public opinion survey carried out by the Dushville Gazette, there is a ___ preference for a new mayor rather than the incumbent one."}, "404": {"1": "deliberate", "2": "practical", "3": "durable", "4": "leading", "answer": "leading", "question": "Letson University's Floyd Medical School is a ___ academic institute which has produced many capable doctors."}, "405": {"1": "develop", "2": "developing", "3": "developed", "4": "develops", "answer": "developing", "question": "Senior researchers at the Russell Botanic Institute are currently ___ new medicine consisting only of natural ingredients."}, "406": {"1": "Accounting", "2": "Accounted", "3": "Accountable", "4": "Accountant", "answer": "Accounting", "question": "___ firms must abide by the laws of the respective state they belong to when conducting an audit."}, "407": {"1": "eventually", "2": "soon", "3": "around", "4": "already", "answer": "already", "question": "You cannot make additional orders for office supplies as the budget has ___ been finalized."}, "408": {"1": "collected", "2": "implemented", "3": "competed", "4": "diverted", "answer": "implemented", "question": "To improve the athletic performance of the football team, the team's coach has ___ a new exercise routine."}, "409": {"1": "directed", "2": "director", "3": "direct", "4": "directly", "answer": "directly", "question": "To complete the transfer process, transfer students should send their transcripts ___ from their previous school's administrative office."}, "410": {"1": "present", "2": "announce", "3": "dispose", "4": "place", "answer": "present", "question": "Volunteers must ___ identification cards to flood victims before carrying out any kind of assistance."}, "411": {"1": "extremely", "2": "immediately", "3": "numerously", "4": "clearly", "answer": "immediately", "question": "Magneta Computing Company had to ___ recall the Fosno- laptops when they turned out to have defects in their hardware."}, "412": {"1": "preparation", "2": "prepare", "3": "prepared", "4": "prepares", "answer": "prepared", "question": "The final draft of the prototype for our newly developed product must be ___ so it can be displayed at the board of trustees' meeting."}, "413": {"1": "range", "2": "ability", "3": "amount", "4": "array", "answer": "ability", "question": "Applicants for the vacant job position must have the ___ to categorize different types of documents, prepare presentation materials, and carry out administrative work."}, "414": {"1": "period", "2": "periodic", "3": "periodical", "4": "periodically", "answer": "periodically", "question": "To ensure a safe trip, Wiota Railway Services ___ conducts technical examinations on all its tracks and trains."}, "415": {"1": "on", "2": "while", "3": "plus", "4": "in addition", "answer": "plus", "question": "You can upgrade the size of the pizza you order ___ three free beverages for no extra charge when you order through the Internet."}, "416": {"1": "preference", "2": "advantage", "3": "recognition", "4": "remittance", "answer": "preference", "question": "If you need a translator at the conference, please check your language ___ on the registration form."}, "417": {"1": "besides", "2": "according to", "3": "otherwise", "4": "due to", "answer": "due to", "question": "The quarterly revenue of Delci Hair Products increased by 10 percent ___ the new marketing strategy they employed."}, "418": {"1": "have been researched", "2": "have researched", "3": "researching", "4": "will be researched", "answer": "have researched", "question": "Students are required to summarize what they ___ for their graduation thesis."}, "419": {"1": "Even", "2": "Besides", "3": "Among", "4": "Since", "answer": "Since", "question": "___ the outbreak of an unidentified disease, the sales volume of personal hygiene items has reached an all-time record."}, "420": {"1": "cooperating", "2": "alongside", "3": "besides", "4": "despite", "answer": "alongside", "question": "Civilians in the southern part of New Zealand are putting every effort into extinguishing bushfires ___ local firefighters."}, "421": {"1": "shortage", "2": "financial", "3": "substitute", "4": "decision", "answer": "substitute", "question": "Because Philip Dalton was absent due to an injury from last game, a ___ player was put into the semifinals."}, "422": {"1": "onto", "2": "above", "3": "than", "4": "within", "answer": "than", "question": "Ferry service at Leaton Island charges 20 percent more on weekends ___ on weekdays."}, "423": {"1": "picturesque", "2": "monetary", "3": "horrible", "4": "singular", "answer": "picturesque", "question": "The movie is quite popular because of its ___ scenes and solid plot, both of which have been praised by movie critics."}, "424": {"1": "practices", "2": "transactions", "3": "absences", "4": "registrations", "answer": "transactions", "question": "Business ___ must be accurately recorded and confirmed by the heads of each respective department before they are delivered to the company's accountant."}, "425": {"1": "facilitated", "2": "facilitate", "3": "to facilitate", "4": "facilitation", "answer": "to facilitate", "question": "Remsell Industries is implementing an incentive program for employees ___ heightened productivity."}, "426": {"1": "punctual", "2": "rhetoric", "3": "contented", "4": "strategic", "answer": "strategic", "question": "President Bruce Dixon of Dewitt Advertising has been promoting a ___ partnership with local businesses."}, "427": {"1": "made of", "2": "came as", "3": "spoke of", "4": "came across", "answer": "came as", "question": "Personnel changes within the marketing department \" ___ no surprise, as it completely failed on the most recent project."}, "428": {"1": "she", "2": "herself", "3": "hers", "4": "her", "answer": "herself", "question": "Emily introduced ___ before starting the interview for the management job."}, "429": {"1": "Response", "2": "Responding", "3": "Respond", "4": "Responds", "answer": "Respond", "question": "___ to the e-mail from the supervisor as soon as possible and ask questions if anything is unclear."}, "430": {"1": "measure", "2": "convention", "3": "scheme", "4": "purpose", "answer": "purpose", "question": "The ___ of the retreat was to allow all of the employees to bond with one another."}, "431": {"1": "protect", "2": "protection", "3": "protective", "4": "protecting", "answer": "protect", "question": "The wildlife preserve was created by the Florida Nature Commission to ___ the state's endangered species."}, "432": {"1": "prior", "2": "timely", "3": "late", "4": "old", "answer": "prior", "question": "Staff members with ___ engagements need not feel obliged to attend next week's field trip."}, "433": {"1": "to arrive", "2": "have arrived", "3": "are arriving", "4": "arrival", "answer": "are arriving", "question": "The building's new tenants ___ in the next couple of days, so the staff is getting everything ready."}, "434": {"1": "elaborated", "2": "elaborately", "3": "elaborate", "4": "elaborator", "answer": "elaborately", "question": "The banquet hall was ___ decorated for the fund-raising gala on June 11."}, "435": {"1": "activate", "2": "active", "3": "action", "4": "activity", "answer": "active", "question": "The Whitby Town Council recently prepared a brochure recommending ways that residents can play an ___ role in the community."}, "436": {"1": "came up with", "2": "dropped by", "3": "looked in on", "4": "ran out of", "answer": "came up with", "question": "Ms. Johnson ___ a feasible solution to the customer's network problem."}, "437": {"1": "within", "2": "through", "3": "under", "4": "among", "answer": "under", "question": "The human resources department is ___ pressure to find a replacement for the senior accountant."}, "438": {"1": "conveniently", "2": "temporarily", "3": "consistently", "4": "wishfully", "answer": "consistently", "question": "BelTrax has ___ ranked as one of the top providers of marketing research since its foundation seven years ago."}, "439": {"1": "will have furnished", "2": "would furnish", "3": "had furnished", "4": "to furnish", "answer": "would furnish", "question": "Mansfield Chemical built an extension that ___ additional space for the newly purchased machinery."}, "440": {"1": "defensive", "2": "creative", "3": "minor", "4": "critical", "answer": "minor", "question": "As the argument raised at the last meeting was on a ___ point, it did not affect the proposal's overall plan."}, "441": {"1": "Anyone", "2": "Those", "3": "Though", "4": "Seldom", "answer": "Those", "question": "___ who still wish to submit applications after the deadline must pay a $45 late fee in order to be considered."}, "442": {"1": "attracted", "2": "reserved", "3": "continued", "4": "suggested", "answer": "suggested", "question": "Everyone at Hammond Construction, Inc. was surprised to find out that the year's greatest cost saving measure was ___ by an intern."}, "443": {"1": "formed", "2": "formation", "3": "formative", "4": "form", "answer": "formative", "question": "Upon his retirement, Mr. Ross was highly commended for his vital contributions during the company's ___ years."}, "444": {"1": "objection", "2": "expansion", "3": "overview", "4": "experience", "answer": "overview", "question": "Ms. Waddill provided a few members of her department with an ___ covering the key points of the CEO's speech."}, "445": {"1": "behind", "2": "from", "3": "regarding", "4": "across", "answer": "regarding", "question": "The doubts among investors ___ the company's ability to expand in the coming year led to a steep decline in the stock's price."}, "446": {"1": "Attend", "2": "Attendee", "3": "Attendant", "4": "Attendance", "answer": "Attendance", "question": "___ at the Latipa Film Festival increased by nearly 30 percent this year thanks to an online marketing campaign."}, "447": {"1": "thereby", "2": "even though", "3": "aside from", "4": "notwithstanding", "answer": "notwithstanding", "question": "During the summer, rooms at the Marigold Hotel are always fully booked ___ the large size of the facility."}, "448": {"1": "permit", "2": "permissive", "3": "permits", "4": "permissively", "answer": "permit", "question": "All employees need a written ___ from the manager to access the office during off-hours."}, "449": {"1": "simplified", "2": "similar", "3": "controversial", "4": "contradictory", "answer": "simplified", "question": "Since the trainees were having difficulty following the instruction manual, the trainer decided to create a ___ version."}, "450": {"1": "worthiest", "2": "worth", "3": "worthier", "4": "worthy", "answer": "worthier", "question": "HGS Company was awarded the construction contract as it had a ___ bid than any of the other competing firms."}, "451": {"1": "deliver", "2": "register", "3": "showcase", "4": "imply", "answer": "deliver", "question": "Ms. Nissim, the founder of Hartwell Industries, will ___ a talk on effective sales strategies at the marketing convention."}, "452": {"1": "basic", "2": "decisive", "3": "effective", "4": "disposable", "answer": "disposable", "question": "Many people have succeeded in reducing household waste by buying fewer ___ products."}, "453": {"1": "has considered", "2": "is considered", "3": "is considering", "4": "considered", "answer": "is considered", "question": "The next work of art for sale ___ one of the finest paintings ever exhibited at the Cole Morton Museum."}, "454": {"1": "criticism", "2": "persuasion", "3": "deliberation", "4": "recognition", "answer": "recognition", "question": "The tenor received widespread ___ for his superb performances at the annual opera festival."}, "455": {"1": "Besides", "2": "Rather", "3": "Among", "4": "Along", "answer": "Besides", "question": "___ having television stations across the state, the American Media Corporation owns several magazines and newspapers."}, "456": {"1": "respectful", "2": "respecting", "3": "respected", "4": "respective", "answer": "respected", "question": "Delegates from the industry's most widely ___ social media marketing firms will speak at next week's summit."}, "457": {"1": "since", "2": "thereafter", "3": "consequently", "4": "now", "answer": "thereafter", "question": "TNP Tech will allow users to download its new software for free until September 1 but will start charging for it ___"}, "458": {"1": "but", "2": "neither", "3": "each", "4": "that", "answer": "but", "question": "The prices in the catalog include both state and national taxes ___ not delivery charges."}, "459": {"1": "separate", "2": "separately", "3": "separates", "4": "separation", "answer": "separate", "question": "Cardston Corporation's fiscal records are kept in ___ boxes and are stored according to year."}, "460": {"1": "regret", "2": "support", "3": "strategy", "4": "comfort", "answer": "support", "question": "Prior to permanently shutting down, Rebound Media thanked customers for the ___ they had shown over the years."}, "461": {"1": "away", "2": "above", "3": "forward", "4": "anywhere", "answer": "anywhere", "question": "Visitors to Holidayland need not worry about bringing enough cash, as credit cards are accepted ___ in the resort."}, "462": {"1": "distribute", "2": "distributors", "3": "distributive", "4": "to distribute", "answer": "distributors", "question": "Having decided to enter the Asian market, Edgeware Electronics is now seeking regional ___ for its products."}, "463": {"1": "Anyone", "2": "Others", "3": "Them", "4": "Nobody", "answer": "Anyone", "question": "___ who wants to reserve a conference room for a meeting can simply e-mail Ms. Bloomberg in administration."}, "464": {"1": "decide", "2": "decides", "3": "decided", "4": "deciding", "answer": "deciding", "question": "After ___ to build a new home in Victoria, Mr. Redmond hired an interior designer to assist him with decorating the house."}, "465": {"1": "explained", "2": "canceled", "3": "acquired", "4": "committed", "answer": "acquired", "question": "First Bonneville Bank ___ 35 branches of CPG Financial Trust for $90 million, strengthening its presence in the region."}, "466": {"1": "extent", "2": "extensive", "3": "extensively", "4": "extend", "answer": "extensive", "question": "Psychologists conducted an ___ study about the negative effects of video games on young children."}, "467": {"1": "hardly", "2": "recently", "3": "habitually", "4": "potentially", "answer": "recently", "question": "Reginald Rentals ___ opened a branch in Sacramento, and after a very short time the new location became profitable."}, "468": {"1": "out of", "2": "toward", "3": "owing to", "4": "versus", "answer": "toward", "question": "The city council has taken steps ___ improving air quality by introducing measures that limit factory pollution."}, "469": {"1": "temporary", "2": "inspected", "3": "sustained", "4": "instructive", "answer": "temporary", "question": "The factory is preparing to hire ___ workers for selected manufacturing plants to meet its quarterly production goals."}, "470": {"1": "Furthermore", "2": "Yet", "3": "Although", "4": "Hence", "answer": "Although", "question": "___ reviews for Leonard Atwood's new book were very positive, orders for the novel were lower than the publisher had expected."}, "471": {"1": "on", "2": "from", "3": "in", "4": "of", "answer": "in", "question": "Those planning to join the historic district tour are asked to be ___ the center's reception area at 8 A.M. tomorrow."}, "472": {"1": "Along", "2": "While", "3": "Once", "4": "Apart", "answer": "While", "question": "___ ski resorts are frequently busier during peak season in the winter, they do attract hikers in the summer."}, "473": {"1": "many", "2": "few", "3": "much", "4": "a lot", "answer": "much", "question": "The organizer of the publicity convention said there is still ___ work to be done, but was not concerned about meeting the deadline."}, "474": {"1": "trades", "2": "waives", "3": "resists", "4": "confines", "answer": "waives", "question": "The appliance maker ___ all repair charges for items that are accompanied by valid warranties."}, "475": {"1": "most attentive", "2": "attentive", "3": "more attentively", "4": "attention", "answer": "more attentively", "question": "The executive director has asked all production supervisors to monitor the work schedule ___ in the future."}, "476": {"1": "talent", "2": "contest", "3": "promise", "4": "trend", "answer": "talent", "question": "Ms. Tennyson has a ___ for spotting good investments and a reputation for being bold and visionary."}, "477": {"1": "manages", "2": "to manage", "3": "had managed", "4": "will manage", "answer": "had managed", "question": "By the time its weeklong promotion was over, Polk Mobile ___ to sell almost its entire inventory of Kelstra smart phones."}, "478": {"1": "which", "2": "this", "3": "some", "4": "who", "answer": "this", "question": "With the financial crisis over and banks eager to provide loans, it has never been ___ easy for the average person to own a home."}, "479": {"1": "beside", "2": "without", "3": "inside", "4": "under", "answer": "without", "question": "Dr. Boyle does not generally see any patients ___ appointments, except for cases of emergency."}, "480": {"1": "subscribe", "2": "subscriber", "3": "subscription", "4": "subscribes", "answer": "subscription", "question": "Customers who sign up for a one-year ___ to Emerald Cable TV by the end of the week will receive a month of free service."}, "481": {"1": "eligible", "2": "occasional", "3": "idle", "4": "absolute", "answer": "absolute", "question": "Well attended by dozens of enthusiasts, the launch party for Fiesta Motors' newest sports car was deemed an ___ success."}, "482": {"1": "appoint", "2": "appointed", "3": "will appoint", "4": "has been appointed", "answer": "has been appointed", "question": "Hector Calma ___ project leader for all Axos activities based in South Africa and is busy preparing to move there for an extended period."}, "483": {"1": "sudden", "2": "delicate", "3": "lenient", "4": "vague", "answer": "delicate", "question": "The supervisor is skilled at managing the ___ balance between the needs of staff and those of upper management."}, "484": {"1": "definition", "2": "policy", "3": "readership", "4": "broadcast", "answer": "readership", "question": "Even though subscriptions to the The Marinberg Herald's print edition have steadily declined, its online ___ continues to grow."}, "485": {"1": "So", "2": "Whether", "3": "While", "4": "Among", "answer": "Whether", "question": "___ the malfunctions with the Clarity Dishwasher are due to defects or low-quality materials is still being investigated."}, "486": {"1": "Instead of", "2": "Up to", "3": "Regardless of", "4": "Just as", "answer": "Just as", "question": "___ those in the delivery industry had predicted, Volo-Air's new routes helped boost its quarterly earnings significantly."}, "487": {"1": "operate", "2": "solidify", "3": "depart", "4": "prevent", "answer": "solidify", "question": "The mayor was able to ___ her plans for improving job creation through the help of local businesses."}, "488": {"1": "compiling", "2": "compiles", "3": "to compile", "4": "are compiling", "answer": "are compiling", "question": "The organizers of the fundraiser ___ a to-do list to hand out to volunteers."}, "489": {"1": "his", "2": "himself", "3": "he", "4": "him", "answer": "he", "question": "Mr. Chen was surprised by the promotion because ___ had not imagined that it could happen this year."}, "490": {"1": "distributes", "2": "distributing", "3": "distributed", "4": "distribution", "answer": "distributed", "question": "Since the report had not yet been ___ , Ms. Pantel had time to correct an error she had found."}, "491": {"1": "created", "2": "composed", "3": "preferred", "4": "assembled", "answer": "created", "question": "Once the account has been ___ , the user will be asked to re-enter their login name and password."}, "492": {"1": "progressive", "2": "progressively", "3": "progress", "4": "progressed", "answer": "progressively", "question": "The downtown branch of Jim's Burgers has ___ outperformed the chain's other locations in the city."}, "493": {"1": "necessary", "2": "diverse", "3": "deep", "4": "comparable", "answer": "diverse", "question": "The marketing department has launched a social media campaign in an effort to reach a more ___ audience."}, "494": {"1": "along", "2": "due to", "3": "as to", "4": "in addition to", "answer": "in addition to", "question": "Guests enjoyed the resort's new swimming pool ___ its outdoor restaurant."}, "495": {"1": "visibly", "2": "casually", "3": "typically", "4": "slightly", "answer": "typically", "question": "Employee assessments are ___ carried out in December but may be delayed until January."}, "496": {"1": "reside", "2": "residential", "3": "residents", "4": "residences", "answer": "residents", "question": "The ___ of the building had to find temporary accommodations during the renovation."}, "497": {"1": "accuracy", "2": "accurately", "3": "accurate", "4": "accurateness", "answer": "accurate", "question": "The fitness tracker is as perfectly ___ as the online advertisements say it is."}, "498": {"1": "shortened", "2": "fragile", "3": "reduced", "4": "preserved", "answer": "reduced", "question": "Tremont Airlines is offering ___ rates to passengers willing to travel late at night."}, "499": {"1": "sign", "2": "signing", "3": "signs", "4": "signed", "answer": "signing", "question": "Customers are asked to acknowledge receipt of their orders by ___ their names on a delivery form."}, "500": {"1": "currently", "2": "conveniently", "3": "knowingly", "4": "insufficiently", "answer": "conveniently", "question": "The trade show convention center was ___ located right next to the subway station, making it easily accessible."}, "501": {"1": "within", "2": "between", "3": "since", "4": "until", "answer": "within", "question": "Employees at Branford Computing Group are expected to respond to all technical support questions ___ 24 hours."}, "502": {"1": "submits", "2": "submitted", "3": "submit", "4": "submitting", "answer": "submitting", "question": "Applicants ___ a form for a new license should make certain that it is completely filled out."}, "503": {"1": "potent", "2": "potential", "3": "potentially", "4": "potentiality", "answer": "potentially", "question": "Storing dangerous chemicals near the main factory floor creates a ___ hazardous situation for the employees who work there."}, "504": {"1": "request", "2": "recruit", "3": "affiliate", "4": "adopt", "answer": "affiliate", "question": "Health One Hospice's board of directors hopes to ___ the institution with a partner that shares similar values."}, "505": {"1": "occasional", "2": "inviting", "3": "operating", "4": "apologetic", "answer": "inviting", "question": "The casting director was looking for an actor with an ___ tone of voice that can persuade listeners to buy a product."}, "506": {"1": "relates", "2": "related", "3": "relate", "4": "relation", "answer": "relation", "question": "The company issued a statement yesterday evening in ___ to the merger agreement."}, "507": {"1": "them", "2": "us", "3": "whom", "4": "which", "answer": "whom", "question": "A banquet was held to honor five employees, all of ___ have worked at the company for more than 20 years."}, "508": {"1": "though", "2": "barring", "3": "toward", "4": "with", "answer": "barring", "question": "Company policy requires that all staff members be at their desks before 9:30 A.M., ___ unforeseen circumstances."}, "509": {"1": "so far", "2": "plus", "3": "in case", "4": "whereas", "answer": "in case", "question": "Hotel employees are stationed at the check-in desk ___ you have any questions during your stay."}, "510": {"1": "constructed", "2": "engaged", "3": "enacted", "4": "measured", "answer": "enacted", "question": "New cycling safety regulations have just been ___ by the Ministry of Transportation."}, "511": {"1": "nominates", "2": "was nominated", "3": "was nominating", "4": "has nominated", "answer": "was nominated", "question": "Author Sylvia Feldman ___ for a Publishers Guild Award for her best-selling nonfiction novel, 21 Ravens."}, "512": {"1": "popular", "2": "more popular", "3": "popularity", "4": "most popular", "answer": "more popular", "question": "According to the study, the ___ a marketing campaign is among young people, the better a product is likely to sell."}, "513": {"1": "subsidiary", "2": "spectator", "3": "turnover", "4": "specialty", "answer": "subsidiary", "question": "The individual that will take on Paige Manufacturing's vice president position is expected to come from a ___ of the company."}, "514": {"1": "figures", "2": "benefits", "3": "profits", "4": "values", "answer": "benefits", "question": "The job comes with several significant ___ including health insurance and three weeks of paid leave."}, "515": {"1": "So that", "2": "Even though", "3": "If", "4": "Likewise", "answer": "If", "question": "___ the deposit for the apartment has been paid, the tenant can move in immediately."}, "516": {"1": "On behalf of", "2": "In compliance with", "3": "Instead of", "4": "Out of respect for", "answer": "In compliance with", "question": "___ the terms of his employment contract, Mr. Allen receives 1.5 times his regular pay rate for overtime hours."}, "517": {"1": "vote", "2": "summary", "3": "program", "4": "conference", "answer": "vote", "question": "The board of trustees took a ___ to decide who would replace the retiring company president."}, "518": {"1": "comfortably", "2": "comfortable", "3": "comforts", "4": "comforted", "answer": "comfortably", "question": "The airline's newly opened lounge in the international terminal can ___ hold up to  travelers."}, "519": {"1": "theirs", "2": "them", "3": "themselves", "4": "they", "answer": "themselves", "question": "Bryant Cosmetics' marketing team developed a promotional campaign by ___ , rather than outsourcing the work."}, "520": {"1": "alliance", "2": "evaluation", "3": "operation", "4": "leadership", "answer": "evaluation", "question": "The human resources director asked for a complete ___ of each staff member hired since January."}, "521": {"1": "training", "2": "trained", "3": "trainer", "4": "trains", "answer": "training", "question": "Those wishing to participate in the sales ___ that will be held in the coming month must sign up by noon on Wednesday."}, "522": {"1": "distributed", "2": "declared", "3": "donated", "4": "offered", "answer": "offered", "question": "Everyone attending one of Stanton Home's real estate investment workshops will be ___ the chance to apply for a loan."}, "523": {"1": "pricey", "2": "priced", "3": "pricing", "4": "pricier", "answer": "pricing", "question": "The city council will not consider a project proposal until its ___ has been determined by an advisory committee."}, "524": {"1": "very", "2": "far", "3": "such", "4": "many", "answer": "very", "question": "The train from Piterburgh to Chamberlin travels ___ slowly because it has to make a lot of stops."}, "525": {"1": "from", "2": "at", "3": "before", "4": "between", "answer": "from", "question": "Patrons who want a refund or exchange must make a request at the customer service center within one month ___ the date of purchase."}, "526": {"1": "to remind", "2": "are reminded", "3": "will be reminding", "4": "reminding", "answer": "are reminded", "question": "Audience members ___ to switch off all electronic devices if they attend any of the presentations scheduled throughout the conference."}, "527": {"1": "aboard", "2": "among", "3": "below", "4": "away", "answer": "aboard", "question": "The tour guide gave assurances and said that the group would not depart for its destination until everyone was definitely ___ the boat."}, "528": {"1": "appreciative", "2": "appreciate", "3": "appreciation", "4": "appreciatively", "answer": "appreciation", "question": "Those who volunteered to work at the festival were given free T-shirts and gift certificates out of ___ for their efforts."}, "529": {"1": "related", "2": "relative", "3": "relations", "4": "relatively", "answer": "relatively", "question": "The meals served at Nightinvale's take a ___ long time to cook, compared to other restaurants."}, "530": {"1": "simplify", "2": "simply", "3": "simplification", "4": "simplest", "answer": "simplest", "question": "After much discussion about the office's slow Internet connection, it was decided that the ___ solution would be to find a different provider."}, "531": {"1": "heavily", "2": "moderately", "3": "exclusively", "4": "additionally", "answer": "exclusively", "question": "Luxus Lotion is available ___ at Dashney Department Stores and cannot be found anywhere else."}, "532": {"1": "whom", "2": "which", "3": "that", "4": "whose", "answer": "whom", "question": "Mr. Chang asked the other board members to think about ___ they would like to nominate as the next chairperson."}, "533": {"1": "persuasive", "2": "grounded", "3": "confidential", "4": "capable", "answer": "capable", "question": "The evaluator found that Ms. Benning was highly ___ of leading a group and suggested she begin training for a managerial position."}, "534": {"1": "In spite of", "2": "Because", "3": "Except for", "4": "Close to", "answer": "In spite of", "question": "___ several complaints about the new security system, Chambers Corporation has decided to continue using it for now."}, "535": {"1": "ruling", "2": "shifting", "3": "convincing", "4": "limiting", "answer": "convincing", "question": "Even after presenting a ___ case to the board, Mr. Wright failed to persuade them to invest in the development project."}, "536": {"1": "divided", "2": "deducted", "3": "calculated", "4": "prolonged", "answer": "prolonged", "question": "The bank officer ___ that it would take Mr. Gordon two more years to settle his remaining debt if he continued to repay it in small amounts."}, "537": {"1": "on", "2": "by", "3": "with", "4": "around", "answer": "on", "question": "The purchasing manager can only order parts from companies that are found ___ the company's list of approved suppliers."}, "538": {"1": "also", "2": "ever", "3": "yet", "4": "always", "answer": "yet", "question": "Lawrence Graham leased his new office space two weeks ago, but he has ___ to move his firm to the location."}, "539": {"1": "identical", "2": "broad", "3": "dominant", "4": "similar", "answer": "dominant", "question": "After buying out its closest rival, Tele-SA will undoubtedly become South Africa's ___ mobile telecommunications provider."}, "540": {"1": "Once", "2": "As", "3": "After", "4": "Like", "answer": "As", "question": "___ Patterson Coffeehouse only has one branch in Australia, it plans to open six new stores by the conclusion of the fiscal year."}, "541": {"1": "had attracted", "2": "attracted", "3": "attracting", "4": "will attract", "answer": "will attract", "question": "When Rubicon Bank's growth rate is announced publicly next week, the information ___ a lot of interest from stock investors."}, "542": {"1": "fascination", "2": "fascinating", "3": "fascinated", "4": "fascinatedly", "answer": "fascinating", "question": "In his latest book, journalist Peter Ormond gives a ___ account of his experiences working in South America."}, "543": {"1": "generously", "2": "accidentally", "3": "immensely", "4": "intensively", "answer": "generously", "question": "In a gesture of goodwill, the San Mateo High School will ___ allow local residents to use its sports facilities on weekends."}, "544": {"1": "imagination", "2": "perspective", "3": "overview", "4": "reflection", "answer": "perspective", "question": "The public's reactions to the monument in Penn Park reveal a difference in ___ regarding how they feel tax money should be spent."}, "545": {"1": "at least", "2": "in advance", "3": "owing to", "4": "aside from", "answer": "owing to", "question": "The cruise ship coming in from Alaska was nearly three hours late arriving at the port in Vancouver ___ stormy weather conditions at sea."}, "546": {"1": "furthest", "2": "deepest", "3": "heaviest", "4": "strongest", "answer": "strongest", "question": "The ___ argument in favor of reevaluating the company's product lines has to be that sales have been consistently declining for the past two years."}, "547": {"1": "idea", "2": "time", "3": "entertainment", "4": "evidence", "answer": "evidence", "question": "Throughout history, scientists have gathered much ___ to support the theory that many animals possess high levels of intelligence."}, "548": {"1": "instruct", "2": "instructor", "3": "instructive", "4": "instruction", "answer": "instructor", "question": "A lecturer with over 10 years experience in information technology was the ___ for the seminar."}, "549": {"1": "so", "2": "whereas", "3": "or", "4": "even", "answer": "so", "question": "The Greenville branch of Clockwork will be closed for its annual inventory on Monday, ___ customers are asked to visit nearby locations instead."}, "550": {"1": "publicity", "2": "publicizing", "3": "public", "4": "publicized", "answer": "publicized", "question": "Spart-Gyms is advertising on television to ensure that the grand opening of its new athletics facility is widely ___"}, "551": {"1": "like", "2": "likely", "3": "liked", "4": "liking", "answer": "likely", "question": "After the marketing convention in Seychelles concludes, Mr. Stevens' staff is ___ to go on a weeklong vacation."}, "552": {"1": "host", "2": "revise", "3": "locate", "4": "remind", "answer": "host", "question": "The Maritime Museum is requesting donations from local businesses to ___ an upcoming series of educational lectures on regional history."}, "553": {"1": "will allow", "2": "is allowing", "3": "have allowed", "4": "to allow", "answer": "have allowed", "question": "Improvements to the subway system and the construction of bicycle lanes ___ city residents to reduce their reliance on cars in recent years."}, "554": {"1": "toward", "2": "between", "3": "since", "4": "during", "answer": "during", "question": "Free copies of Richard Lucas's new book, Lens Explorer, will be handed out to guests ___ his photo exhibit at El Patio Museum on Monday."}, "555": {"1": "varied", "2": "variable", "3": "vary", "4": "variety", "answer": "variety", "question": "Huntington Hotel provides a wide ___ of recreational activities for its guests, including water sports and sightseeing tours."}, "556": {"1": "what", "2": "which", "3": "these", "4": "who", "answer": "which", "question": "Customers will receive points for every purchase they make, ___ they can use to buy other products sold in the store."}, "557": {"1": "collects", "2": "collection", "3": "collective", "4": "collectively", "answer": "collective", "question": "The planning committee representatives made a ___ decision to postpone the event until the end of the month."}, "558": {"1": "expenses", "2": "investments", "3": "predictions", "4": "beliefs", "answer": "predictions", "question": "In a report, the Energy Department offered its best ___ of future oil prices in relation to the current world supply."}, "559": {"1": "diligent", "2": "tedious", "3": "classified", "4": "thoughtful", "answer": "tedious", "question": "As traveling by bus can be ___ , many passengers bring along a book or an electronic device for entertainment throughout their journeys."}, "560": {"1": "currently", "2": "shortly", "3": "slightly", "4": "originally", "answer": "originally", "question": "The opening of the warehouse in Philadelphia was ___ scheduled for next week, but construction problems have caused a significant delay."}, "561": {"1": "cleared", "2": "clearly", "3": "clearing", "4": "clearance", "answer": "clearly", "question": "Because there are many job openings, applicants must indicate which position they are seeking by ___ marking the appropriate box."}, "562": {"1": "qualified", "2": "expert", "3": "scarce", "4": "minor", "answer": "scarce", "question": "Prices for certain commodities are rising around the nation as they become more ___ ."}, "563": {"1": "correspond", "2": "corresponds", "3": "correspondingly", "4": "correspondence", "answer": "correspondence", "question": "While the CEO is away at the conference in Santiago, his assistant, Mr. Hale, will handle all official ___ on his behalf."}, "564": {"1": "mostly", "2": "nearly", "3": "extremely", "4": "promptly", "answer": "mostly", "question": "The vendors at the trade fair come ___ from Europe, but a few are from North America and other parts of the world."}, "565": {"1": "as if", "2": "after", "3": "in that", "4": "still", "answer": "after", "question": "The bank only evaluates small business loan applications ___ clients submit a feasibility report on their proposed operational strategy."}, "566": {"1": "past", "2": "out", "3": "without", "4": "up", "answer": "past", "question": "The tour bus drove ___ several notable sites in Victoria and made three stops in particularly interesting districts."}, "567": {"1": "experiments", "2": "accidents", "3": "damages", "4": "facilities", "answer": "damages", "question": "Blueline Insurance will immediately cover the cost of repairing clients' automobiles if ___ amount to less than $1,"}, "568": {"1": "Instead", "2": "Provided", "3": "In an effort to", "4": "So long as", "answer": "In an effort to", "question": "___ minimize distractions, Janzyll Incorporated discourages the personal use of telephones and the Internet while on duty."}, "569": {"1": "installed", "2": "dedicated", "3": "distributed", "4": "generated", "answer": "dedicated", "question": "The Simon Pillars Foundation is a global organization of architects ___ to building free homes for underprivileged families."}, "570": {"1": "memorable", "2": "memorize", "3": "memory", "4": "memorably", "answer": "memorable", "question": "The group was very pleased with the cruise arranged by stellar Travel, with many saying that it was the most ___ of holidays they had ever been on."}, "571": {"1": "readjust", "2": "readjusts", "3": "readjustments", "4": "readjusting", "answer": "readjusting", "question": "After working in London for five years, Ms. Shatya had trouble ___ to the climate in her home country of Malaysia."}, "572": {"1": "supposedly", "2": "explicitly", "3": "alternately", "4": "consecutively", "answer": "explicitly", "question": "Unless Kempley Telecom is ___ told to cancel a subscription, it will continue to charge users the regular monthly fee."}, "573": {"1": "eliminated", "2": "strived", "3": "climbed", "4": "outlined", "answer": "strived", "question": "Motivated by the chance to earn a large bonus, Carver Properties' sales team ___ to meet its annual quota."}, "574": {"1": "honorable", "2": "honored", "3": "honors", "4": "honoring", "answer": "honoring", "question": "A special recognition award was presented to Dane Evans, ___ him for his many years of service on the police force."}, "575": {"1": "gathered", "2": "convinced", "3": "implemented", "4": "channeled", "answer": "implemented", "question": "The Traffic Bureau ___ the new regulations to protect pedestrians and motorists from road accidents at night."}, "576": {"1": "each", "2": "whose", "3": "whatever", "4": "quite", "answer": "each", "question": "The Hotel Duvarney is committed to providing ___ of its guests with a pleasant and comfortable stay."}, "577": {"1": "investigations", "2": "interpretations", "3": "conditions", "4": "interactions", "answer": "investigations", "question": "The Labor Relations Commission is conducting thorough ___ into claims that some employees at the Hartford Company are being treated unfairly."}, "578": {"1": "attain", "2": "engage", "3": "permit", "4": "emerge", "answer": "engage", "question": "The City of Clarkston requires that retail outlets obtain business licenses in order to ___ in commerce."}, "579": {"1": "bring", "2": "brings", "3": "bringing", "4": "to bring", "answer": "bring", "question": "Danika Incorporated has promised substantial bonuses to employees who ___ in a minimum of  new customers this year."}, "580": {"1": "As if", "2": "Rather than", "3": "Not only", "4": "So long as", "answer": "So long as", "question": "___ the mayor but all of the members of the city council attended the New Year's celebrations at city hall."}, "581": {"1": "reason", "2": "reasonable", "3": "reasonably", "4": "reasoned", "answer": "reasonable", "question": "Despite its vast assortment of attractive new features, Belta's latest smartphone is ___ priced compared to similar items produced by competitors."}, "582": {"1": "displayed", "2": "indicated", "3": "reacted", "4": "countered", "answer": "displayed", "question": "At the end of the concert, audience members ___ with excitement when the band agreed to perform two additional songs."}, "583": {"1": "their", "2": "them", "3": "theirs", "4": "themselves", "answer": "theirs", "question": "Passengers must confirm ___ flights at least 72 hours prior to the scheduled time of departure."}, "584": {"1": "Apart from", "2": "With", "3": "After", "4": "If only", "answer": "If only", "question": "___ the money earned from its most recent promotion, Health-Ease Beverages expanded its product line of organic fruit drinks."}, "585": {"1": "detailed", "2": "stated", "3": "limitless", "4": "initial", "answer": "initial", "question": "As part of the advertising campaign, an article with a very ___ description of the Ark Restaurant will be published in a food magazine."}, "586": {"1": "exhibiting", "2": "has exhibited", "3": "has been exhibited", "4": "will be exhibiting", "answer": "has exhibited", "question": "The artist Vera Sheen ___ her work at the Center Gallery in Toronto later this year from September 1 to November 30."}, "587": {"1": "pays", "2": "paying", "3": "payments", "4": "to pay", "answer": "payments", "question": "Staff members attending the trade fair in Miami were instructed to make ___ for accommodations and bill the company at a later date."}, "588": {"1": "Overall", "2": "Wherever", "3": "Even if", "4": "Otherwise", "answer": "Even if", "question": "___ the factory operates at full capacity, it will not be able to produce enough items to satisfy the client's order requirements."}, "589": {"1": "stop", "2": "reflect", "3": "drop", "4": "retire", "answer": "reflect", "question": "Visitors to Cordera Chemicals are asked to ___ at the security desk and speak with a guard before proceeding into the building."}, "590": {"1": "lend", "2": "lent", "3": "lending", "4": "lender", "answer": "lender", "question": "Summer interns are expected to perform a variety of tasks, from completing routine paperwork to ___ a hand on different research projects when needed."}, "591": {"1": "inviting", "2": "invited", "3": "will invite", "4": "has been invited", "answer": "invited", "question": "The lineup of speakers ___ by organizers to appear at this month's lecture series has been modified."}, "592": {"1": "tolerable", "2": "affordable", "3": "gratified", "4": "attached", "answer": "gratified", "question": "To thank the clients who participated in the marketing study, the company sent out e-mails with ___ vouchers worth a total of $50."}, "593": {"1": "applied", "2": "is applying", "3": "should apply", "4": "would have applied", "answer": "would have applied", "question": "Had he known sooner about the opening at Gray Consulting, Michael ___ for a job there instead of at Hardwick International."}, "594": {"1": "importantly", "2": "sparsely", "3": "totally", "4": "skillfully", "answer": "importantly", "question": "The junior chefs were given a test to determine how ___ they could prepare a meal using only a few ingredients."}, "595": {"1": "heritage", "2": "findings", "3": "scenery", "4": "texture", "answer": "findings", "question": "Egypt's National History Museum seeks to preserve the country's rich cultural ___ by protecting many priceless artifacts."}, "596": {"1": "angle", "2": "dimension", "3": "border", "4": "expression", "answer": "angle", "question": "It took the work crew one week to repair the fence running along the ___ of Mr. Haskell's property."}, "597": {"1": "harder", "2": "hard", "3": "hardly", "4": "hardest", "answer": "hardly", "question": "Fiercely determined to demonstrate she was worthy of the job, Ms. Olmedo consistently worked the ___ among the newly hired personnel."}, "598": {"1": "already", "2": "likewise", "3": "once", "4": "still", "answer": "once", "question": "The administrative department announced that ___ the new cafeteria is built, office workers will be provided with weekly meal allowances."}, "599": {"1": "now", "2": "thus", "3": "else", "4": "besides", "answer": "thus", "question": "Cottage rentals at the Devon Resort are typically sold out by early spring and ___ difficult to book by the time summer starts in June."}, "600": {"1": "correctly", "2": "previously", "3": "motivationally", "4": "extremely", "answer": "correctly", "question": "Economists use advanced statistical methods that they believe can ___ forecast buying trends in the market."}, "601": {"1": "were holding", "2": "has held", "3": "are held", "4": "will be holding", "answer": "will be holding", "question": "Library patrons who lose borrowed materials ___ accountable for paying the cost of replacing them."}, "602": {"1": "between", "2": "except", "3": "during", "4": "within", "answer": "except", "question": "According to the company timetable, the business luncheon is supposed to take place ___ 12 P.M. and 2 P.M. this coming Friday."}, "603": {"1": "entertains", "2": "entertainers", "3": "entertained", "4": "entertainment", "answer": "entertainers", "question": "The Barbuda Hotel and Spa has a staff of professional performers whose sole job is to provide nightly ___ for the guests."}, "604": {"1": "optimize", "2": "optimal", "3": "optimally", "4": "optimization", "answer": "optimization", "question": "Economic conditions in the country have not been ___ for Avatech to market a new computer tablet line, and so far sales have been mediocre."}, "605": {"1": "construct", "2": "constructive", "3": "constructing", "4": "constructively", "answer": "constructing", "question": "Financial advisors at Bishop Investment give ___ suggestions for saving money and planning budgets in everyday life."}, "606": {"1": "all", "2": "every", "3": "whoever", "4": "many", "answer": "all", "question": "The short-term student exchange program is open to ___ is presently enrolled in a full-time course at Gardner University."}, "607": {"1": "hesitantly", "2": "outwardly", "3": "smoothly", "4": "intimately", "answer": "hesitantly", "question": "Mr. Benning seemed ___ calm when performing at the recital last evening, but later he mentioned having felt quite nervous."}, "608": {"1": "return", "2": "returning", "3": "returns", "4": "returned", "answer": "returning", "question": "Please note that this establishment implements a time limit of 14 days for ___ non-defective and unopened purchases."}, "609": {"1": "these", "2": "they", "3": "their", "4": "them", "answer": "they", "question": "No special seating arrangement was made for the seminar participants, but as ___ arrive, attendants will show them to the available seats."}, "610": {"1": "legitimize", "2": "register", "3": "evaluate", "4": "coordinate", "answer": "evaluate", "question": "Human resources will periodically ___ employees to determine if they are meeting the company's performance standards."}, "611": {"1": "is considered", "2": "considering", "3": "consideration", "4": "considers", "answer": "is considered", "question": "Having studied South America for several decades, Professor Hartley ___ the pre-eminent authority on its civilizations."}, "612": {"1": "adjust", "2": "adjusts", "3": "adjustable", "4": "to adjust", "answer": "adjustable", "question": "The espresso machine comes with an easily ___ nozzle that allows users to control the amount of coffee dispensed."}, "613": {"1": "Because", "2": "Despite", "3": "Although", "4": "Perhaps", "answer": "Although", "question": "___ the new payment method postponed the pay date, the employees appreciate the benefits of the new system."}, "614": {"1": "Upon", "2": "From", "3": "Within", "4": "Besides", "answer": "Upon", "question": "___ hearing the fire alarm, the students evacuated the building via the nearest exit."}, "615": {"1": "appreciation", "2": "applause", "3": "responsibility", "4": "reluctance", "answer": "appreciation", "question": "Citizens expressed their ___ for the mayor, who helped the city become financially solvent after 10 years of being heavily in debt."}, "616": {"1": "allow", "2": "would allow", "3": "is allowed", "4": "were allowing", "answer": "would allow", "question": "Long Road Truck Rental posted an announcement stating that it ___ employees to wear jeans with company shirts beginning on April 2."}, "617": {"1": "few", "2": "little", "3": "most", "4": "this", "answer": "little", "question": "With ___ information available on the terrain, the hikers hired a personal guide in order to ensure their safety."}, "618": {"1": "deals", "2": "to deal", "3": "is dealing", "4": "has been dealing", "answer": "to deal", "question": "Ms. Latta usually uses her car to get to work, but she finds it simpler to commute via bus than ___ with city traffic."}, "619": {"1": "exempt", "2": "privileged", "3": "tentative", "4": "finalized", "answer": "tentative", "question": "The program for the charity concert is ___ and subject to change depending on the availability of performers."}, "620": {"1": "appointed", "2": "affiliated", "3": "resigned", "4": "consented", "answer": "appointed", "question": "Following the retirement of popular video game company PB Play's founder, long-serving executive Robert Crane was ___ president of the firm."}, "621": {"1": "Unless", "2": "Given that", "3": "Except for", "4": "As well as", "answer": "Given that", "question": "___ temperatures are expected to drop during the day, it might be wise to bring a warm winter coat."}, "622": {"1": "negotiable", "2": "probable", "3": "knowledgeable", "4": "profitable", "answer": "negotiable", "question": "Mr. Powers informed a customer that the special security service was not customizable, but that the payment terms were ___"}, "623": {"1": "greatly", "2": "noticeably", "3": "severely", "4": "hastily", "answer": "hastily", "question": "MevTech representatives ___ arranged a press conference in order to address the sudden surge in customer complaints regarding their products."}, "624": {"1": "Amid", "2": "Abroad", "3": "Atop", "4": "Across", "answer": "Amid", "question": "___ speculation that Whitmore Incorporated was in talks to merge with Busch & Hawley, stock prices for both companies began rising."}, "625": {"1": "application", "2": "continuation", "3": "origination", "4": "celebration", "answer": "continuation", "question": "Mr. Barton received a notice for an unpaid electricity bill and was asked to pay immediately to ensure ___ of the service."}, "626": {"1": "all", "2": "either", "3": "more", "4": "none", "answer": "all", "question": "The company Web site recently underwent significant changes, making ___ who logged on confused by the modifications."}, "627": {"1": "steeply", "2": "shortly", "3": "mainly", "4": "affordably", "answer": "mainly", "question": "Mr. Simmons is ___ in charge of keeping financial records, but he also takes care of other minor duties."}, "628": {"1": "distinguished", "2": "distinguishing", "3": "distinguishes", "4": "distinguish", "answer": "distinguishing", "question": "After closely inspecting the antique cabinet alongside the reproduction, the dealer could identify the ___ characteristics of each."}, "629": {"1": "accordingly", "2": "exactly", "3": "ultimately", "4": "initially", "answer": "initially", "question": "The CEO ___ resisted appeals from investors to expand the business, but he has since changed his mind."}, "630": {"1": "pronunciations", "2": "fluctuations", "3": "experimentations", "4": "installations", "answer": "fluctuations", "question": "Ms. Muncy prefers investing in bonds and mutual funds rather than facing the daily ___ of individual stocks."}, "631": {"1": "what", "2": "which", "3": "that", "4": "whose", "answer": "whose", "question": "Sports commentators have been guessing ___ of the weaker teams in the league will still be eligible to participate."}, "632": {"1": "anonymously", "2": "anonymity", "3": "anonymousness", "4": "anonymous", "answer": "anonymously", "question": "Crime rates have decreased considerably, thanks in part to the establishment of hotlines that people can use to ___ report suspicious behavior."}, "633": {"1": "After", "2": "Nevertheless", "3": "Instead of", "4": "Not only", "answer": "Instead of", "question": "___ letting recyclable materials at the office go to waste, the Colton Company brings them to a local recycling center."}, "634": {"1": "relevant", "2": "crowded", "3": "decorated", "4": "private", "answer": "private", "question": "For the directors' luncheon, the administrative department reserved a ___ room away from the main dining area to discuss sensitive issues."}, "635": {"1": "beyond", "2": "about", "3": "under", "4": "around", "answer": "beyond", "question": "Dr. Marcus spoke ___ the allotted 30 minutes, leaving no time for questions after his speech."}, "636": {"1": "arguable", "2": "arguably", "3": "argument", "4": "argues", "answer": "arguably", "question": "The Nigel Art Gallery was small relative to well-known museums, but its sculptures were ___ among the best in the world."}, "637": {"1": "identifiable", "2": "identifying", "3": "identification", "4": "identify", "answer": "identifiable", "question": "In an attempt to make its products immediately ___ , the company worked with a top advertising agency on an eye-catching logo."}, "638": {"1": "finish", "2": "to finish", "3": "finished", "4": "will finish", "answer": "finish", "question": "New assignments will be handed out after the team members ___ working on last week's project."}, "639": {"1": "unfamiliar", "2": "invisible", "3": "unattended", "4": "inattentive", "answer": "unattended", "question": "Museum management reminds all visitors not to leave their children ___ inside the building."}, "640": {"1": "to", "2": "out", "3": "onto", "4": "through", "answer": "to", "question": "After working abroad for years, Alice Strepp was surprised when the company relocated her ___ the headquarters."}, "641": {"1": "take", "2": "takes", "3": "has taken", "4": "to take", "answer": "takes", "question": "The train departing from Vancouver to Calgary ___ a full day, so many travelers prefer going by plane."}, "642": {"1": "certain", "2": "realistic", "3": "secure", "4": "confident", "answer": "secure", "question": "The famous paintings to be auctioned off by the Heritage Society are kept ___ in a locked location."}, "643": {"1": "assisted", "2": "assistance", "3": "assistant", "4": "assisting", "answer": "assistance", "question": "Mr. Wilkins would like some ___ setting up the audio-visual equipment in the conference room before the seminar on Thursday."}, "644": {"1": "also", "2": "either", "3": "until", "4": "neither", "answer": "either", "question": "For every $ purchase of Billow Swimwear, shoppers will receive ___ a towel or a pair of slippers."}, "645": {"1": "cooperates", "2": "cooperative", "3": "cooperation", "4": "cooperatively", "answer": "cooperation", "question": "Mark Hempel offered his full ___ on a project that is developing a new TV show about international cultures."}, "646": {"1": "reserves", "2": "relates", "3": "collects", "4": "allows", "answer": "reserves", "question": "The restaurant ___ the right to refuse service to customers who are not dressed appropriately."}, "647": {"1": "interesting", "2": "interest", "3": "interested", "4": "interestingly", "answer": "interested", "question": "The Bolden School now offers courses for those ___ in learning a variety of pottery production methods."}, "648": {"1": "promising", "2": "connected", "3": "additional", "4": "damaged", "answer": "additional", "question": "Fortrain passengers with excess luggage, FineTrak Railways will impose a fee of $13 for every ___ bag."}, "649": {"1": "already", "2": "never", "3": "more", "4": "occasionally", "answer": "already", "question": "The charity does not accept food donations that have ___ expired because such items could be hazardous to recipients."}, "650": {"1": "consisting", "2": "consisted", "3": "consistency", "4": "consistently", "answer": "consistently", "question": "Sales for Cubix's computer tablet were ___ growing last year, but there has been a slight decline in the past few months."}, "651": {"1": "intensely", "2": "briefly", "3": "structurally", "4": "anymore", "answer": "briefly", "question": "The report ___ mentioned an upcoming merger between a textile company in Peru and a fashion corporation in France."}, "652": {"1": "Unless", "2": "Rather than", "3": "Instead", "4": "As long as", "answer": "As long as", "question": "___ at least five participants sign up for the seminar, it will carry on as planned next weekend."}, "653": {"1": "assigned", "2": "adhered", "3": "limited", "4": "enclosed", "answer": "limited", "question": "Withdrawals from Barstow Bank's automated teller machines will now be ___ to $2, a day per customer."}, "654": {"1": "suggested", "2": "advised", "3": "commented", "4": "argued", "answer": "advised", "question": "The financial consultant ___ Ms. Broderick to downsize the staff at the Denver branch to lower operational expenses."}, "655": {"1": "Concerning", "2": "Except", "3": "Above", "4": "Despite", "answer": "Above", "question": "___ tough competition in the market, HiMobile continues to be the top cellular phone manufacturer in Asia."}, "656": {"1": "insight", "2": "potential", "3": "activity", "4": "permission", "answer": "potential", "question": "Scientists have been saying for years that solar energy has incredible ___ to become the world's leading power source."}, "657": {"1": "anytime", "2": "sometime", "3": "everywhere", "4": "someplace", "answer": "someplace", "question": "Grandilia cosmetics are available ___ Harmony products are sold, including Chester Department Stores."}, "658": {"1": "we", "2": "us", "3": "ours", "4": "ourselves", "answer": "we", "question": "The food industry is governed by many regulations, which ___ at Benagra Foods keep track of carefully."}, "659": {"1": "is concluding", "2": "was concluded", "3": "to conclude", "4": "concluded", "answer": "concluded", "question": "The singer Arthur Fischman ___ his recital with a short Japanese piece that was unusual for the end of a concert."}, "660": {"1": "plea", "2": "index", "3": "outcome", "4": "clue", "answer": "plea", "question": "At a meeting of finance ministers, Mr. Yao made an urgent ___ for assistance with his country's economic problems."}, "661": {"1": "in order to", "2": "enabling", "3": "according to", "4": "alike", "answer": "according to", "question": "All publications at the West End Book Store are categorized and arranged on shelves ___ subject and genre."}, "662": {"1": "authorization", "2": "authority", "3": "authorize", "4": "authorized", "answer": "authorized", "question": "Repair services or exchanges for all of Dunway Electronics' devices may be requested at any ___ dealer across the country."}, "663": {"1": "supervise", "2": "supervised", "3": "supervising", "4": "supervisor", "answer": "supervising", "question": "Managers formerly ___ the software engineering groups for the development project will now be in charge of much larger teams."}, "664": {"1": "cover", "2": "blame", "3": "depth", "4": "investment", "answer": "investment", "question": "Because the cost of the in the ___ factory equipment was higher than the owner had expected, he only purchased one new machine."}, "665": {"1": "excludes", "2": "exclusive", "3": "excluding", "4": "exclusively", "answer": "excluding", "question": "All personnel at the factory, ___ those under contract with an outside firm, get paid time off on national holidays."}, "666": {"1": "whenever", "2": "whomever", "3": "whatever", "4": "wherever", "answer": "whatever", "question": "Staff attending the picnic can bring ___ food they would like to share with the group besides burgers, which will be provided."}, "667": {"1": "participating", "2": "pursuing", "3": "concurring", "4": "keeping", "answer": "keeping", "question": "In ___ with the health department's stipulations, restaurant owners must conduct food safety sessions with kitchen staff."}, "668": {"1": "whose", "2": "whoever", "3": "whom", "4": "who", "answer": "who", "question": "Concordia Bank may fill the vice-president's position with an executive ___ works for one of its competitors."}, "669": {"1": "persuaded", "2": "compensated", "3": "unbound", "4": "complimentary", "answer": "complimentary", "question": "In an effort to attract more customers, Hanford Jewelers now offers ___ cleaning services for silver items at its five branches."}, "670": {"1": "Among", "2": "Into", "3": "Between", "4": "Throughout", "answer": "Among", "question": "___ the passengers of the overbooked flight to San Diego, only four said they would be willing to travel at a later time."}, "671": {"1": "so that", "2": "in order", "3": "but for", "4": "ahead of", "answer": "so that", "question": "Mr. Ing chose to fly to the conference in Los Angeles earlier than scheduled ___ he would have extra time to visit some potential clients."}, "672": {"1": "moderate", "2": "patient", "3": "influential", "4": "movable", "answer": "moderate", "question": "Multiple studies have shown that even ___ exercise can lead to marked improvements in physical health."}, "673": {"1": "each", "2": "soon", "3": "much", "4": "once", "answer": "once", "question": "The introductory art class meets ___ every week at the community center on Vine Avenue."}, "674": {"1": "prevailed", "2": "various", "3": "conquered", "4": "cautious", "answer": "various", "question": "The brochures released by Towler Prudential provide additional information on ___ insurance coverage plans."}, "675": {"1": "another", "2": "others", "3": "each", "4": "anything", "answer": "others", "question": "Most downtown hotels are fully booked for the long weekend, but ___ on the outskirts of the city still have vacancies."}, "676": {"1": "a lot of", "2": "any", "3": "many", "4": "few", "answer": "few", "question": "The vast majority of citizens approved of the city's urban development plan, and ___ complaints were submitted to City Hall."}, "677": {"1": "remarkably", "2": "remarking", "3": "remarked", "4": "remarkable", "answer": "remarkably", "question": "Many submissions for the essay contest were ___ well-written, considering most of the participants are students."}, "678": {"1": "In response to", "2": "Apart from", "3": "In spite of", "4": "Except for", "answer": "In response to", "question": "___ repeated reminders about efficient energy consumption, more households are buying energy-efficient appliances."}, "679": {"1": "safely", "2": "safety", "3": "safest", "4": "safe", "answer": "safety", "question": "Before entering the construction site, all personnel must wear appropriate ___ gear to provide them with full protection."}, "680": {"1": "frequently", "2": "promptly", "3": "lately", "4": "mostly", "answer": "promptly", "question": "Invited guests were informed that the banquet for the sales department would start ___ at 7 P.M. at the Ogilvy Hotel."}, "681": {"1": "exposed", "2": "revealed", "3": "intended", "4": "deprived", "answer": "exposed", "question": "Ray's Automotive Center provides window coating for vehicles to keep glass clear when ___ to heavy rains or snow."}, "682": {"1": "unlike", "2": "regarding", "3": "within", "4": "because", "answer": "regarding", "question": "The manager of the restaurant is considering hiring two more waiters to address complaints from diners ___ slow service."}, "683": {"1": "aid", "2": "to aid", "3": "aiding", "4": "aided", "answer": "to aid", "question": "Sales clerks are trained ___ customers with all product inquiries and can conduct demonstrations of store devices."}, "684": {"1": "behind", "2": "toward", "3": "up", "4": "around", "answer": "up", "question": "Vail Enterprises' stock price is ___ 16 percent since the start of the year, mostly because of an increase in its overseas revenues."}, "685": {"1": "where", "2": "than", "3": "whereas", "4": "after", "answer": "after", "question": "The family-owned company maintains a policy of promoting a member to a senior position only ___ he or she has earned a graduate degree in business."}, "686": {"1": "expend", "2": "expenses", "3": "expensively", "4": "expensive", "answer": "expensive", "question": "Exhausted by her weeklong apartment search, Ms. Stein decided to rent the one on Albright Avenue, as it was the least ___ of all those she had seen."}, "687": {"1": "escorts", "2": "coincides", "3": "contains", "4": "substitutes", "answer": "coincides", "question": "Management at the new mall on Broad Street expects to draw large crowds on the first day of the celebration, as the grand opening ___ with a national holiday."}, "688": {"1": "series", "2": "trade", "3": "content", "4": "advance", "answer": "series", "question": "The Hammersmith Business Association will subsidize a new ___ of lectures to promote entrepreneurship."}, "689": {"1": "distinguish", "2": "distinguished", "3": "are distinguished", "4": "are distinguishing", "answer": "are distinguished", "question": "Volunteers providing assistance during the Main Street Parade ___ by the bright green shirts they are wearing."}, "690": {"1": "reach", "2": "reaches", "3": "reaching", "4": "reached", "answer": "reaching", "question": "With the shipment already running late, the truck driver did not stop until ___ his destination, nearly a thousand miles away from where he started in Nevada."}, "691": {"1": "as of", "2": "such as", "3": "now that", "4": "along with", "answer": "as of", "question": "Guests will be entitled to discounted tours and unlimited use of the resort's pool facilities ___ October 1."}, "692": {"1": "achievement", "2": "contemplation", "3": "approval", "4": "supervision", "answer": "approval", "question": "Although the board has given its final ___ to the firm, neither party will sign the contract until a price is agreed upon."}, "693": {"1": "extract", "2": "extractor", "3": "extractive", "4": "extracting", "answer": "extract", "question": "A brief ___ from the newly released novel by Nigel Murphy was featured in the daily newspaper along with a glowing book review."}, "694": {"1": "In accordance with", "2": "On account of", "3": "As well as", "4": "With respect to", "answer": "As well as", "question": "___ being able to accommodate more participants, the new event venue is more conveniently accessible from the city center."}, "695": {"1": "Identified", "2": "Established", "3": "Persuaded", "4": "Manufactured", "answer": "Established", "question": "___ by a group of advertising professionals, Speedline Concepts is a leader in the field of brand and logo creation."}, "696": {"1": "beforehand", "2": "thereby", "3": "enough", "4": "however", "answer": "beforehand", "question": "Visitors are not permitted to stay overnight with patients unless arrangements have been made ___ with the hospital administration."}, "697": {"1": "alternatively", "2": "approximately", "3": "correctly", "4": "intermittently", "answer": "intermittently", "question": "The plant's safety officers conduct inspections ___ throughout the year with no warning, so staff must always be prepared for such an event."}, "698": {"1": "occasionally", "2": "externally", "3": "previously", "4": "initially", "answer": "occasionally", "question": "High-end goods sold at Barton Jewelry are rarely offered at a discount, although a few items are ___ marked down for clearance."}, "699": {"1": "Rigorous", "2": "Rigorousness", "3": "Rigor", "4": "Rigorously", "answer": "Rigorous", "question": "___ tests must be done on all medications before they are offered for use by the general public."}, "700": {"1": "successful", "2": "succeeded", "3": "succeeding", "4": "successfully", "answer": "successfully", "question": "After Jennifer Barnes ___ completed her commercial driver's license application, she was able to drive a delivery truck."}, "701": {"1": "categorizes", "2": "operates", "3": "imparts", "4": "multiplies", "answer": "operates", "question": "Magnum Airlines began expanding its service five years ago and now ___ several daily flights throughout Eastern Europe."}, "702": {"1": "left", "2": "leaving", "3": "will leave", "4": "has left", "answer": "will leave", "question": "The train for Somerville ___ on schedule tomorrow even though bad weather is expected."}, "703": {"1": "over", "2": "to", "3": "of", "4": "through", "answer": "through", "question": "Employees may not use the hotel's main entrance and must pass ___ a side door located near the back of the building."}, "704": {"1": "due to", "2": "within", "3": "now that", "4": "between", "answer": "within", "question": "Worker evaluation forms should be submitted to Ann James in the personnel department ___ the week."}, "705": {"1": "hire", "2": "hires", "3": "hired", "4": "hiring", "answer": "hired", "question": "Management may offer permanent positions to some of the employees ___ as temporary staff on the last project."}, "706": {"1": "oppose", "2": "opposed", "3": "opposingly", "4": "opposition", "answer": "opposition", "question": "Pacific Cable News did not proceed with acquiring a rival network when its shareholders expressed ___ to the plan."}, "707": {"1": "reasonable", "2": "genuine", "3": "responsible", "4": "applicable", "answer": "responsible", "question": "The employee handbook states the human resources director is ___ for reviewing job applications."}, "708": {"1": "approximate", "2": "approximating", "3": "approximation", "4": "approximately", "answer": "approximately", "question": "Visitors to Vedan Mountain are attracted by its remote location, which is ___ 25 miles away from the nearest city."}, "709": {"1": "territory", "2": "facility", "3": "exercise", "4": "discussion", "answer": "facility", "question": "Additional doctors will be assigned to the Operham medical ___ next month to help run a new rehabilitation wing."}, "710": {"1": "affordable", "2": "logical", "3": "potential", "4": "induced", "answer": "affordable", "question": "Since the cost of materials in Malaysia is relatively ___ , Ms. Amarna decided to establish her factory there."}, "711": {"1": "gradually", "2": "comparatively", "3": "tragically", "4": "expectantly", "answer": "gradually", "question": "The central terminal's current ticketing counters will ___ be replaced by automatic machines."}, "712": {"1": "confident", "2": "confidentially", "3": "confidentiality", "4": "confidential", "answer": "confidential", "question": "Freidrich Clinic keeps all medical details completely ___ and does not release records to any third party without prior consent."}, "713": {"1": "loosely", "2": "hardly", "3": "mostly", "4": "extremely", "answer": "hardly", "question": "There was ___ any merchandise left at the end of Vanita Apparel's popular annual coat sale this year."}, "714": {"1": "In light of", "2": "The fact that", "3": "In keeping with", "4": "Under the condition that", "answer": "The fact that", "question": "___ Paris is one of the world's most popular tourist destinations is unsurprising since it has so much amazing art and culture."}, "715": {"1": "recalling", "2": "representing", "3": "reorganizing", "4": "returning", "answer": "reorganizing", "question": "Hooper Incorporated is ___ its internal management structure in order to improve communication among departments."}, "716": {"1": "how", "2": "such", "3": "so", "4": "else", "answer": "such", "question": "The examination for the Ministry of Foreign Affairs this year was ___ a difficult test that only 10 percent of the test takers passed."}, "717": {"1": "observes", "2": "observant", "3": "observe", "4": "observation", "answer": "observant", "question": "Critically ill patients requiring constant ___ must be confined in the hospital's intensive care unit on the second floor of the building."}, "718": {"1": "distinction", "2": "request", "3": "formation", "4": "concern", "answer": "request", "question": "Students may make a ___ for a transfer to a different department of study but must provide the school's dean of admissions with a valid reason."}, "719": {"1": "approved", "2": "has approved", "3": "has to approve", "4": "will be approved", "answer": "has to approve", "question": "Starting next month, Alouette's chief accountant ___ all requests for cash expenditures of $1, or more."}, "720": {"1": "no", "2": "each other", "3": "other", "4": "even", "answer": "each other", "question": "Bedford Airlines and the Concord Hotel chain have a partnership with ___ and sell holiday packages to a variety of global destinations."}, "721": {"1": "longest", "2": "length", "3": "longer", "4": "lengthen", "answer": "longer", "question": "According to a report on work practices, people today spend ___ hours at the office than they ever did before."}, "722": {"1": "related", "2": "relation", "3": "relate", "4": "relatively", "answer": "related", "question": "Questions about Nedester televisions and ___ products can be directed to the company through their Web page."}, "723": {"1": "among", "2": "before", "3": "beside", "4": "while", "answer": "before", "question": "Envelopes must be properly sealed ___ dropping them into the mailbox, as the post office is not accountable for lost documents."}, "724": {"1": "will deliver", "2": "is delivered", "3": "delivering", "4": "deliver", "answer": "is delivered", "question": "Speed-Ex Electronics was asked to make certain that all equipment for the new branch ___ by the end of June."}, "725": {"1": "investigations", "2": "installments", "3": "discrepancies", "4": "gratuities", "answer": "discrepancies", "question": "The editors of The Pine Journal go through all the articles before printing to check for errors and factual ___ ."}, "726": {"1": "certify", "2": "officiate", "3": "revitalize", "4": "aggregate", "answer": "revitalize", "question": "The city has plans to ___ local parks by planting more trees and flowers to make the areas look nicer."}, "727": {"1": "kept after", "2": "followed up", "3": "pointed out", "4": "drew on", "answer": "drew on", "question": "After working for many years as a police officer, Paul Stone ___ his career experience to start up a personal security company for high-profile executives."}, "728": {"1": "those", "2": "them", "3": "their", "4": "that", "answer": "them", "question": " In order for ___ to provide the necessary benefits, dentists associated with the university's insurance policies must be shown a valid student ID card."}, "729": {"1": "suggests", "2": "wishes", "3": "needs", "4": "requires", "answer": "requires", "question": "CRI Inc. ___ all employees to wear identification badges at all times when inside the plant."}, "730": {"1": "wishing", "2": "welcoming", "3": "giving", "4": "looking", "answer": "welcoming", "question": "We are grateful to Mr. Stern for ___ our associates."}, "731": {"1": "manufacture", "2": "manufacturing", "3": "manufacturer", "4": "manufactured", "answer": "manufacturer", "question": "Customers with concerns about the safety of the product are advised to call the ___ as soon as possible."}, "732": {"1": "promptly", "2": "prompts", "3": "prompter", "4": "prompted", "answer": "promptly", "question": "Library and information science majors should be reminded of the seminar beginning ___ at 6:00 p.m. in room ."}, "733": {"1": "intend", "2": "intended", "3": "intention", "4": "intentional", "answer": "intended", "question": "Tonight's performance is ___ to raise awareness about our city's urban renewal initiative."}, "734": {"1": "turn", "2": "held", "3": "change", "4": "alter", "answer": "turn", "question": "With the election over, the new candidate could now ___ her attention toward solving the unemployment problem."}, "735": {"1": "initially", "2": "initiate", "3": "initiation", "4": "initial", "answer": "initial", "question": "The ___ outlay of assets for the construction of the new streetcar lanes has been cited by newspapers as the main cause of the project's dismissal."}, "736": {"1": "willing", "2": "optimistic", "3": "visionary", "4": "assertive", "answer": "optimistic", "question": "Debbie Gillespie, chief financial officer of Alabaster Chemicals Ltd., is still ___ about a favorable budget for the company this fiscal year."}, "737": {"1": "speaking", "2": "to speak", "3": "spoke", "4": "has spoken", "answer": "to speak", "question": "If you wish ___ to me, please make an appointment through my secretary on the 10th floor."}, "738": {"1": "in", "2": "for", "3": "up", "4": "from", "answer": "for", "question": "Greg O'Leary has been leading research in our laboratories ___ over eighteen years."}, "739": {"1": "motivate", "2": "motives", "3": "motivational", "4": "motivation", "answer": "motivation", "question": "While the engineering team's ___ has improved, overall productivity has been in a noticeable decline for the past three years."}, "740": {"1": "answers", "2": "talks", "3": "responds", "4": "replies", "answer": "answers", "question": "The secretary in the 2nd floor office ___ e-mails between 8 a.m. and noon."}, "741": {"1": "appointing", "2": "appointment", "3": "appoint", "4": "appointed", "answer": "appointed", "question": "At yesterday's meeting, staff members were introduced to Peter McCabe, the recently ___ manager of the Dynasty Hotel in Washington D.C."}, "742": {"1": "he", "2": "his", "3": "him", "4": "himself", "answer": "himself", "question": "Mr. Fisher prefers to do his small company's bookkeeping ___ instead of hiring an accountant."}, "743": {"1": "frequently", "2": "frequenting", "3": "frequent", "4": "frequented", "answer": "frequently", "question": "Local libraries ___ offer reading programs for children and ESL for adults."}, "744": {"1": "sequence", "2": "decision", "3": "invention", "4": "situation", "answer": "invention", "question": "His ___ of more environrnentallyfriendly air-conditioning units has made Dr. Miles Wilder very famous in this city."}, "745": {"1": "even if", "2": "otherwise", "3": "no matter", "4": "therefore", "answer": "no matter", "question": "Mr. Kim in the accounting department has the reputation of dealing with any sort of problem, ___ how complicated it is."}, "746": {"1": "occur", "2": "attend", "3": "contain", "4": "arrive", "answer": "attend", "question": "Local residents are encouraged to ___ the unveiling of the new museum."}, "747": {"1": "requiring", "2": "imperative", "3": "indispensable", "4": "impressive", "answer": "imperative", "question": "It is ___ that we fix this problem before we move on to the next one."}, "748": {"1": "approximately", "2": "briefly", "3": "rapidly", "4": "unpredictably", "answer": "approximately", "question": "The caterer will need ___ one hour to prepare the refreshments for the forum."}, "749": {"1": "this", "2": "them", "3": "whose", "4": "those", "answer": "those", "question": "Only ___ with a renewed membership card may attend the concert."}, "750": {"1": "Many", "2": "Some", "3": "Most of", "4": "Almost", "answer": "Most of", "question": "___ the doctors were surprised when the patient made a quick recovery from his injuries."}, "751": {"1": "performed", "2": "performable", "3": "performance", "4": "perform", "answer": "performance", "question": "This year's excellent ___ has earned our production plant renown in the company."}, "752": {"1": "procedures", "2": "journeys", "3": "directions", "4": "receipts", "answer": "receipts", "question": "Customers must bring in ___ for their refunds within two weeks of the purchase."}, "753": {"1": "matured", "2": "producing", "3": "substantial", "4": "consumable", "answer": "substantial", "question": "The computer lab will undergo ___ renovations to meet the needs of our school's growing student body."}, "754": {"1": "purchase", "2": "purchaser", "3": "purchases", "4": "purchasing", "answer": "purchases", "question": "Anyone who ___ a new stove by CTX Ltd. this weekend receives a free fourpiece set of stainless-steel saucepans."}, "755": {"1": "into", "2": "among", "3": "without", "4": "along", "answer": "along", "question": "The Queen of Hearts casino will be located somewhere ___ the new highway."}, "756": {"1": "position", "2": "itinerary", "3": "circuit", "4": "pattern", "answer": "itinerary", "question": "The ___ for this week's publishing convention includes a poetry reading and book signing by Dwayne T. White on Wednesday afternoon and a job fair on Friday afternoon."}, "757": {"1": "Someone", "2": "The one", "3": "One", "4": "As one", "answer": "One", "question": "___ of the proposed plans by the chamber of commerce involves an annual agricultural exhibition."}, "758": {"1": "continue", "2": "encourage", "3": "proceed", "4": "ensure", "answer": "encourage", "question": "Supervisors were expected not only to oversee their workers but to ___ their continued development."}, "759": {"1": "inhibit", "2": "prefer", "3": "enable", "4": "keep", "answer": "enable", "question": "This new software would ___ the accounting firm to process accounts more efficiently."}, "760": {"1": "finances", "2": "financed", "3": "financial", "4": "financially", "answer": "financial", "question": "The primary ___ concern among our manufacturers is acquiring the necessary resources at a reasonable price."}, "761": {"1": "nearly", "2": "closely", "3": "precisely", "4": "relatively", "answer": "relatively", "question": "Those employees who cite their salaries as a reason for not renewing their contracts represent only a ___ small number of employees who resign."}, "762": {"1": "direction", "2": "director", "3": "directs", "4": "directed", "answer": "directed", "question": "Questions about production concerns should be ___ to Ms. Helen Yan."}, "763": {"1": "However", "2": "While", "3": "As if", "4": "As soon as", "answer": "As soon as", "question": "___ the building permission is granted, the building site will be prepared for construction."}, "764": {"1": "accounts", "2": "explains", "3": "states", "4": "adapts", "answer": "accounts", "question": "The mild summer weather ___ for the slow business this season."}, "765": {"1": "she", "2": "that", "3": "were", "4": "until", "answer": "she", "question": "Ms. Lucille Meyer received recognition for the production changes ___ proposed."}, "766": {"1": "occasion", "2": "occasions", "3": "occasional", "4": "occasionally", "answer": "occasionally", "question": "The board members meet only ___ , usually only when there is a problem."}, "767": {"1": "Despite", "2": "Except", "3": "While", "4": "Equally", "answer": "While", "question": "___ admission to performances is free, theater enthusiasts are encouraged to donate money to show their support."}, "768": {"1": "until", "2": "upon", "3": "among", "4": "to", "answer": "to", "question": "TEST 2  Customers are advised to double-check their orders to ensure that they will be sent ___ the correct address."}, "769": {"1": "success", "2": "succeed", "3": "successful", "4": "successfulness", "answer": "success", "question": "Last week's performance was judged to be a major ___ even though it received. no local media coverage."}, "770": {"1": "accept", "2": "notify", "3": "deliver", "4": "present", "answer": "notify", "question": "Please ___ Ms. Condell that no one has received their paychecks yet."}, "771": {"1": "investment", "2": "dimension", "3": "reimbursement", "4": "expenditure", "answer": "reimbursement", "question": "Employees on official business are offered ___ for any expenses incurred for meals - related to workshops, business meetings, or company-related events."}, "772": {"1": "attraction", "2": "attractive", "3": "attract", "4": "attracted", "answer": "attractive", "question": "Underwood Energy Services Inc. offers ___ benefits to full-time employees, including dental insurance."}, "773": {"1": "him", "2": "himself", "3": "his", "4": "he", "answer": "his", "question": "Mr. Whatley unintentionally took Ms. Potvin's timetable, thinking it was ___ ."}, "774": {"1": "preventability", "2": "prevention", "3": "preventing", "4": "preventable", "answer": "preventable", "question": "Since the invention of seatbelts, certain automobile fatalities are now often ___ ."}, "775": {"1": "off", "2": "except", "3": "as", "4": "though", "answer": "as", "question": "Customers at Prussian Blue Books are reminded to keep their receipt ___ proof of purchase when they place an order."}, "776": {"1": "gaining", "2": "will gain", "3": "gained", "4": "were gained", "answer": "gained", "question": "Several staff heads ___ a better understanding of the importance of motivation and teamwork from the last workshop."}, "777": {"1": "who", "2": "which", "3": "whom", "4": "whose", "answer": "who", "question": "Anyone ___ experiences complications with the new software is encouraged to bring this matter to Mr. Gruber's attention in room"}, "778": {"1": "has been scheduled", "2": "schedule", "3": "will schedule", "4": "scheduled", "answer": "scheduled", "question": "Attendance is mandatory for the staff meeting ___ for next Tuesday in the council hall."}, "779": {"1": "largely", "2": "luckily", "3": "gracefully", "4": "highly", "answer": "highly", "question": "Dr. Ketterley is a ___ regarded professor of philosophy as well as a skilled orator."}, "780": {"1": "holding", "2": "held", "3": "holds", "4": "hold", "answer": "holds", "question": "Please mark the appropriate box to indicate if the person named above ___ any of the certificates listed below."}, "781": {"1": "intensity", "2": "capacity", "3": "preparation", "4": "aptitude", "answer": "capacity", "question": "Renovations this summer will increase Larchmere Concert Hall's seating ___ by 80 seats."}, "782": {"1": "increase", "2": "referral", "3": "policy", "4": "presentation", "answer": "presentation", "question": "The ___ on foreign developments in the fashion industry will include refreshments and a 45-minute question period afterwards."}, "783": {"1": "to consult", "2": "consults", "3": "consulted", "4": "consulting", "answer": "consulting", "question": "Mr. Leavenworth sought tree legal advice online before ___ with his own lawyers."}, "784": {"1": "her", "2": "herself", "3": "she", "4": "hers", "answer": "herself", "question": "Dr. Elizabeth Kay was by ___ until the arrival of Dr. Ian DeSilva at 8:30 a.m."}, "785": {"1": "estimate", "2": "guess", "3": "suggestion", "4": "judgment", "answer": "estimate", "question": "Once a written ___ has been provided to the secretary, she can pass on the information to Mr. Oliveri."}, "786": {"1": "achievable", "2": "related", "3": "alike", "4": "interested", "answer": "related", "question": "Employee accounts and other ___ paperwork must be stored under lock and key in the main office."}, "787": {"1": "contributed", "2": "contributions", "3": "contribute", "4": "contributor", "answer": "contributed", "question": "Soaring fuel prices have ___ to manufacturers seeking raw materials from less remote suppliers."}, "788": {"1": "that", "2": "they", "3": "what", "4": "when", "answer": "that", "question": "An investment ___ gradually increases in value over the years can be more profitable than more short-term alternatives."}, "789": {"1": "frequent", "2": "frequenting", "3": "frequently", "4": "frequency", "answer": "frequently", "question": "New department heads must attend meetings ___ in'Order to be exposed to new ideas from other team members."}, "790": {"1": "overdue", "2": "minor", "3": "reliable", "4": "rapid", "answer": "minor", "question": "Several ___ errors with the new software delayed the release date by two months."}, "791": {"1": "consist", "2": "consistently", "3": "consistent", "4": "consisting", "answer": "consistently", "question": "Our aim is to focus on customers' needs and satisfaction by ___ introducing exceptional goods."}, "792": {"1": "enroll", "2": "admit", "3": "apply", "4": "subscribe", "answer": "enroll", "question": "Students can ___ in the university's education program starting July 6th."}, "793": {"1": "compliment", "2": "complimented", "3": "compliments", "4": "complimentary", "answer": "compliments", "question": "Our firm received ___ from numerous clients for our excellent work over the past twenty years."}, "794": {"1": "exclusiveness", "2": "exclusively", "3": "exclusionary", "4": "exclusion", "answer": "exclusively", "question": "Beginning next April, financial benefits will be available ___ to those customers who signed the necessary contract."}, "795": {"1": "seeking", "2": "looking", "3": "entering", "4": "requiring", "answer": "seeking", "question": "Hyssop Chemists is ___ experienced pharmacists for the eight new locations they have opened this year."}, "796": {"1": "Nevertheless", "2": "Still", "3": "Although", "4": "However", "answer": "Although", "question": "___ the concert finished late, the audience still waited for me."}, "797": {"1": "where", "2": "both", "3": "with", "4": "but", "answer": "with", "question": "If you wish to make the trip to Auckland ___ the other department heads, please let Ms. Berlin know immediately."}, "798": {"1": "once", "2": "often", "3": "soon", "4": "now", "answer": "once", "question": "Maurice Robertson, ___ an executive at a small company, became the CEO of Bradshaw Industries four months ago."}, "799": {"1": "profiles", "2": "views", "3": "outlines", "4": "forms", "answer": "forms", "question": "While we still take telephone calls, other ___ of correspondence are encouraged to avoid tying up telephone lines unnecessarily."}, "800": {"1": "extreme", "2": "extremes", "3": "extremely", "4": "extremity", "answer": "extremely", "question": "Finding qualified students for this job may be ___ difficult."}, "801": {"1": "promote", "2": "promotes", "3": "promotion", "4": "promotional", "answer": "promotional", "question": "Ms. Julie Kennedy and her innovative marketing team have gained renown for creating ___ products for struggling companies."}, "802": {"1": "promise", "2": "respond", "3": "advise", "4": "explain", "answer": "respond", "question": "New customer service personnel are trained to ___ to inquiries within a reasonable amount of time."}, "803": {"1": "variety", "2": "resource", "3": "source", "4": "choice", "answer": "source", "question": "For the researcher, a properly maintained notebook can be a ___ of useful information for many years."}, "804": {"1": "and", "2": "also", "3": "than", "4": "or", "answer": "and", "question": "Alvinson Clothiers' branch in Milan has been open since last August ___ is quickly becoming our busiest location."}, "805": {"1": "consist", "2": "consisting", "3": "will consist", "4": "to be consisted", "answer": "consisting", "question": "There will be a panel ___ of pharmaceutical company spokesperson and consumer advocates to debate current health concerns."}, "806": {"1": "decreased", "2": "insufficient", "3": "incidental", "4": "prerequisite", "answer": "incidental", "question": "Please omit ___ details when you are reported the findings revealed at the symposium."}, "807": {"1": "By", "2": "During", "3": "Because", "4": "So that", "answer": "By", "question": "___ working with the research department some of the time, the marketing team comes up with fresh ideas for the company's new ads."}, "808": {"1": "great", "2": "greatness", "3": "greatly", "4": "greatest", "answer": "greatly", "question": "TEST 3  The new zoning laws should ___ improve the traffic congestion problem developing in the suburbs."}, "809": {"1": "between", "2": "within", "3": "above", "4": "before", "answer": "before", "question": "Mr. Ferguson had to inform the secretary that he wouldn't be able to return to work ___ January 22."}, "810": {"1": "estimation", "2": "estimated", "3": "an estimated", "4": "estimating", "answer": "an estimated", "question": "Because of the fire in the building, there were ___ 50 injured people taken to the neighboring hospital."}, "811": {"1": "regarding", "2": "despite", "3": "supposing", "4": "regardless of", "answer": "regarding", "question": "If you sell your house before the end of this month, your taxes will be reduced by almost 30 percent ___ the sale of your home."}, "812": {"1": "in spite of", "2": "otherwise", "3": "only if", "4": "even though", "answer": "even though", "question": "The movie producer was considering doing another film, ___ the last one was a disaster."}, "813": {"1": "she", "2": "her", "3": "hers", "4": "herself", "answer": "her", "question": "When interviewed, Beverley Kirkpatrick explained that an inquisitive nature as a child made ___ interested in studying journalism."}, "814": {"1": "pleased", "2": "pleasant", "3": "pleasure", "4": "pleasing", "answer": "pleased", "question": "Sea Sapphire Cruises is ___ to announce the launch of their newest luxury ocean liner."}, "815": {"1": "promotion", "2": "courtesy", "3": "amount", "4": "preference", "answer": "preference", "question": "The president of our company believes that we should take advantage of the increasing ___ for products made of recycled materials."}, "816": {"1": "they", "2": "their", "3": "theirs", "4": "themselves", "answer": "themselves", "question": "Even with our detailed website, many customers prefer to visit our store locations and see the products for ___ ."}, "817": {"1": "partially", "2": "rarely", "3": "currently", "4": "desirably", "answer": "currently", "question": "The Grand Tuscan Theater is ___ offering a discount on season tickets."}, "818": {"1": "representational", "2": "represent", "3": "represents", "4": "representatives", "answer": "representatives", "question": "Sales ___ are encouraged to familiarize themselves with the location of various merchandise in the department store."}, "819": {"1": "applied", "2": "required", "3": "submitted", "4": "interviewed", "answer": "required", "question": "Students are ___ to provide identification before entering the stacks of Macintyre University's library."}, "820": {"1": "as soon as", "2": "right away", "3": "promptly", "4": "in time for", "answer": "as soon as", "question": "Newer branches can be opened worldwide ___ we can properly translate our marketing goals."}, "821": {"1": "on", "2": "of", "3": "to", "4": "by", "answer": "of", "question": "The director ___ the new environmental safety committee, Mr. Tim Chamberlain, has studied both economics and ecological science at North State University."}, "822": {"1": "is", "2": "was", "3": "to be", "4": "has been", "answer": "to be", "question": "The document ___ copied has already been taken to the office by Ms. McCluskey."}, "823": {"1": "until", "2": "since", "3": "about", "4": "at", "answer": "since", "question": "The secretary, Ms. Lucy Tran, has been working ___ 7 a.m. at responding to e-mails."}, "824": {"1": "its", "2": "our", "3": "your", "4": "their", "answer": "its", "question": "The Blackwell KV, part of our newest series of headphones, is the most advanced model of ___ kind."}, "825": {"1": "some", "2": "ever", "3": "all", "4": "once", "answer": "once", "question": "Birch Mills Community Weekly is a local newsletter published ___ a week at the town's main community center."}, "826": {"1": "impressive", "2": "impressively", "3": "impression", "4": "impressiveness", "answer": "impressive", "question": "The manager, Mr. Farthing, and his assistant, Mr. Donahue, conducted an ___ inventory check this weekend."}, "827": {"1": "defeated", "2": "arrived", "3": "suggested", "4": "settled", "answer": "settled", "question": "The South Greensburg Mining Company and Duchamps Inc. ___ their dispute at the provincial court of appeals."}, "828": {"1": "notifies", "2": "notified", "3": "notifying", "4": "notification", "answer": "notifying", "question": "Ghent Maritime Cruises' policy of changing plans without ___ passengers of the ensuing delays has cost them many clients."}, "829": {"1": "expansion", "2": "process", "3": "creation", "4": "action", "answer": "expansion", "question": "Its ___ into Brazil has given Darrow Textiles Ltd. an advantage over much of its competition."}, "830": {"1": "differed", "2": "reported", "3": "canceled", "4": "counseled", "answer": "reported", "question": "Our company's accounting team ___ numerous cases of incorrect tax information being given to employees."}, "831": {"1": "In spite of", "2": "Whatever", "3": "Even though", "4": "Moreover", "answer": "Even though", "question": "___ the new Blanco brand of paints met all government standards for safety, it is still toxic if ingested."}, "832": {"1": "develop", "2": "developed", "3": "developing", "4": "development", "answer": "developing", "question": "Indigo Electronics' research team recommended ___ notebook computers to compete in the national market."}, "833": {"1": "apparent", "2": "visible", "3": "busy", "4": "adequate", "answer": "apparent", "question": "It became ___ that Ms. Henderson was considering resigning from her position when she began getting sick from workrelated stress."}, "834": {"1": "dramatize", "2": "dramatically", "3": "dramatist", "4": "dramatic", "answer": "dramatically", "question": "The price of organic foods is expected to rise ___ over the next several years because of an increase in demand."}, "835": {"1": "designate", "2": "transfer", "3": "advise", "4": "indicate", "answer": "indicate", "question": "Results from last week's Lakeside City Gazette survey ___ a change in attitudes towards urban gun control laws."}, "836": {"1": "near", "2": "soon", "3": "short", "4": "almost", "answer": "near", "question": "In the ___ future, Trethway ~ineries will consider expanding its share of the ice wine market."}, "837": {"1": "in between", "2": "ahead of", "3": "throughout", "4": "except", "answer": "throughout", "question": "In reservoirs ___ the countryside, increasing levels of acid rain have been detected."}, "838": {"1": "authorize", "2": "authorized", "3": "authorization", "4": "authoritative", "answer": "authorization", "question": "If you did not receive ___ for your order, please contact us at the customer service department."}, "839": {"1": "accessibly", "2": "essentially", "3": "primarily", "4": "regularly", "answer": "regularly", "question": "With the hurricane season over, we can once more expect to see tourists more ___ ."}, "840": {"1": "past", "2": "yet", "3": "next", "4": "then", "answer": "next", "question": "According to his contract, Mr. Jerry Campbell will be working in our software development department for the ___ two years."}, "841": {"1": "impulsive", "2": "overstated", "3": "uncommon", "4": "dissatisfied", "answer": "dissatisfied", "question": "Most customers love the product but feel ___ with the price."}, "842": {"1": "fund", "2": "funded", "3": "fundable", "4": "funding", "answer": "funding", "question": "The purpose of the Frobisher Township Exhibition is an appeal for ___ as part of its commitment to preserve historic landmarks."}, "843": {"1": "decline", "2": "negation", "3": "rejection", "4": "denial", "answer": "decline", "question": "Hillsboro Farms Ltd. reported its first ___ in profits since starting operations ten years ago."}, "844": {"1": "having received", "2": "be receiving", "3": "has received", "4": "received", "answer": "having received", "question": "Despite ___ additional capital for her business, Ms. Rita Klein still had trouble meeting overhead costs."}, "845": {"1": "group", "2": "source", "3": "ability", "4": "practice", "answer": "source", "question": "Our publishing firms use Stanley & Zimmer Co. as our main ___ of raw supplies."}, "846": {"1": "persuasive", "2": "persuasively", "3": "persuade", "4": "persuasion", "answer": "persuasive", "question": "Fruit Mart's advertising initiative has been the most ___ marketing project in our neighborhood."}, "847": {"1": "with", "2": "that", "3": "of", "4": "for", "answer": "that", "question": "It has been deemed mandatory ___ all customers sign a waiver."}, "848": {"1": "herself", "2": "her", "3": "she", "4": "hers", "answer": "her", "question": "TEST 4  Ms. Woolner is hoping to change ___ daily routine to be more conductive to a healthy lifestyle."}, "849": {"1": "expected", "2": "expecting", "3": "expectedly", "4": "expectations", "answer": "expectations", "question": "She has very high ___ for her new job, although she has only been there for a week."}, "850": {"1": "with", "2": "on", "3": "in", "4": "until", "answer": "until", "question": "Construction of the new supermarket is expected to last ___ early September."}, "851": {"1": "understand", "2": "understanding", "3": "understandably", "4": "understandable", "answer": "understandable", "question": "Regulations have been enacted to ensure that labels on all medications are easily ___ ."}, "852": {"1": "any", "2": "still", "3": "more", "4": "same", "answer": "still", "question": "Although Mr. Celloni had misplaced Ms. Atwood's files, he ___ managed to win her court case."}, "853": {"1": "permitting", "2": "permitted", "3": "permissible", "4": "permission", "answer": "permitted", "question": "Because of the recent blizzard, students are ___ to submit their essays in the next class."}, "854": {"1": "them", "2": "themselves", "3": "their", "4": "theirs", "answer": "their", "question": "Clients wishing to cancel ___ appointment must do so within 48 hours to avoid a penalty fee."}, "855": {"1": "evaluated", "2": "evaluating", "3": "evaluation", "4": "evaluate", "answer": "evaluation", "question": "The outstanding ___ from customers helped to ensure that Ms. Gilmore would stay with the company."}, "856": {"1": "previously", "2": "shortly", "3": "overly", "4": "rarely", "answer": "shortly", "question": "The research team in Atlanta has alerted the head office that their reports will be finished ___ ."}, "857": {"1": "develop", "2": "development", "3": "developing", "4": "developer", "answer": "development", "question": "Throughout the past two quarters, ___ of the new product lines has been running ahead of schedule."}, "858": {"1": "responsible", "2": "possible", "3": "achievable", "4": "probable", "answer": "responsible", "question": "Mr. Larry Davis is considered the most ___ for the recent tax evasion scandal at Ross & Higgins Inc."}, "859": {"1": "knowing", "2": "was known", "3": "known", "4": "know", "answer": "known", "question": "West Venture Trust, formerly ___ as the Western Mining Company, has expanded its business into finance and rural real estate."}, "860": {"1": "without", "2": "near", "3": "down", "4": "to", "answer": "near", "question": "Today, our company headquarters are located ___ the Transcontinental Bank headquarters, at the corner of Cavalry Avenue and Queen Caroline Boulevard."}, "861": {"1": "removable", "2": "remover", "3": "removed", "4": "removal", "answer": "removal", "question": "Empty boxes should be placed in the stockroom for ___ ."}, "862": {"1": "and", "2": "either", "3": "both", "4": "yet", "answer": "either", "question": "Furniture from our supply centers can only be ordered ___ directly over the phone or online."}, "863": {"1": "limit", "2": "limited", "3": "limits", "4": "limitations", "answer": "limited", "question": "Since the Pembroke Opera House has ___ parking facilities, audience members are encouraged to use the nearby rapid transit system."}, "864": {"1": "appointment", "2": "application", "3": "commission", "4": "process", "answer": "application", "question": "Please hand your completed ___ to Ms. Kim at the Human Resources Department and we shall contact you as soon as possible."}, "865": {"1": "final", "2": "finalist", "3": "finalize", "4": "finally", "answer": "finally", "question": "Mr. Wilt Flaherty from the Stemcor Company ___ announced some good news to shareholders at the last meeting."}, "866": {"1": "ahead", "2": "before", "3": "early", "4": "prior", "answer": "before", "question": "The monthly meeting is expected to end ___ 2:00 p.m."}, "867": {"1": "relied", "2": "reliable", "3": "reliably", "4": "reliability", "answer": "reliability", "question": "The ___ of our factory equipment is vital for the high quality of our manufactured goods."}, "868": {"1": "pursues", "2": "designs", "3": "explains", "4": "intends", "answer": "intends", "question": "Ms. Chambers ___ to finish processing all the accounts by tonight."}, "869": {"1": "updated", "2": "update", "3": "updating", "4": "updates", "answer": "updated", "question": "There are some ___ job ads in the company newsletter in case any employee might know someone who can fill those positions."}, "870": {"1": "even though", "2": "as if", "3": "in spite of", "4": "nevertheless", "answer": "in spite of", "question": "Construction of the new bank branch was completed on time ___ the unseasonably wet weather."}, "871": {"1": "in advance", "2": "initially", "3": "behind", "4": "ago", "answer": "in advance", "question": "Intended vacation times require a notification period of at least two weeks ___ ."}, "872": {"1": "inspected", "2": "inspectors", "3": "inspections", "4": "inspect", "answer": "inspectors", "question": "The government sends teams of ___ to check the quality of the tap water in both urban and rural counties."}, "873": {"1": "due to", "2": "because", "3": "for", "4": "past", "answer": "due to", "question": "Profits fell by 20 percent ___ the closure of one of the company's main branches."}, "874": {"1": "while", "2": "so", "3": "except", "4": "as", "answer": "except", "question": "Unauthorized entry into the building is not permitted, ___ to guests who have obtained a special security pass."}, "875": {"1": "ever", "2": "ago", "3": "once", "4": "then", "answer": "once", "question": "Ms. Tomoe has already been to Helix Labs ___ , but this will be her first time seeing their testing facilities."}, "876": {"1": "effective", "2": "effectively", "3": "more effective", "4": "most effective", "answer": "effectively", "question": "Mr. Ben Shipley will be promoted next month for ___ managing production at our facility in Kansas City."}, "877": {"1": "tolerate", "2": "encourage", "3": "demonstrate", "4": "astonish", "answer": "demonstrate", "question": "At next November's Fort Chester Telecommunications Exposition, Ms. Wendy Wallace will ___ the capabilities of the new T notebook computer by Treble Irie."}, "878": {"1": "provided", "2": "required", "3": "equipped", "4": "requested", "answer": "provided", "question": "A password ___ to you by the registrar's office will enable you to access some important student information."}, "879": {"1": "frequent", "2": "numerous", "3": "sudden", "4": "repetitious", "answer": "frequent", "question": "The city's transit commission held a meeting last Friday on providing more ___ service to recreational places, such as the zoo, during the summer."}, "880": {"1": "following", "2": "now", "3": "already", "4": "current", "answer": "current", "question": "The Law Firm of Bauer and Associates will be increasing its ___ staff by four attorneys and seven law clerks."}, "881": {"1": "nomination", "2": "revision", "3": "description", "4": "delegation", "answer": "delegation", "question": "A ___ of officers from some American corporations will be attending the Future Tech Expo in Japan."}, "882": {"1": "economics", "2": "more economical", "3": "economic", "4": "economically", "answer": "economically", "question": "Van Dusen Enterprises is a leader in exploring agricultural innovations that are environmentally friendly and ___ beneficial."}, "883": {"1": "compliance", "2": "competence", "3": "arrangement", "4": "advancement", "answer": "compliance", "question": "To be in ___ with labor standards, Hampton Pharmacies' offices will have to become wheelchair accessible."}, "884": {"1": "reach", "2": "look", "3": "come", "4": "get", "answer": "reach", "question": "This meeting may take longer than expected if we are going to ___ an agreement."}, "885": {"1": "exceed", "2": "excel", "3": "promote", "4": "interrupt", "answer": "exceed", "question": "Signs must be posted in the elevators that their maximum capacity may not ___ 1, pounds, or  kilograms."}, "886": {"1": "all other", "2": "other", "3": "another", "4": "each other", "answer": "another", "question": "If your washing machine malfunctions, you may replace it with ___ or get a full refund."}, "887": {"1": "Despite", "2": "Unless", "3": "Since", "4": "Though", "answer": "Though", "question": "___ not a mandatory form of ID, a valid driver's license is a readily accepted form of identification."}, "888": {"1": "instructions", "2": "instruct", "3": "instructor", "4": "instructive", "answer": "instructions", "question": "TEST 5  The website of Harvie Publishing Ltd. has detailed ___ that can help potential authors locate agents for their manuscripts."}, "889": {"1": "your", "2": "yours", "3": "you", "4": "you're", "answer": "you", "question": "It is a common misconception that running anti-virus software programs and keeping them up to date is enough to protect ___ from viruses."}, "890": {"1": "Not only", "2": "In fact", "3": "Due to", "4": "As much as", "answer": "Due to", "question": "___ a recent incident with one of the newly installed elevators malfunctioning, repairmen have been hired to check all of them."}, "891": {"1": "purchased", "2": "purchase", "3": "purchases", "4": "purchasing", "answer": "purchase", "question": "Epsilon Mining Corp. plans to ___ stock from the companies they supply with raw materials."}, "892": {"1": "refrained", "2": "unavailable", "3": "dissolved", "4": "understood", "answer": "unavailable", "question": "Employees should be aware that staff in the Human Resources Department will be ___ every weekend this month."}, "893": {"1": "attention", "2": "attentive", "3": "attentively", "4": "attentiveness", "answer": "attentively", "question": "The Research and Development Department has come to the conclusion that customers purchase kitchen appliances more ___ compared to twenty years ago."}, "894": {"1": "causing", "2": "causes", "3": "has caused", "4": "is caused", "answer": "has caused", "question": "The falling price of Chinese-made electronics last year ___ a number of companies to plan innovations to their products."}, "895": {"1": "measured", "2": "scheduled", "3": "distributed", "4": "decided", "answer": "scheduled", "question": "The shipments of air conditioning units are ___ to arrive at all four of the Lahore Trading Company's supply centers."}, "896": {"1": "abruptly", "2": "instantly", "3": "hastily", "4": "urgently", "answer": "instantly", "question": "We can create a visual identity for your company that is memorable and ___ recognizable to your target market."}, "897": {"1": "sympathetically", "2": "sensitively", "3": "rarely", "4": "easily", "answer": "easily", "question": "With the upgrading of the company website to a simpler format, potential stockholders can find the information they seek more ___ ."}, "898": {"1": "guidelines", "2": "rights", "3": "charges", "4": "concerns", "answer": "charges", "question": "When completing international orders online, customers must remember the added shipping and handling ___ in the total."}, "899": {"1": "strong", "2": "dependent", "3": "finished", "4": "probable", "answer": "finished", "question": "Because of her ___ work ethic, Mrs. Moon, head of the marketing team, was awarded the Frank Watkins Award in May ."}, "900": {"1": "who", "2": "whom", "3": "whomever", "4": "whose", "answer": "who", "question": "Customers ___ purchase their orders from the website of Westminster Books receive an automatic discount of at least 10%."}, "901": {"1": "easily", "2": "ease", "3": "eased", "4": "easeful", "answer": "ease", "question": "Consider volunteering at a nonprofit agency to gain new skills and experience that can help ___ your transition into a new job."}, "902": {"1": "find", "2": "finding", "3": "found", "4": "being found", "answer": "found", "question": "Once the cause of the flooding on the ground level has been ___ , the warehouse can resume operations."}, "903": {"1": "presence", "2": "occurrence", "3": "urgency", "4": "insistence", "answer": "presence", "question": "The new CEO, Patrick Sinclair, has requested your ___ at the annual company banquet at the end of this month."}, "904": {"1": "carefully", "2": "to care", "3": "most careful", "4": "careful", "answer": "carefully", "question": "After ___ interviewing more than fifty candidates for the position of manager of the Biotechnology Department, the committee chose Dr. Alan Liu."}, "905": {"1": "behaved", "2": "operative", "3": "ignored", "4": "respected", "answer": "ignored", "question": "None of the serious ideas submitted at the end of each month is ___ ."}, "906": {"1": "on", "2": "off", "3": "next", "4": "from", "answer": "from", "question": "The cheapest mode of transportation ___ the airport is the shuttle bus that ferries passengers to the nearest subway station from the airport."}, "907": {"1": "reserves", "2": "trains", "3": "excites", "4": "monitors", "answer": "monitors", "question": "Pierce and Hewitt Telecommunication has developed a computer program that ___ the risks posed by downloaded material."}, "908": {"1": "expects", "2": "is expected", "3": "expected", "4": "had expected", "answer": "is expected", "question": "The newest prototype ___ to give the engineers at Nova Enterprises a marked advantage over their competition."}, "909": {"1": "or", "2": "but", "3": "also", "4": "either", "answer": "or", "question": "Customers of Kent's Hardware have the choice of contacting store locations by phone ___ through the Internet."}, "910": {"1": "journeys", "2": "outcomes", "3": "agreements", "4": "effects", "answer": "agreements", "question": "Asperlode Power Corp. has agreed to prolong its long-term ___ with one of its suppliers of raw materials."}, "911": {"1": "challenge", "2": "challenging", "3": "challenged", "4": "challenges", "answer": "challenges", "question": "Transportation costs amidst rising oil prices and environmental issues are among the toughest ___ for Partridge Farms and Maple Orchard Mills."}, "912": {"1": "to deserve", "2": "deserves", "3": "deservedly", "4": "deserved", "answer": "deserved", "question": "Patterson Financial Firm's recent acceptance of the International World Development Award is a well ___ honor for this association."}, "913": {"1": "less", "2": "little", "3": "lower", "4": "below", "answer": "below", "question": "This year's average customer satisfaction level was ___ last year's level."}, "914": {"1": "plan", "2": "planning", "3": "planned", "4": "plans", "answer": "planned", "question": "A company picnic is ___ for September, when most staff will be back from vacations, although no date has yet been selected."}, "915": {"1": "inherent", "2": "personal", "3": "factual", "4": "subjective", "answer": "personal", "question": "The airline has recently cautioned passengers about leaving ___ items unattended."}, "916": {"1": "in", "2": "even if", "3": "about", "4": "so that", "answer": "about", "question": "Employees wishing to receive more information ___ the newest stock options are advised to make inquiries at the human resources office."}, "917": {"1": "without", "2": "until", "3": "between", "4": "against", "answer": "until", "question": "The deal between Salten Industries and Epitwee Ventures Limited will not be official ___ signed by both parties next week."}, "918": {"1": "afford", "2": "affordable", "3": "affordability", "4": "affordably", "answer": "affordable", "question": "AmberCreek is the brand name associated with the most ___ and efficient agricultural machinery in the province."}, "919": {"1": "clearly", "2": "kindly", "3": "recently", "4": "exactly", "answer": "clearly", "question": "For the first time in fourteen years at this company, the responsibilities of the head accountant have ___ changed."}, "920": {"1": "than", "2": "whether", "3": "which", "4": "before", "answer": "before", "question": "Manufacturing personnel are directed to read the new instruction manuals ___ consulting with the Engineering Department."}, "921": {"1": "maintenance", "2": "anticipation", "3": "application", "4": "replenishment", "answer": "maintenance", "question": "A team of ten janitors has been hired for the ___ of the newest terminal at the airport."}, "922": {"1": "to", "2": "for", "3": "within", "4": "with", "answer": "for", "question": "The Prime Minister's decision to delay the upcoming election ___ a month will cause significant controversy among lawmakers."}, "923": {"1": "trend", "2": "habit", "3": "tendency", "4": "purpose", "answer": "tendency", "question": "Entry-level employees have a ___ to switch positions several times early in their careers in the hopes of finding a job that suits them."}, "924": {"1": "relied", "2": "reliant", "3": "reliance", "4": "relying", "answer": "reliant", "question": "Many corporate farms are increasingly ___ on subsidies from the government thanks to fluctuating food prices."}, "925": {"1": "that", "2": "so that", "3": "what", "4": "unless", "answer": "that", "question": "The new management will ask ___ you please make sure you are aware of the new safety guidelines in the laboratories."}, "926": {"1": "exchanged", "2": "eliminated", "3": "proceeded", "4": "forwarded", "answer": "forwarded", "question": "After the surveys were collected, the Research Department organized them and ___ the results to the chemistry team on the 3rd floor."}, "927": {"1": "by", "2": "of", "3": "while", "4": "around", "answer": "of", "question": "Hitchens Financial Advisors has been hiring accountants ___ the highest ability."}, "928": {"1": "all", "2": "almost", "3": "always", "4": "every", "answer": "all", "question": "TEST 6  On weekends the Italian restaurant is often busy ___ hours of the day and night."}, "929": {"1": "recognized", "2": "recognizing", "3": "recognize", "4": "recognizes", "answer": "recognized", "question": "Forelli Media Inc. is an internationally ___ - marketing firm noted for its success throughout Europe, East Asia, and the Americas."}, "930": {"1": "available", "2": "cooperative", "3": "common", "4": "direct", "answer": "available", "question": "More than  state-owned companies still remain ___ for privatization, according to the Privatization Agency."}, "931": {"1": "select", "2": "selecting", "3": "selected", "4": "was selected", "answer": "selected", "question": "The Wallace Goldberg Committee of Environmental Awareness unanimously ___ the technical team of Walpole Enterprises for their annual award."}, "932": {"1": "between", "2": "into", "3": "near", "4": "until", "answer": "near", "question": "Patients may hang their coats in the closet ___ the vending machine in the waiting room."}, "933": {"1": "enough", "2": "so", "3": "more", "4": "approximately", "answer": "approximately", "question": "It may take ___ 4 days for international orders to arrive at their destination, depending on the location."}, "934": {"1": "increases", "2": "increasing", "3": "increase", "4": "increased", "answer": "increases", "question": "Salary ___ are verified after an evaluation performed every six months after starting employment."}, "935": {"1": "announce", "2": "enclose", "3": "measure", "4": "bargain", "answer": "announce", "question": "Bancroft Weekly will ___ the winning entry of the September Shakespeare Festival."}, "936": {"1": "familiarity", "2": "familiarly", "3": "familiar", "4": "familiarize", "answer": "familiar", "question": "New owners of Century Regal's condominiums are advised to become more ___ with the amenities and services available to residents."}, "937": {"1": "instead of", "2": "still", "3": "even though", "4": "however", "answer": "even though", "question": "Cairne Fitness Centers has decided to open a large facility in Manhattan ___ its financial situation is unstable because of shifting property values."}, "938": {"1": "relevant", "2": "reluctant", "3": "redundant", "4": "reduced", "answer": "reluctant", "question": "Most banks are ___ to loan money to small businesses and that is the big reason for the recession in this country."}, "939": {"1": "publish", "2": "published", "3": "publication", "4": "publishing", "answer": "published", "question": "Bullet Hole Press specializes in the publication of horror, mystery, and psychological thrillers, so no other genres will be ___ ."}, "940": {"1": "at", "2": "in", "3": "upon", "4": "before", "answer": "before", "question": "Customers should know that ordering one of the new JP- laptops online ___ December 1st will guarantee that it will arrive prior to the start of the Christmas shopping season."}, "941": {"1": "once", "2": "never", "3": "not", "4": "ever", "answer": "ever", "question": "Purchasing tickets for Rocky Multiplexes has become easier than ___ thanks to changes made to the theater's website."}, "942": {"1": "truly", "2": "quickly", "3": "shortly", "4": "efficiently", "answer": "quickly", "question": "Several seats in the auditorium may be easily and ___ removed tor the accommodation of wheelchairs."}, "943": {"1": "farther", "2": "over", "3": "aside from", "4": "in addition to", "answer": "over", "question": "The total income of many smaller clothing retail franchises reaches ___ $20 million annually."}, "944": {"1": "various", "2": "vary", "3": "variety", "4": "varied", "answer": "variety", "question": "The ___ of foods at Ricotta Supermarkets makes it a popular choice among consumers who enjoy preparing international cuisine."}, "945": {"1": "allows", "2": "promotes", "3": "accepts", "4": "gives", "answer": "allows", "question": "As part of our latest marketing strategy, this coupon ___ customers to save more money on purchases made within a certain time period."}, "946": {"1": "affordable", "2": "affording", "3": "affords", "4": "afford", "answer": "affordable", "question": "Changes in automotive technology are making hybrid cars increasingly ___ to more consumers."}, "947": {"1": "while", "2": "during", "3": "wherever", "4": "as well as", "answer": "while", "question": "Your e-mail, ___ in transit, is potentially visible to anyone outside your enterprise who might have access to your server."}, "948": {"1": "limited", "2": "limit", "3": "limitations", "4": "limiting", "answer": "limited", "question": "Since the supply is ___ , all customers are encouraged to make orders as soon as possible."}, "949": {"1": "By", "2": "Regarding", "3": "Against", "4": "Above", "answer": "By", "question": "___ the end of next week, all employees must complete an evaluation form."}, "950": {"1": "comment", "2": "remark", "3": "address", "4": "exclaim", "answer": "address", "question": "The Chamber of Commerce will ___ concerns about declining investment in the township's newly-constructed industries."}, "951": {"1": "severely", "2": "severe", "3": "severeness", "4": "severity", "answer": "severely", "question": "A few vehicles were ___ damaged by the recent hailstorm and will have to be replaced immediately."}, "952": {"1": "he", "2": "who", "3": "his", "4": "whose", "answer": "who", "question": "Karen Solden will replace Harold Walker, ___ is being promoted to a higher position in the company."}, "953": {"1": "applicants", "2": "application", "3": "applies", "4": "applied", "answer": "applicants", "question": "The ___ for the research team are asked to wait in room  for their interviews."}, "954": {"1": "in order to", "2": "so that", "3": "because of", "4": "just as", "answer": "so that", "question": "Contractors will be renovating the office building ___ the stockroom will be on the first floor."}, "955": {"1": "length", "2": "lengthen", "3": "lengthy", "4": "lengthens", "answer": "lengthy", "question": "Registering and shelving new books and other media is now a ___ process since we are down to seven librarians."}, "956": {"1": "conducted", "2": "installed", "3": "admitted", "4": "posted", "answer": "installed", "question": "The new, energy-efficient air conditioners have not been ___ yet, so employees are permitted to bring in oscillating fans from home in the meantime."}, "957": {"1": "while", "2": "yet", "3": "on", "4": "if", "answer": "if", "question": "Marco Polo Airlines can upgrade a ticket only ___ it is more than 48 hours prior to departure time."}, "958": {"1": "approving", "2": "outstanding", "3": "magnified", "4": "hopeful", "answer": "outstanding", "question": "Seaton Landscaping makes sure that customers receive ___ service for a good price and within a reasonable amount of time."}, "959": {"1": "preference", "2": "choice", "3": "placement", "4": "decision", "answer": "preference", "question": "13?. A new survey by the Allentown Gazette revealed a strong ___ for small, local coffee shops instead of large franchises."}, "960": {"1": "of", "2": "to", "3": "with", "4": "off", "answer": "with", "question": "Whenever you look to make a deal ___ anybody, always establish the decisionmaking hierarchy ahead of time."}, "961": {"1": "whether", "2": "as it", "3": "except", "4": "unless", "answer": "unless", "question": "Information on clients of Van Houten Exchange Bank remains confidential ___ written permission is provided by the individual."}, "962": {"1": "wastes", "2": "wasted", "3": "wasting", "4": "waste", "answer": "waste", "question": "Nearly 1, ___ tires were diverted from landfill disposal and recycled into rubber to resurface the school track."}, "963": {"1": "viewers", "2": "fees", "3": "budgets", "4": "scenes", "answer": "budgets", "question": "The advertising ___ of smaller businesses often leave them without enough exposure in local media."}, "964": {"1": "your", "2": "mine", "3": "yours", "4": "my", "answer": "your", "question": "After making ___ final decision, please inform the secretary, Mrs. Chester."}, "965": {"1": "Almost", "2": "Only", "3": "Entirely", "4": "Neither", "answer": "Only", "question": "___ those applicants who have graduated after four years at an accredited university will be considered for the position."}, "966": {"1": "avoid", "2": "avoided", "3": "to avoid", "4": "avoids", "answer": "to avoid", "question": "The business weekly magazine suggested that ___ shipping problems in the upcoming holiday season, businesses should encourage customers to shop early."}, "967": {"1": "values", "2": "profits", "3": "outcomes", "4": "costs", "answer": "costs", "question": "Because of operating ___ , Fayette Industries seeks to operate its manufacturing plants in only certain parts of the country."}, "968": {"1": "competing", "2": "competitive", "3": "competes", "4": "competition", "answer": "competition", "question": "The price ___ between the two companies was intense, but customers benefited from the low-priced products."}, "969": {"1": "storing", "2": "store", "3": "stores", "4": "to store", "answer": "to store", "question": "Once you purchase a carton of milk, you are supposed ___ it at a low temperature."}, "970": {"1": "informed", "2": "joined", "3": "announced", "4": "applied", "answer": "announced", "question": "After several board member meetings, the chief executive ___ that the company is going to merge with its partner company, KOS Inc."}, "971": {"1": "it", "2": "itself", "3": "other", "4": "them", "answer": "it", "question": "Although the company's board members decided on a new promotional product, the CEO chose a different one because he thought ___ would not appeal to the public."}, "972": {"1": "closely", "2": "perfectly", "3": "recently", "4": "highly", "answer": "recently", "question": "Because the price of oil has gone up ___ , the demand for hybrid cars has been increasing as well."}, "973": {"1": "as", "2": "to", "3": "on", "4": "at", "answer": "at", "question": "Despite the fact that the company has held its annual ceremonies ___ Shaneil Hall in the past, the new general manager decided to hold the ceremony at a different place this year."}, "974": {"1": "regular", "2": "regularly", "3": "regularity", "4": "regulating", "answer": "regular", "question": "Our ___ customers are what have been sustaining our sales even though the number of customers has decreased ever since the recession."}, "975": {"1": "extensive", "2": "extensively", "3": "extension", "4": "extending", "answer": "extensively", "question": "As an anthropologist, Micky has to travel ___ in order to explore different cultures and traditions around the world."}, "976": {"1": "neither", "2": "whether", "3": "either", "4": "unless", "answer": "whether", "question": "When John had to decide ___ to apply for a new job or keep his old one, he kept his old job because there were not that many job opportunities available."}, "977": {"1": "her", "2": "hers", "3": "she", "4": "herself", "answer": "her", "question": "When Kimmy realized that ___ agent charged her more than what he was supposed to, she hired a lawyer to sue him."}, "978": {"1": "respond", "2": "response", "3": "responsive", "4": "responded", "answer": "response", "question": "As a ___ to my proposal, Mike simply threw away the notes I brought to him, indicating that he is not satisfied with my ideas."}, "979": {"1": "inspection", "2": "inspected", "3": "inspect", "4": "inspecting", "answer": "inspected", "question": "The entire company had to be ___ because the CEO was sued for inappropriate usage of the company's funds."}, "980": {"1": "Previous", "2": "Included", "3": "Experienced", "4": "Actual", "answer": "Experienced", "question": "___ workers always have a better chance at getting a job and also a higher salary."}, "981": {"1": "if", "2": "or", "3": "even", "4": "both", "answer": "if", "question": "Jane always wondered ___ she would have been more successful if she had completed graduate school."}, "982": {"1": "Those", "2": "This", "3": "Which", "4": "Whose", "answer": "This", "question": "Pointing at the book in front of him, Peter said, \" ___ is the book that inspired me to study science.\""}, "983": {"1": "On", "2": "Around", "3": "From", "4": "Into", "answer": "From", "question": "___ the time I lost my job, I've been constantly looking at the career section of the newspaper, but haven't been able to find anything."}, "984": {"1": "cautious", "2": "cautiously", "3": "caution", "4": "cautiousness", "answer": "caution", "question": "Although the note said \"Please handle with ___ ,\"most of the workers were handling it as if it was some kind of toy."}, "985": {"1": "only", "2": "earlier", "3": "yet", "4": "rather", "answer": "yet", "question": "Workers who have not ___ paid the entrance fee to the summer conference are required to do so by the end of the day."}, "986": {"1": "stepping", "2": "entering", "3": "processing", "4": "producing", "answer": "entering", "question": "All the interns are required to wear special aprons, gloves and goggles prior to ___ the laboratory."}, "987": {"1": "initially", "2": "equally", "3": "shortly", "4": "nearly", "answer": "shortly", "question": "Since the climate control system has finally been repaired, the Ice Age section of the museum will be reopening ___ ."}, "988": {"1": "growth", "2": "effort", "3": "rise", "4": "strength", "answer": "effort", "question": "Jack's boss dislikes the way he works because he works without putting any ___ into it."}, "989": {"1": "started", "2": "had started", "3": "would start", "4": "will be started", "answer": "started", "question": "Mr. Jones ___ his own business last January and it is already turning a healthy profit."}, "990": {"1": "except", "2": "after", "3": "unlike", "4": "with", "answer": "after", "question": "The stores in this area are generally closed ___ 6 p.m., but they were open until 9 p.m. tonight because of the upcoming long weekend."}, "991": {"1": "prefer", "2": "preferred", "3": "preference", "4": "preferring", "answer": "preferred", "question": "Diesel engine cars are ___ in Asian countries due to their high torque and high oil efficiency."}, "992": {"1": "locate", "2": "location", "3": "located", "4": "locations", "answer": "locations", "question": "Confused by the two very close ___ of the companies, John had trouble finding the place, which resulted in him being late on his first day at work."}, "993": {"1": "As long as", "2": "Prior to", "3": "Despite", "4": "In order to", "answer": "As long as", "question": "___ Parker keeps up his good work, his boss is planning on promoting him next month."}, "994": {"1": "efficiency", "2": "demand", "3": "influx", "4": "benefit", "answer": "demand", "question": "Because the ___ for electricity has increased, the government is looking for an alternative way to produce more power."}, "995": {"1": "little", "2": "whoever", "3": "few", "4": "so", "answer": "few", "question": "Although there are many respected role models among the executives at the company, employees tend to only pay attention to the ___ bad examples."}, "996": {"1": "precede", "2": "precedes", "3": "preceded", "4": "preceding", "answer": "preceding", "question": "Considering the size of the company in the ___ year, BHW corporation has made tremendous progress."}, "997": {"1": "nor", "2": "instead of", "3": "so that", "4": "if", "answer": "so that", "question": "The company registered the copyright for its new product ___ no other companies could create a similar product."}, "998": {"1": "congested", "2": "congestion", "3": "congestive", "4": "congests", "answer": "congestion", "question": "The ___ of blood vessels that often results in serious health issues can be genetically passed on to the next generation."}, "999": {"1": "advocated", "2": "assumed", "3": "administered", "4": "recognized", "answer": "recognized", "question": "At the fall conference, retiring employees were ___ for having made a huge contribution to the company for more than 30 years."}, "1000": {"1": "brief", "2": "briefer", "3": "briefly", "4": "briefness", "answer": "briefly", "question": "During his visit to the company factories, Mr. Van Wyk also ___ visited with local town leaders in order to gain their trust."}, "1001": {"1": "in order to", "2": "and", "3": "should", "4": "when", "answer": "should", "question": "Although the company sent a formal letter indicating that the leaking building ___ be fixed as soon as possible, the building owner didn't even respond to it."}, "1002": {"1": "saved", "2": "accepted", "3": "provoked", "4": "offered", "answer": "offered", "question": "Chandler ___ a great deal to his partner company, but it was rejected because they had already signed a contract with another company."}, "1003": {"1": "accustomed", "2": "donated", "3": "distributed", "4": "outfitted", "answer": "outfitted", "question": "According to NFA rules, football players must be ___ with proper equipment, including shoulder pads and a helmet."}, "1004": {"1": "represent", "2": "representation", "3": "represented", "4": "representative", "answer": "representative", "question": "A ___ from BHY explained that the recent recall of its tires would not adversely affect sales."}, "1005": {"1": "are familiar to", "2": "will be familiar with", "3": "been familiarized", "4": "should familiarize", "answer": "should familiarize", "question": "The new members of the board ___ themselves with the company's employees so that they can provide a more friendly work environment."}, "1006": {"1": "vacant", "2": "scattered", "3": "deserted", "4": "wasteful", "answer": "wasteful", "question": "The industrial engineers realized that the procedure that the factory was currently going through was ___ and needed some changes."}, "1007": {"1": "In order for", "2": "By the time", "3": "As much as", "4": "Now that", "answer": "By the time", "question": "___ the company launched its new products, it was already too late to make a significant impact on the market."}, "1008": {"1": "she", "2": "her", "3": "hers", "4": "herself", "answer": "her", "question": "Since she's running late for ___ meeting downtown, Ms. Joyce will have to catch a taxi."}, "1009": {"1": "on", "2": "from", "3": "by", "4": "in", "answer": "from", "question": "As all our locations are individually owned and operated, prices will vary ___ location to location."}, "1010": {"1": "type", "2": "will type", "3": "was tying", "4": "to type", "answer": "to type", "question": "Dr. Teitelbaum asked his assistant ___ the report for tomorrow morning's meeting."}, "1011": {"1": "or", "2": "and", "3": "yet", "4": "if", "answer": "and", "question": "Between April 2nd ___ April 11th, the Merewether Library will be closed for renovations."}, "1012": {"1": "More", "2": "Over", "3": "Higher", "4": "Further", "answer": "Over", "question": "___ $5 million was paid for the construction of this office building."}, "1013": {"1": "always", "2": "nearly", "3": "well", "4": "for", "answer": "always", "question": "Anne Farnsworth ___ tries to interview potential employees as thoroughly as possible."}, "1014": {"1": "success", "2": "successful", "3": "successfully", "4": "successes", "answer": "successfully", "question": "Once Mr. Mirren ___ completes his studies and necessary training, he may come and work for our corporation."}, "1015": {"1": "between", "2": "through", "3": "after", "4": "out", "answer": "after", "question": "All work ___ 9 p.m. is considered overtime according to your contract."}, "1016": {"1": "directs", "2": "directed", "3": "direction", "4": "directly", "answer": "direction", "question": "Under the ___ of Dr. Veracini, Cascadia Chamicals Inc. has patented several formulas and signed some lucrative contracts with other companies."}, "1017": {"1": "attend", "2": "attendance", "3": "were attending", "4": "attendee", "answer": "attend", "question": "While Mr. Christopher Bloom is in New York to meet with an important client, he may ___ a few financial investment seminars."}, "1018": {"1": "into", "2": "until", "3": "among", "4": "without", "answer": "without", "question": "Borrowing library materials ___ the necessary identification is not allowed."}, "1019": {"1": "procedures", "2": "developments", "3": "categories", "4": "qualifications", "answer": "procedures", "question": "Standard ___ when performing certain experiments in the laboratory have changed over the past twenty years."}, "1020": {"1": "value", "2": "valuable", "3": "valuably", "4": "valuing", "answer": "valuable", "question": "Graduates from the Melrose College of Technology often make ___ contributions in several fields, including engineering, computer sciences, and astronomy."}, "1021": {"1": "produced", "2": "assembled", "3": "equipped", "4": "delivered", "answer": "delivered", "question": "Large packages will be ___ to the stockroom in the northwest corner of the building."}, "1022": {"1": "equal", "2": "equally", "3": "equaled", "4": "equality", "answer": "equally", "question": "The two competing software programs were determined to be ___ effective in making filing taxes from home an easy task."}, "1023": {"1": "proposed", "2": "commented", "3": "regarded", "4": "expressed", "answer": "expressed", "question": "Mr. Keating, the CEO, has ___ concern about rising fuel prices on our ability to efficiently transport raw materials."}, "1024": {"1": "expected", "2": "expecting", "3": "expectation", "4": "expect", "answer": "expected", "question": "The ___ delivery date was moved ahead by one week because of a minor computer error."}, "1025": {"1": "present", "2": "scheme", "3": "series", "4": "progression", "answer": "series", "question": "Ms. Jane Millard will be the guest lecturer at a ___ of seminars on ethical journalism."}, "1026": {"1": "funding", "2": "funds", "3": "funded", "4": "found", "answer": "funded", "question": "Public health and obesity experts are getting increasingly worried about the number of studies being ___ by food and beverage companies."}, "1027": {"1": "refund", "2": "purchase", "3": "limit", "4": "registration", "answer": "refund", "question": "Customers who want a ___ must return with the merchandise and the receipt within 30 days of purchase."}, "1028": {"1": "implementation", "2": "implements", "3": "implemented", "4": "implementing", "answer": "implemented", "question": "The research team ___ several policies on how sensitive issues should be tackled."}, "1029": {"1": "probable", "2": "responsible", "3": "trusting", "4": "powerful", "answer": "responsible", "question": "Ms. Yamaha was ___ for the successful funding campaign at the new business college."}, "1030": {"1": "competitor", "2": "competitiveness", "3": "competitive", "4": "competitively", "answer": "competitiveness", "question": "Poplar Mills Inc. has been purchasing more arable land, hoping to increase not only production but also its ___ in the nation's grocery stores."}, "1031": {"1": "Who", "2": "When", "3": "Why", "4": "Which", "answer": "When", "question": "___ passengers board the plane, flight attendants are expected to politely greet them."}, "1032": {"1": "our", "2": "ours", "3": "us", "4": "we", "answer": "us", "question": "Our new website allows ___ to keep track of all orders."}, "1033": {"1": "canceled", "2": "productive", "3": "initial", "4": "impartial", "answer": "initial", "question": "The ___ shipment of desktop computers should arrive on March 23rd."}, "1034": {"1": "careful", "2": "carefully", "3": "more careful", "4": "carefulness", "answer": "carefully", "question": "When handling large funds, bank employees are required to check the statements ___ to make sure that everything is correct."}, "1035": {"1": "obtain", "2": "define", "3": "recall", "4": "inquire", "answer": "obtain", "question": "If you make an error on the application form, it is advised that you discard it and ___ a new copy at the front desk."}, "1036": {"1": "so", "2": "such", "3": "ones", "4": "some", "answer": "some", "question": "On the municipality's website one can read reviews of ___ of the city's finest restaurants."}, "1037": {"1": "freely", "2": "extremely", "3": "definitely", "4": "usually", "answer": "definitely", "question": "Dr. Renault reassured the company's president that the research department will ___ reach this year's goals with the allotted funding."}, "1038": {"1": "as", "2": "of", "3": "for", "4": "with", "answer": "of", "question": "To increase your chances ___ obtaining your accommodation in a hotel of your choice, kindly return the form as soon as possible."}, "1039": {"1": "Because", "2": "After", "3": "Now that", "4": "Even if", "answer": "After", "question": "___ arriving at the office at 8 a.m., Ms. McAllister begins her day by preparing the necessary client files for that day."}, "1040": {"1": "kind", "2": "kindly", "3": "kindlier", "4": "kinder", "answer": "kindly", "question": "The Phalanx Bus Co. reminds passengers to ___ refrain from propping their feet against the seat in front of them."}, "1041": {"1": "unfolded", "2": "outstanding", "3": "reversing", "4": "inscribed", "answer": "outstanding", "question": "Her ___ work with the branch in San Francisco has earned Ms. Sosa a welldeserved promotion."}, "1042": {"1": "most of", "2": "too much", "3": "all the more", "4": "many more", "answer": "all the more", "question": "Mr.Kim's acceptance of this award is ___ remarkable when we realize that he has not worked in the field of digital multimedia's technology."}, "1043": {"1": "rapidly", "2": "securely", "3": "carefully", "4": "anxiously", "answer": "securely", "question": "The Peterson-Jaffe wedding day is ___ approaching, but the caterers haven't started working on it yet."}, "1044": {"1": "frequented", "2": "frequently", "3": "frequent", "4": "frequency", "answer": "frequent", "question": "Doctors at Stephen Mallory Memorial Hospital claim that cases of food poisoning caused by improper storage are becoming more ___ ."}, "1045": {"1": "economy", "2": "deposit", "3": "finance", "4": "placement", "answer": "deposit", "question": "We will process your ___ after proper notification from the other bank."}, "1046": {"1": "them", "2": "theirs", "3": "their own", "4": "themselves", "answer": "their own", "question": "Bruce and Kate French have decided to quit their old jobs at Citadel Financial and start a financial consulting business of ___ ."}, "1047": {"1": "estimating", "2": "unfolding", "3": "discontinuing", "4": "solving", "answer": "discontinuing", "question": "SAV Inc. will be ___ production of one of their trademark products."}, "1048": {"1": "filling", "2": "fell", "3": "fallen", "4": "file", "answer": "file", "question": "When you need supplies, ___ a request with the office manager."}, "1049": {"1": "are", "2": "have", "3": "be", "4": "do", "answer": "be", "question": "The bell captain suggested that more porters ___ hired."}, "1050": {"1": "depart", "2": "departs", "3": "to depart", "4": "departing", "answer": "departs", "question": "The last train to Hamburg ___ at 10:30."}, "1051": {"1": "as", "2": "by", "3": "to", "4": "from", "answer": "by", "question": "The vice-president will be seated ___ the chairman at the banquet."}, "1052": {"1": "to work", "2": "was working", "3": "workable", "4": "worked", "answer": "to work", "question": "The manager got his staff ___ last weekend."}, "1053": {"1": "to ascend", "2": "to increase", "3": "to escalate", "4": "to raise", "answer": "to increase", "question": "The newspaper expects circulation ___ next year."}, "1054": {"1": "going", "2": "are going", "3": "go", "4": "is going", "answer": "is going", "question": "The head of operations ___ to the management convention."}, "1055": {"1": "limits", "2": "to limit", "3": "limiting", "4": "limit", "answer": "to limit", "question": "Reductions in the budget require us ___ our costs for international travel."}, "1056": {"1": "confusing", "2": "confuse", "3": "confused", "4": "confuses", "answer": "confused", "question": "The ticketholders may be ___ about the change in date."}, "1057": {"1": "creative", "2": "most creative", "3": "more creative", "4": "the most creative", "answer": "the most creative", "question": "Ms. Mosley is ___ member of our advertising team."}, "1058": {"1": "assume", "2": "assign", "3": "assent", "4": "assist", "answer": "assist", "question": "Mr. Cruz needs someone to ___ him with the conference display."}, "1059": {"1": "on", "2": "through", "3": "into", "4": "without", "answer": "on", "question": "The stapler is ___ the desk."}, "1060": {"1": "is list", "2": "listing", "3": "is listed", "4": "is listing", "answer": "is listed", "question": "Each passenger's name ___ with his or her cabin number."}, "1061": {"1": "paid", "2": "will pay", "3": "have paid", "4": "are paying", "answer": "will pay", "question": "If the delivery is late, we ___ the shipping charges."}, "1062": {"1": "until", "2": "to", "3": "at", "4": "for", "answer": "at", "question": "The bus will leave promptly ___ 8:30."}, "1063": {"1": "reviewing", "2": "reviews", "3": "review", "4": "to review", "answer": "review", "question": "The ship's captain requests that all passengers ___ emergency procedures."}, "1064": {"1": "knew", "2": "known", "3": "is knowing", "4": "has known", "answer": "knew", "question": "Ms. Friel ___ about her promotion before it was announced."}, "1065": {"1": "with", "2": "in", "3": "for", "4": "by", "answer": "by", "question": "All travel arrangements must be completed ___ December 5."}, "1066": {"1": "the busiest", "2": "busier than", "3": "busy as", "4": "as busy", "answer": "busier than", "question": "The airport was ___ Mr. Debionne had expected."}, "1067": {"1": "prosper", "2": "prosperous", "3": "prosperity", "4": "prospering", "answer": "prosper", "question": "A firm will not ___ if its employees are unhappy."}, "1068": {"1": "coming", "2": "to come", "3": "comes", "4": "come", "answer": "comes", "question": "At midnight, the second shift of security guards ___ on duty."}, "1069": {"1": "final", "2": "finalize", "3": "finally", "4": "finality", "answer": "finalize", "question": "Ms. Najar wants to ___ the costs by tonight."}, "1070": {"1": "hire", "2": "hiring", "3": "hired", "4": "to hire", "answer": "hiring", "question": "Ms. Yu has suggested ___ more reservation clerks."}, "1071": {"1": "always is available", "2": "is always available", "3": "is available always", "4": "being always available", "answer": "is always available", "question": "A customer service representative ___ at our catalogue number."}, "1072": {"1": "on", "2": "for", "3": "at", "4": "in", "answer": "at", "question": "Can you meet with us ___ 11:00?"}, "1073": {"1": "organized", "2": "organizing", "3": "organizes", "4": "to organize", "answer": "organizing", "question": "The manager suggested ___ a research team."}, "1074": {"1": "takes", "2": "took", "3": "take", "4": "taken", "answer": "takes", "question": "The receptionist ___ a message if you do not answer your phone."}, "1075": {"1": "includes", "2": "is included", "3": "is including", "4": "included", "answer": "is included", "question": "A list of compatible software ___ with your new computer."}, "1076": {"1": "to include", "2": "includes", "3": "including", "4": "include", "answer": "includes", "question": "The price of all cruises ___ airfare and all transfers."}, "1077": {"1": "Although", "2": "Because", "3": "Therefore", "4": "However", "answer": "Because", "question": "___ we were late, we could not enter the conference hall."}, "1078": {"1": "requited", "2": "required", "3": "requisite", "4": "repulsed", "answer": "required", "question": "Hotel employees are ___ to knock before entering the rooms."}, "1079": {"1": "to wear", "2": "wear", "3": "be worn", "4": "is wearing", "answer": "to wear", "question": "Visitors are reminded ___ name tags at all times."}, "1080": {"1": "notebook", "2": "calendar", "3": "appointment", "4": "notice", "answer": "appointment", "question": "Mr. Nolde called to cancel his ___"}, "1081": {"1": "can sometimes learn", "2": "learning sometimes can", "3": "sometimes learn can", "4": "sometimes can learning", "answer": "can sometimes learn", "question": "A manager ___ new things from his or her staff."}, "1082": {"1": "at", "2": "from", "3": "until", "4": "on", "answer": "on", "question": "The budget analysis is due ___ Friday."}, "1083": {"1": "is enclosed", "2": "enclose", "3": "enclosing", "4": "enclosed", "answer": "enclosed", "question": "Please use the, ___ envelope for your reply."}, "1084": {"1": "invitation", "2": "inventory", "3": "invention", "4": "invoice", "answer": "inventory", "question": "We cannot ship the order now because our ___ is low."}, "1085": {"1": "is keeping", "2": "are keeping", "3": "to keep", "4": "has kept", "answer": "are keeping", "question": "The technicians in the research division ___ the process confidential."}, "1086": {"1": "better", "2": "as good", "3": "best", "4": "the best", "answer": "the best", "question": "Our service technicians receive ___ training available."}, "1087": {"1": "in", "2": "for", "3": "with", "4": "at", "answer": "for", "question": "Your room has been reserved ___ two nights."}, "1088": {"1": "printer", "2": "printed", "3": "printing", "4": "print", "answer": "printed", "question": "The seminar was canceled because the invitations were not ___ in time."}, "1089": {"1": "always has considered been", "2": "has been always considered", "3": "has been considered always", "4": "has always been considered", "answer": "has always been considered", "question": "This product ___ our most popular item."}, "1090": {"1": "rarely", "2": "every'week", "3": "always", "4": "sometimes", "answer": "every'week", "question": "Budget meetings are held ___ in the conference room."}, "1091": {"1": "smooth", "2": "smoothness", "3": "smoothed", "4": "smoothly", "answer": "smoothly", "question": "An administrative assistant keeps an office running ___"}, "1092": {"1": "are", "2": "is", "3": "were", "4": "has", "answer": "is", "question": "A record of complaints ___ kept in the purser's office."}, "1093": {"1": "whose", "2": "which", "3": "whom", "4": "who", "answer": "who", "question": "The person ___ lost a briefcase may claim it in the lobby."}, "1094": {"1": "whose", "2": "which", "3": "whom", "4": "who", "answer": "who", "question": "Salespeople ___ attract new clients receive a bonus."}, "1095": {"1": "receive", "2": "receives", "3": "received", "4": "receiving", "answer": "receive", "question": "Many customers have requested that they ___ notice of our sales."}, "1096": {"1": "or", "2": "and", "3": "but", "4": "nor", "answer": "and", "question": "The status report ___ the financial projections were both late."}, "1097": {"1": "in", "2": "of", "3": "on", "4": "to", "answer": "on", "question": "The message is ___ Mr. Moriwaki's answering machine."}, "1098": {"1": "mails", "2": "mailed", "3": "mail", "4": "mailing", "answer": "mail", "question": "Many subscribers have requested that we ___ the journals to their offices."}, "1099": {"1": "Although", "2": "Because", "3": "Therefore", "4": "However", "answer": "Because", "question": "___ none of us were familiar with the city, Mr. Gutman drove us to the meeting."}, "1100": {"1": "deposited", "2": "deposits", "3": "deposit", "4": "depositing", "answer": "depositing", "question": "The auditor discovered that the accountant had not been ___ the checks into the correct account."}, "1101": {"1": "move", "2": "moving", "3": "mover", "4": "moved", "answer": "move", "question": "The trainers for the seminar had the crew ___ their equipment to the conference center."}, "1102": {"1": "soon", "2": "as soon", "3": "as soon as", "4": "soon than", "answer": "as soon as", "question": "Mr. Cain will return your call ___ he arrives."}, "1103": {"1": "to take", "2": "taking", "3": "took", "4": "taken", "answer": "to take", "question": "The travel agent persuaded us ___ an evening flight."}, "1104": {"1": "in", "2": "on", "3": "over", "4": "at", "answer": "at", "question": "The train from Madrid arrives ___ noon."}, "1105": {"1": "lent", "2": "to loan", "3": "loaned", "4": "borrowed", "answer": "borrowed", "question": "The clerk ___ the computer manual from the secretary."}, "1106": {"1": "were", "2": "was", "3": "will be", "4": "would be", "answer": "were", "question": "If there ___ some restaurants near the hotel, the tourist would not have to take taxis."}, "1107": {"1": "are", "2": "is", "3": "was .", "4": "am", "answer": "are", "question": "Pens and stationery ___ kept in the top drawer."}, "1108": {"1": "popularized", "2": "popular", "3": "populated", "4": "popularity", "answer": "popular", "question": "The new insurance plan is especially ___ with employees who have families."}, "1109": {"1": "as soon as", "2": "twice a day", "3": "seldom", "4": "rarely", "answer": "twice a day", "question": "You should check your messages ___"}, "1110": {"1": "will call", "2": "had called", "3": "called", "4": "would call", "answer": "would call", "question": "The operator ___ Mr. Smith if she knew where to reach him."}, "1111": {"1": "are included", "2": "have included", "3": "is including", "4": "has including", "answer": "is including", "question": "The company ___ spouses of employees in the invitation to the banquet."}, "1112": {"1": "because", "2": "that", "3": "until", "4": "when", "answer": "until", "question": "We cannot process the order ___ we get a copy of the purchase order."}, "1113": {"1": "in", "2": "on", "3": "over", "4": "at", "answer": "on", "question": "The package should arrive ___ Tuesday."}, "1114": {"1": "to advertise", "2": "advertise", "3": "advertising", "4": "advertisement", "answer": "advertising", "question": "The company has quit ___ in that magazine."}, "1115": {"1": "economize", "2": "economically", "3": "economy", "4": "economical", "answer": "economical", "question": "Hiring temporary workers can be very ___"}, "1116": {"1": "will answer", "2": "answered", "3": "answers", "4": "answering", "answer": "answered", "question": "Mr. Ho's assistant ___ his mail while he was away."}, "1117": {"1": "beside", "2": "among", "3": "between", "4": "across", "answer": "beside", "question": "The bookcase is ___ the door."}, "1118": {"1": "Although", "2": "During", "3": "Because", "4": "That", "answer": "Because", "question": "___ it was Mr. Guiton's birthday, his staff took him to lunch."}, "1119": {"1": "successfully", "2": "successive", "3": "success", "4": "successful", "answer": "successful", "question": "Ms. Franklin directed a very ___ project."}, "1120": {"1": "including", "2": "include", "3": "been included", "4": "included", "answer": "included", "question": "The airport taxes are ___ in the ticket price."}, "1121": {"1": "but", "2": "and", "3": "as", "4": "though", "answer": "and", "question": "New paint ___ pictures will make the office look better."}, "1122": {"1": "made", "2": "has made", "3": "make", "4": "makes", "answer": "make", "question": "The president had her travel agent ___ the reservations."}, "1123": {"1": "among", "2": "between", "3": "from", "4": "beside", "answer": "beside", "question": "Please leave your luggage ___ the bus for loading."}, "1124": {"1": "explains", "2": "is explaining", "3": "explain", "4": "explaining", "answer": "explains", "question": "The cruise handbook ___ all ship policies."}, "1125": {"1": "until", "2": "because", "3": "although", "4": "once", "answer": "because", "question": "The fax was not received ___ the fax number was wrong."}, "1126": {"1": "is never too busy", "2": "never too busy is", "3": "is too busy never", "4": "being never too busy", "answer": "is never too busy", "question": "A good waiter ___ to explain the menu."}, "1127": {"1": "they", "2": "who", "3": "which", "4": "whom", "answer": "who", "question": "Participants ___ fly to the convention can get a group rate."}, "1128": {"1": "to", "2": "in", "3": "by", "4": "at", "answer": "to", "question": "Inter Coast Airlines' flight ___ Seoul has been delayed."}, "1129": {"1": "for", "2": "to", "3": "from", "4": "on", "answer": "on", "question": "The finance committee will meet again ___ the eighth of May."}, "1130": {"1": "constructive", "2": "construction", "3": "construct", "4": "constructed", "answer": "construction", "question": "The ___ of the new building will start next month."}, "1131": {"1": "be filing", "2": "is filed", "3": "be filed", "4": "is filing", "answer": "is filed", "question": "The itinerary ___ with the cruise list."}, "1132": {"1": "are calling", "2": "call", "3": "calls", "4": "will call", "answer": "call", "question": "Please ___ me any time if I can help you."}, "1133": {"1": "within", "2": "among", "3": "inside", "4": "between", "answer": "inside", "question": "The laundry bag is ___ the cabinet."}, "1134": {"1": "on", "2": "under", "3": "in", "4": "over", "answer": "in", "question": "The corporate office is located ___ the Jamieson Building."}, "1135": {"1": "that", "2": "whose", "3": "it", "4": "who", "answer": "that", "question": "The conference ___ was scheduled for next week has been postponed."}, "1136": {"1": "conducting", "2": "to conduct", "3": "conducted", "4": "conducts", "answer": "to conduct", "question": "The purser got his assistant ___ the passenger orientation."}, "1137": {"1": "be designating", "2": "are designating", "3": "were designated", "4": "designated", "answer": "designated", "question": "Please use the parking spaces ___ for visitors."}, "1138": {"1": "excite'", "2": "exciting", "3": "excited", "4": "excites", "answer": "excited", "question": "Mr. Hatori was very ___ when he got a promotion."}, "1139": {"1": "For", "2": "That", "3": "And", "4": "Before", "answer": "Before", "question": "___ she left the ship, the purser signed out."}, "1140": {"1": "to send", "2": "sending", "3": "will send", "4": "sends", "answer": "to send", "question": "Ask the accounts receivable clerk ___ the invoice."}, "1141": {"1": "had sold", "2": "don't sell", "3": "will sell", "4": "would not sell", "answer": "would not sell", "question": "If the product were not safe, we ___ it."}, "1142": {"1": "of", "2": "in", "3": "for", "4": "on", "answer": "on", "question": "The meeting will be held ___ Thursday."}, "1143": {"1": "or", "2": "and", "3": "but", "4": "neither", "answer": "and", "question": "Our company stands for quality ___ design."}, "1144": {"1": "current", "2": "currently", "3": "current than", "4": "current as", "answer": "current than", "question": "This list of contributors is more ___ that one."}, "1145": {"1": "on", "2": "under", "3": "in", "4": "over", "answer": "on", "question": "The ship's restaurant is located ___ the sun deck."}, "1146": {"1": "composed", "2": "is composing", "3": "was composing", "4": "composes", "answer": "was composing", "question": "The secretary ___ a letter when the computer crashed."}, "1147": {"1": "had used never", "2": "had never used", "3": "never had used", "4": "used had never", "answer": "had never used", "question": "The intern ___ a fax machine before."}, "1148": {"1": "Variety", "2": "Variably", "3": "Variation", "4": "Various", "answer": "Various", "question": "The conference's keynote speaker addressed ___ impacts of digital technology on the current music industry."}, "1149": {"1": "Initially", "2": "Initiate", "3": "Initiation", "4": "Initial", "answer": "Initial", "question": "The ___ outlay of assets for the construction of the new streetcar lanes has been cited by newspapers as the main cause of the project's sdismissal."}, "1150": {"1": "Additional", "2": "Addition", "3": "Adding", "4": "Additionally", "answer": "Additional", "question": "Customers who purchase more than  dollars worth of items can request an HDTV cable box at no ___ charge."}, "1151": {"1": "Substantiate", "2": "Substantially", "3": "Substance", "4": "Substantial", "answer": "Substantial", "question": "The unions requested that they be offered ___ pay increase equaling about 40, dollars a year."}, "1152": {"1": "worry", "2": "worrying", "3": "worried", "4": "worries", "answer": "worrying", "question": "One of the most ___ consequences of worldwide climate change is the steady rise of sea levels."}, "1153": {"1": "favorable", "2": "favorably", "3": "favorite", "4": "favor", "answer": "favorable", "question": "People unanimously agreed that John would have performed a great deal better under more ___ circumstances."}, "1154": {"1": "Responsibility", "2": "Responsibilities", "3": "Responsible", "4": "Responsibly", "answer": "Responsible", "question": "The office manager is ___ for supporting staff members and ensuring that their work is done efficiently."}, "1155": {"1": "Confident", "2": "Obvious", "3": "Noticeable", "4": "Intelligent", "answer": "Confident", "question": "Considering her ability, dedication, and expertise, I am ___ that Ms. Yoko will be the most suitable person for the position of marketing manager."}, "1156": {"1": "Potential", "2": "Concentrated", "3": "Dedicated", "4": "Confidential", "answer": "Confidential", "question": "The information you provide on this questionnaire is strictly ___ and will not be shared with any other vendors."}, "1157": {"1": "barely", "2": "shortly", "3": "absolutely", "4": "exclusively", "answer": "shortly", "question": "A minor electrical malfunction was discovered by the pilot ___ before the plane took off."}, "1158": {"1": "estimation", "2": "estimate", "3": "estimated", "4": "estimating", "answer": "estimated", "question": "We will make the final decision about changing the landscaping of the property after reviewing the ___ costs."}, "1159": {"1": "along", "2": "during", "3": "over", "4": "when", "answer": "over", "question": "MyHealth Co. has produced a wide range of vitamin supplements for ___ two decades."}, "1160": {"1": "brief", "2": "straight", "3": "former", "4": "steep", "answer": "brief", "question": "Following Ms. Rivera's ___ statement, the official awards ceremony for Plex Industries will commence."}, "1161": {"1": "prepare", "2": "oppose", "3": "postponed", "4": "extend", "answer": "postponed", "question": "The Master Gardeners Club had to ___ its monthly meeting because the community center's conference room was double-booked."}, "1162": {"1": "without", "2": "regarding", "3": "among", "4": "unlike", "answer": "without", "question": "The short story cannot be reprinted ___ explicit permission from the writer."}, "1163": {"1": "rising", "2": "above", "3": "dependable", "4": "lengthy", "answer": "rising", "question": "Because of ___ fuel costs, some people are choosing to stay home for the summer vacation rather than drive to tourist sites."}, "1164": {"1": "continuously", "2": "accordingly", "3": "immeasurably", "4": "recognizably", "answer": "accordingly", "question": "Two items in Ms. Burke's order were out of stock, so her invoice was adjusted ___"}, "1165": {"1": "admission", "2": "possibility", "3": "deadline", "4": "output", "answer": "deadline", "question": "Artists wanting to participate in the contest should submit their work by the ___ of June 30."}, "1166": {"1": "reimbursement", "2": "reimbursed", "3": "reimburse", "4": "reimbursing", "answer": "reimbursing", "question": "The company plans on ___ the salespeople for the expenses they incurred while attending the conference."}, "1167": {"1": "other", "2": "neither", "3": "every", "4": "each other", "answer": "each other", "question": "The monthly staff dinners give employees from different departments the chance to interact with ___ on a personal level."}, "1168": {"1": "proposed", "2": "deferred", "3": "dedicated", "4": "observed", "answer": "dedicated", "question": "Eco Unite is a non-profit organization ___ to educating the public about the environmental issues."}, "1169": {"1": "rather than", "2": "in spite of", "3": "as if", "4": "provided that", "answer": "as if", "question": "Even though Ms. Garcia had a small account at the financial institution, the employee treated her ___ she were a major investor."}, "1170": {"1": "solitary", "2": "spare", "3": "previous", "4": "random", "answer": "solitary", "question": "The witness saw only a ___ figure standing near the lamppost shortly before the crime was committed."}, "1171": {"1": "In addition", "2": "Given", "3": "For example", "4": "Upon", "answer": "Upon", "question": "___ auditing the financial records of Rockford Consulting, the accountant will submit an official report."}, "1172": {"1": "except", "2": "considering", "3": "still", "4": "along", "answer": "except", "question": "All of the trees on the property were damaged in the storm ___ the one near the rear entrance."}, "1173": {"1": "he", "2": "him", "3": "himself", "4": "his", "answer": "his", "question": "Mr. Hotei had to undergo several medical tests before receiving ___ diagnosis from the physician."}, "1174": {"1": "underway", "2": "automatic", "3": "frequent", "4": "energetic", "answer": "automatic", "question": "The library has requested funding for ___ doors for the convenience of patrons."}, "1175": {"1": "accent", "2": "function", "3": "distance", "4": "region", "answer": "region", "question": "An additional route was added to the rail line to reduce travel times in the southern ___"}, "1176": {"1": "solve", "2": "carry", "3": "impress", "4": "occupy", "answer": "carry", "question": "During the holiday season, Schwartz Department Store will ___ special make-up gift sets."}, "1177": {"1": "newly", "2": "precisely", "3": "regretfully", "4": "highly", "answer": "precisely", "question": "The air conditioner can ___ monitor the humidity level in a room."}, "1178": {"1": "superbly", "2": "traditionally", "3": "intently", "4": "incrementally", "answer": "incrementally", "question": "Banks nationwide have been raising interest rates on housing loans ___ over the last five years."}, "1179": {"1": "early", "2": "considerably", "3": "remotely", "4": "occasionally", "answer": "occasionally", "question": "Staff functions for workers in the city council department are usually held in the office lounge, but special events are ___ hosted in restaurants or hotels."}, "1180": {"1": "overly", "2": "typically", "3": "greatly", "4": "tightly", "answer": "typically", "question": "Customer service representatives at NQ Corp ___ respond to client inquires within three days."}, "1181": {"1": "abundantly", "2": "marginally", "3": "immediately", "4": "profitably", "answer": "marginally", "question": "Although Mola's skin cream is only ___ more effective than competing brands, many customers prefer it."}, "1182": {"1": "exactly", "2": "narrowly", "3": "relatively", "4": "rarely", "answer": "relatively", "question": "The gift shop on Baker Street is popular with customers because it is conveniently located, and its products are ___ inexpensive."}, "1183": {"1": "absolutely", "2": "ultimately", "3": "methodically", "4": "frequently", "answer": "frequently", "question": "Cell phone users who ___ send text messages should take advantage of the new plan being offered by the wireless carrier."}, "1184": {"1": "mistakenly", "2": "entirely", "3": "gradually", "4": "hopefully", "answer": "entirely", "question": "Because Ms. Ruiz's artwork is made ___ from reused materials, she has won awards from environmental organizations."}, "1185": {"1": "assertively", "2": "cordially", "3": "promptly", "4": "particularly", "answer": "promptly", "question": "Employees should be back in the conference room by 10:00 am, as the meeting will resume ___ once the manager has arrived."}, "1186": {"1": "recently", "2": "usually", "3": "certainly", "4": "freshly", "answer": "recently", "question": "The company has ___ hired some new staff, so a gathering to introduce them will be held at the cafeteria."}, "1187": {"1": "extensive", "2": "skilled", "3": "regular", "4": "dedicated", "answer": "skilled", "question": "Ms. Roberts is ___ at training incoming staff because she has been working in the human resources division for more than a decade."}, "1188": {"1": "economic", "2": "effective", "3": "eager", "4": "eligible", "answer": "eligible", "question": "When the entrepreneur checked the requirements listed on the Web site, he learned that he was ___ for a loan."}, "1189": {"1": "irrefutable", "2": "agreeable", "3": "compatible", "4": "desirable", "answer": "compatible", "question": "The equipment the laboratory ordered from Japan is ___ with the machines it currently uses."}, "1190": {"1": "likely", "2": "inserted", "3": "comparable", "4": "increased", "answer": "likely", "question": "Though the official announcement has not been made yet, the tickets are ___ to go on sale about the musical performance."}, "1191": {"1": "complimentary", "2": "provided", "3": "insolent", "4": "exempt", "answer": "exempt", "question": "According to Cubicle Suppllly's Web site, shoppers who make a purchase of $ or more are ___ from all shipping and handling charges."}, "1192": {"1": "relevant", "2": "relaxing", "3": "willing", "4": "necessary", "answer": "willing", "question": "Ms. Stein accepted the job offer as the company is ___ to let her work from home when needed."}, "1193": {"1": "compulsory", "2": "subject", "3": "uncovered", "4": "interior", "answer": "subject", "question": "The proposed change to the regulation regarding carbon emissions from factories is ___ to review by the Ministry of the Environment."}, "1194": {"1": "dependable", "2": "debatable", "3": "inevitable", "4": "responsible", "answer": "responsible", "question": "The library is not ___ for your personal possessions, so please do not leave your belongings unattended."}, "1195": {"1": "connected", "2": "considered", "3": "concerned", "4": "convinced", "answer": "concerned", "question": "The directors of Coleman Legal Services are ___ about the recent loss of several prominent clients to a competing law firm."}, "1196": {"1": "assured", "2": "concentrated", "3": "offered", "4": "dedicated", "answer": "dedicated", "question": "The Blue Ribbon Corporation is ___ to providing consistent, timely, and quality service to customers."}, "1197": {"1": "expressive", "2": "reliable", "3": "partial", "4": "extreme", "answer": "reliable", "question": "Mr. Sim needs a more ___ vehicle for commuting from his suburban home to his office downtown."}, "1198": {"1": "Then", "2": "So that", "3": "Before", "4": "Whereas", "answer": "Before", "question": "___ Mr Williams addressed the audience, he showed a brief video about the engine he had designed."}, "1199": {"1": "more important", "2": "importantly", "3": "importance", "4": "important", "answer": "importance", "question": "The company started to recognize the increasing ___ of using resources responsibly."}, "1200": {"1": "increases", "2": "increased", "3": "increasingly", "4": "increase", "answer": "increasingly", "question": "Aurora Furnishings is finding it difficult to make a point in its ___ competitive market."}, "1201": {"1": "attendance", "2": "was attended", "3": "has been attended", "4": "is attended", "answer": "was attended", "question": "The conference ___ by more than once hundred management executives last week."}, "1202": {"1": "present", "2": "being present", "3": "presenting", "4": "to present", "answer": "presenting", "question": "I listened carefully to my opponent's arguments before ___ my own."}, "1203": {"1": "afford", "2": "prefer", "3": "accept", "4": "agree", "answer": "afford", "question": "We can't ___ to make the types of mistakes that we have been making."}, "1204": {"1": "have meeting", "2": "have met", "3": "meet", "4": "meeting", "answer": "meeting", "question": "I am genuinely looking forward to ___ our new CEO."}, "1205": {"1": "sent", "2": "borrowed", "3": "wrote", "4": "read", "answer": "sent", "question": "I need to get the proposal back which I ___ you last week."}, "1206": {"1": "is intimidated", "2": "has intimidated", "3": "is intimidating", "4": "intimidates", "answer": "is intimidated", "question": "My boss ___ by the general manager."}, "1207": {"1": "regardless of", "2": "depending on", "3": "due to", "4": "according to", "answer": "due to", "question": "___ our decreased revenue, we have been forced to reduce expenses."}, "1208": {"1": "strikes", "2": "points", "3": "rings", "4": "predicts", "answer": "strikes", "question": "I want you to be home before the clock ___ ten."}, "1209": {"1": "However", "2": "No matter", "3": "Apart from", "4": "Despite", "answer": "No matter", "question": "___ what happens, I'll have my report on your desk by Friday morning."}, "1210": {"1": "guests", "2": "clients", "3": "visitors", "4": "customers", "answer": "guests", "question": "Employees were allowed to invite three ___ to the company picnic, such as their spouse or other family members."}, "1211": {"1": "prepare", "2": "prepared", "3": "preparation", "4": "preparing", "answer": "preparing", "question": "It looks like you could use some help ___ for the conference."}, "1212": {"1": "standing", "2": "appearance", "3": "attitude", "4": "occupation", "answer": "attitude", "question": "The first thing most employers look for in an employee is a good ___"}, "1213": {"1": "abundant", "2": "accidental", "3": "habitual", "4": "occasional", "answer": "abundant", "question": "Contrary to common belief, Africa is well endowed with ___ natural resources, from it's natural biological resources to its vast mineral riches."}, "1214": {"1": "chance", "2": "duty", "3": "blame", "4": "charge", "answer": "charge", "question": "Mr. Armstrong is expected to take ___ of the newly built factory that specializes in manufacturing all kinds of antique furniture."}, "1215": {"1": "expel", "2": "expand", "3": "exalt", "4": "exclaim", "answer": "expand", "question": "The advertising company has chosen to ___ its business into China because of its strong economy and abundant human resources."}, "1216": {"1": "twice more", "2": "as twice", "3": "twice more than", "4": "more than twice", "answer": "more than twice", "question": "Many studies have proven that eating at fast-food restaurants ___ per week is associated with more weight gain in otherwise healthy young adults."}, "1217": {"1": "has worked", "2": "worked", "3": "work", "4": "working", "answer": "work", "question": "Although Steve Pearson used to ___ as a statistical analyst for a private corporation, he is now a financial consultant for the government."}, "1218": {"1": "Gave", "2": "Taked", "3": "Showed", "4": "Elected", "answer": "Gave", "question": "Harry Worthing ___ a short presentation on the effect of the recent drop in oil prices on our investment plans in the Middle East."}, "1219": {"1": "Other", "2": "The other", "3": "Another", "4": "Some", "answer": "Another", "question": "If you travel frequently, find an agency that will change one foreign currency directly into ___"}, "1220": {"1": "clear", "2": "clearly", "3": "clearness", "4": "clearance", "answer": "clearly", "question": "All managers selected for product demonstrations at the trade show must always speak ___"}, "1221": {"1": "Convenient", "2": "Conveniently", "3": "Convenience", "4": "Convening", "answer": "Conveniently", "question": "Indianola was chosen as the convention site because its software development complex is ___ located near the airport"}, "1222": {"1": "you", "2": "your", "3": "yours", "4": "yourself", "answer": "you", "question": "He enclosed catalogue will help ___ make the right decision about the best tools for your needs."}, "1223": {"1": "considerate", "2": "consider", "3": "consideration", "4": "considerable", "answer": "considerable", "question": "Because we buy this magazine in bulk quantities, we get a ___ discount on the cover price."}, "1224": {"1": "So", "2": "Such", "3": "Very", "4": "Well", "answer": "Well", "question": "Cobalt Jewelry deals in some wholesale and special order sales at ___ below the price offered by most jewelry stores."}, "1225": {"1": "finalize", "2": "finalization", "3": "finalized", "4": "to finalize", "answer": "to finalize", "question": "Because Friday is a holiday, it will be necessary ___ the new schedule by Thursday."}, "1226": {"1": "base", "2": "based", "3": "be based", "4": "to base", "answer": "be based", "question": "The final report should ___ on the more recent findings rather than on the data collected a few months ago."}, "1227": {"1": "convenient", "2": "conveniently", "3": "convenience", "4": "convening", "answer": "conveniently", "question": "Indianola was chosen as the convention site because its software development complex is ___ located near the airport."}, "1228": {"1": "accountable", "2": "accounting", "3": "account", "4": "accounted", "answer": "account", "question": "You no longer need to enter your ___ number unless you wish to change the information included under your user name."}, "1229": {"1": "inflexibly", "2": "inherently", "3": "inaccurately", "4": "insincerely", "answer": "inherently", "question": "Although recognized as an ___ risky line of work, many young people are now training to become professional firefighters."}, "1230": {"1": "other", "2": "the other", "3": "another", "4": "some", "answer": "another", "question": "If you travel frequently, find an agency that will change one foreign currency directly into ___"}, "1231": {"1": "variety", "2": "variably", "3": "variation", "4": "various", "answer": "various", "question": "The conference's keynote speaker addressed ___ impacts of digital technology on the current music industry."}, "1232": {"1": "unwilling", "2": "unfavorable", "3": "opposing", "4": "reluctant", "answer": "unfavorable", "question": "The president has just realized that the launch of our new product must be postponed owing to ___ conditions in the market."}, "1233": {"1": "effective", "2": "effect", "3": "effectiveness", "4": "effectively", "answer": "effectively", "question": "The organizing committee decided to allocate specific tasks to members to achieve its goals more ___"}, "1234": {"1": "challenge", "2": "challenging", "3": "challenged", "4": "challenges", "answer": "challenges", "question": "Transportation costs amidst rising oil prices and environmental issues are among the toughest ___ for Partridge Farms and Maple Orchard Mills."}, "1235": {"1": "fix", "2": "write", "3": "send", "4": "direct", "answer": "write", "question": "When filling out the order form, please ___ your address clearly to prevent delays."}, "1236": {"1": "yet", "2": "just", "3": "few", "4": "still", "answer": "just", "question": "The building owner purchased the property ___ three months ago, but she has already spent a great deal of money on renovations."}, "1237": {"1": "selects", "2": "select", "3": "selections", "4": "selectable", "answer": "selections", "question": "The final ___ for regional sales manager submitted by the hiring committee include three candidates already working within the company."}, "1238": {"1": "many", "2": "more", "3": "the most", "4": "the very", "answer": "the most", "question": "Their latest proposal includes one of ___ unusual business strategies they have ever considered adopting."}, "1239": {"1": "stress", "2": "press", "3": "depress", "4": "suppress", "answer": "stress", "question": "We have always laid ___ on maintaining the most professional standards when conducting business with our associates."}, "1240": {"1": "because", "2": "since", "3": "as", "4": "due to", "answer": "due to", "question": "___ the fact that different prices affect different people, there are many varying measures of inflation in use."}, "1241": {"1": "amount", "2": "munber", "3": "cost", "4": "value", "answer": "amount", "question": "When budget the ___ of money you can live on, don't include dollars that you can't be sure you'll receive, such as year-end bonuses and tax refunds."}, "1242": {"1": "made", "2": "let", "3": "had", "4": "advised", "answer": "advised", "question": "The CEO ___ the assistant manager to conduct performance reviews for all sales agents at the Chicago office."}, "1243": {"1": "Within", "2": "Over", "3": "Between", "4": "Along", "answer": "Between", "question": "The chemistry ___ the lead actors is good, but the outdated Canadian cliches displayed throughout the movie sometimes were a bit too much for audience."}, "1244": {"1": "to", "2": "for", "3": "by", "4": "as", "answer": "as", "question": "Charies Lazarus initially founded the toy business, which is now know ___ toys \"R\" Us, in Washington DC during the postwar baby boom era in ."}, "1245": {"1": "increases", "2": "has increased", "3": "increased", "4": "increasing", "answer": "increased", "question": "Not surprisingly, the extra features on this cell phone, including its GPS function and video games, sharply ___ its price."}, "1246": {"1": "terminate", "2": "termination", "3": "terminating", "4": "terminated", "answer": "termination", "question": "The ___ of the agreement forced Ms. Zhang to negotiate a new contract with the owner of the raw materials supplier."}, "1247": {"1": "is", "2": "does", "3": "has", "4": "do", "answer": "is", "question": "Conflicts often take place in the fashion industry because intellectual property is not enforced as it ___ in the film industry and music industry."}, "1248": {"1": "keep", "2": "feature", "3": "enable", "4": "become", "answer": "keep", "question": "Managers need to know what motivates their employees to ___ them committed to their organization."}, "1249": {"1": "respect", "2": "respectful", "3": "respectfully", "4": "respected", "answer": "respectfully", "question": "Treating employees ___ with dignity will build strong rapport between companies and their own workers."}, "1250": {"1": "development", "2": "increase", "3": "growth", "4": "expansion", "answer": "expansion", "question": "Fast food giant McDonald's Corp has said it will accelerate its ___ into the Asian market in a move to boost growth."}, "1251": {"1": "high", "2": "wide", "3": "round", "4": "open", "answer": "wide", "question": "The CEO briefed the members of the board in an informal session on a ___ range of issues."}, "1252": {"1": "clears", "2": "clearly", "3": "clearest", "4": "clear", "answer": "clear", "question": "It is ___ that with the glut of digital products coming to the market, the electronics industry is entering a challenging phase."}, "1253": {"1": "while", "2": "during", "3": "when", "4": "about", "answer": "during", "question": "The city's roads are usually very crowded ___ rush hours, due to an increase in car ownership in recent years."}, "1254": {"1": "Had", "2": "Having", "3": "To have", "4": "Having been", "answer": "Having", "question": "___ finished all their work, all staff involved in the project was given one week vacation."}, "1255": {"1": "itself", "2": "some", "3": "which", "4": "theirs", "answer": "itself", "question": "The company won ___ an enviable reputation in Hong Kong in the mid-s as the territory's number one IT HR recruitment firm."}, "1256": {"1": "abundant", "2": "accidental", "3": "habitual", "4": "occasional", "answer": "habitual", "question": "Contrary to common belief, Africa is well endowed with ___ natural resources, from it's natural biological resources to its vast mineral riches."}, "1257": {"1": "Steadily", "2": "Nonchalantly", "3": "Consistently", "4": "Heavily", "answer": "Heavily", "question": "How National Auto Suppliers will be restructured depends ___ on this quarter's financial results."}, "1258": {"1": "Defaulted", "2": "Tempted", "3": "Declined", "4": "Hinged", "answer": "Defaulted", "question": "Sam could not pay back the money he owed the bank and ultimately ___ on his loan."}, "1259": {"1": "Included", "2": "Studied", "3": "Attributed", "4": "Marked", "answer": "Attributed", "question": "A decrease in the number of nursing home residents has been ___ to seniors over the age of 65 being healthier and wealthier."}, "1260": {"1": "Qualified", "2": "Quantified", "3": "Quantity", "4": "Quarterly", "answer": "Qualified", "question": "Have you interviewed any ___ applicants for the translator position?"}, "1261": {"1": "Does", "2": "Do", "3": "Are", "4": "Is", "answer": "Are", "question": "Not only ___ distributors allowed to decide their own prices, they can also choose how to position the products to their clients."}, "1262": {"1": "Increase", "2": "Growth", "3": "Advance", "4": "Develop", "answer": "Growth", "question": "The technology sector of the economy achieved enormous ___ during the nineties."}, "1263": {"1": "Reinvesting", "2": "Reinvestment", "3": "Reinstating", "4": "Rescuing", "answer": "Reinvesting", "question": "The shareholders had the option of ___ the capital from the dividend payout."}, "1264": {"1": "Overtake", "2": "Take over", "3": "Hang up", "4": "Take out", "answer": "Take over", "question": "We need someone to ___ the training program next year."}, "1265": {"1": "as a result of", "2": "caused by", "3": "based on", "4": "because of", "answer": "based on", "question": "Our estimate is ___ the current cost of materials, which may change by the time of production."}, "1266": {"1": "help", "2": "helpful", "3": "helpfully", "4": "helpfulness", "answer": "helpful", "question": "Attending the quarterly seminar on customer service was ___ for the staff members of Moon River Hotel."}, "1267": {"1": "affirmed", "2": "repaired", "3": "identified", "4": "recognized", "answer": "repaired", "question": "As the cost getting the printer ___ was nearly the same as its original price, management chose to purchase a new model."}, "1268": {"1": "were sent", "2": "were sending", "3": "sent", "4": "rising", "answer": "were sent", "question": "The lipstick samples ___ back to the manufacturer when it was discovered that a number of the products cases were damaged."}, "1269": {"1": "promoted", "2": "produced", "3": "prompted", "4": "proactive", "answer": "promoted", "question": "Rick has done such a good job this year that he has been ___ to assistant marketing director."}, "1270": {"1": "factions", "2": "factories", "3": "factors", "4": "factorings", "answer": "factors", "question": "The price of a bond depends on several ___ , including it's yield."}, "1271": {"1": "prepare", "2": "preparing", "3": "prepared", "4": "prepares", "answer": "preparing", "question": "For many middle-aged-people when it comes to ___ for retirement, they are not quite sure about how much money they should save and spend."}, "1272": {"1": "several", "2": "a few", "3": "some", "4": "a lot", "answer": "some", "question": "Dell, one of the biggest computer makers, decided to lay off ___ 8, employees over the next year as part of an going restructuring project."}, "1273": {"1": "had", "2": "would have had", "3": "have had", "4": "will have", "answer": "will have", "question": "All the staff members ___ an opportunity to express their opinions about the design of the new factory before construction begins."}, "1274": {"1": "can have", "2": "could have", "3": "will have", "4": "had", "answer": "could have", "question": "Had he set out by taxi rather than by bus, John ___ reached the bank in time for the money transfer."}, "1275": {"1": "on", "2": "until", "3": "for", "4": "by", "answer": "by", "question": "For the sake of efficiency, you are supported to turn in your proposal ___ next Monday morning at the latest."}, "1276": {"1": "widely most celebrated", "2": "most widely celebrated", "3": "widely celebrated most", "4": "most celebrated widely", "answer": "most widely celebrated", "question": "In the Western world, second only to New Year's Day, Christmas is perhaps the ___ holiday."}, "1277": {"1": "they", "2": "their", "3": "them", "4": "themselves", "answer": "their", "question": "Passengers on the aircraft are asked to secure ___ belongings during takeoff and landing."}, "1278": {"1": "dramatically", "2": "dramatize", "3": "dramatic", "4": "drama", "answer": "dramatic", "question": "Because of a ___ increase in profits this quarter, Tyro Sportswear employees will receive their first-ever year-end bonus."}, "1279": {"1": "to service", "2": "service", "3": "serviced", "4": "services", "answer": "services", "question": "Arcosa Design Ltd. offers digital and print design ___ that fit the individual client's requirements."}, "1280": {"1": "to invite", "2": "invite", "3": "inviting", "4": "are invited", "answer": "are invited", "question": "The company-sponsored five-kilometer run will be held on October 15, and all employees ___ to participate."}, "1281": {"1": "manufacturer", "2": "manufactures", "3": "manufactured", "4": "manufacture", "answer": "manufacture", "question": "Major industries in this district include food processing and aircraft ___"}, "1282": {"1": "will have corrected", "2": "had been correcting", "3": "are correcting", "4": "will correct", "answer": "will have corrected", "question": "By the time Clear Blaze Technology's word processing program goes on the market, software engineers ___ its remaining flaws."}, "1283": {"1": "at", "2": "on", "3": "for", "4": "to", "answer": "on", "question": "I am writing ___ behalf of Mr. William to inform you of the alteration in the date of our meeting in Tokyo."}, "1284": {"1": "need", "2": "needs", "3": "needed", "4": "necessary", "answer": "needed", "question": "The County Commission is still waiting for word from the Kansas City Railroad Company concerning repairs ___ to be done at three crossings."}, "1285": {"1": "beyond", "2": "within", "3": "above", "4": "along", "answer": "beyond", "question": "The managers hope that the new plan will increase sales both in the coming year and ___"}, "1286": {"1": "less", "2": "more", "3": "better", "4": "fewer", "answer": "less", "question": "Graduates holding an MBA degree are ___ competitive these days due to growing skepticism about the value of the education."}, "1287": {"1": "compel", "2": "compelled", "3": "the compelled", "4": "compelling", "answer": "compelling", "question": "The market research report was full of ___ predictions about exchange rates that later proved completely wrong."}, "1288": {"1": "During", "2": "After", "3": "Next", "4": "Above", "answer": "After", "question": "___ graduating from Laccord University, Jing Xiong worked for Osiris Financial Service."}, "1289": {"1": "outside", "2": "through", "3": "next", "4": "beyond", "answer": "beyond", "question": "Ulrich Electronics will provide free ___ of any entertainment system by June 30."}, "1290": {"1": "As long as", "2": "Because", "3": "According to", "4": "In order that", "answer": "According to", "question": "___ the terms of the contract, Mulz Janitorial Service will clean all offices in the Lundquist Building daily."}, "1291": {"1": "overwhelm", "2": "overwhelms", "3": "overwhelming", "4": "overwhelmingly", "answer": "overwhelming", "question": "Based on the ___ number of advance ticket sales, we expect to see record attendance levels at this year's festival in Donegal."}, "1292": {"1": "closely", "2": "collaboratively", "3": "primarily", "4": "independently", "answer": "independently", "question": "The environmental protection plans submitted to the council were developed by various organizations working ___ of each other."}, "1293": {"1": "for", "2": "from", "3": "of", "4": "off", "answer": "of", "question": "Please make a note ___ your customer and receipt numbers in case you need to contact us about your order."}, "1294": {"1": "assign", "2": "account", "3": "charge", "4": "contribute", "answer": "account", "question": "Dairy exports ___ for only five percent of country's total agricultural sales."}, "1295": {"1": "establishment", "2": "measurement", "3": "transaction", "4": "procedure", "answer": "procedure", "question": "The ___ for taking a holiday includes filling out a vacation request form."}, "1296": {"1": "emerge", "2": "disturb", "3": "promote", "4": "pose", "answer": "promote", "question": "Director Tim Crane is in town attending multiple gatherings to ___ his most recent movie."}, "1297": {"1": "productive", "2": "advantageous", "3": "durable", "4": "abundant", "answer": "productive", "question": "To ensure the assembly workers remain ___ , the supervisor asks them not to chat during the work hours."}, "1298": {"1": "distant", "2": "current", "3": "confident", "4": "alive", "answer": "current", "question": "Staff members are required to follow the ___ regulation as written in the employee manual unless otherwise indicated by their supervisors."}, "1299": {"1": "they", "2": "their own", "3": "them", "4": "themselves", "answer": "their own", "question": "After giving the team their assignment, the project manager left them to figure out a strategy on ___"}, "1300": {"1": "eligible", "2": "considerate", "3": "available", "4": "partial", "answer": "eligible", "question": "To be ___ for the corporate shareholder's program, you must have been working here for at least three consecutive years."}, "1301": {"1": "provisionally", "2": "comparably", "3": "restrictively", "4": "critically", "answer": "provisionally", "question": "Maria has been ___ appointed to serve as the chairperson for the treasury committee, but the position will not be permanently filled until later this month."}, "1302": {"1": "expands", "2": "guarantees", "3": "notices", "4": "affords", "answer": "guarantees", "question": "The manufacturer of these digital cameras ___ the quality of materials and labor for a period of one year from the date of purchase."}, "1303": {"1": "replacement", "2": "choice", "3": "suggestion", "4": "favor", "answer": "choice", "question": "Gmail subscribers can now select a Korean interface to give them easier access to the e-mail services in the language of their ___"}, "1304": {"1": "damaged", "2": "stretched", "3": "opened", "4": "prolonged", "answer": "prolonged", "question": "___ exposure to noise at these levels can permanently damage the bones of the middle ear and the nerves of the inner ear."}, "1305": {"1": "exact", "2": "cooperate", "3": "capable", "4": "useful", "answer": "useful", "question": "The lecture last week was especially ___ to the public relations team because it outlined the company's position on environmental responsibility."}, "1306": {"1": "specialty", "2": "negotiations", "3": "composition", "4": "priorities", "answer": "negotiations", "question": "Following weeks of ___ , the three major companies in the city's Jewelry Industry have agreed to meet for talks on product inflation rates."}, "1307": {"1": "grants", "2": "donates", "3": "requires", "4": "retrieves", "answer": "grants", "question": "Our corporation ___ employees an additional day of leave for every weekend training workshop they attend."}, "1308": {"1": "eligible", "2": "considerable", "3": "available", "4": "probable", "answer": "available", "question": "For traveler's convenience, a ticketing agent is ___ in the main terminal 24 hours a day, 7 days per week."}, "1309": {"1": "refunds", "2": "retailers", "3": "advertising", "4": "merchandise", "answer": "merchandise", "question": "Some ___ contained in the magazine may not be in stock at the warehouse."}, "1310": {"1": "By promoting", "2": "To promote", "3": "For the promotion", "4": "As a promotion", "answer": "To promote", "question": "___ the use of recycled paper, the Natural Resources Department decided to fund up to 30 percent of the cost of using recycled stationary for participating businesses."}, "1311": {"1": "attributes", "2": "supplies", "3": "members", "4": "facilities", "answer": "facilities", "question": "The team leaders are responsible for ordering safety hats, gloves, vests, and other ___ for their construction crews."}, "1312": {"1": "diversity", "2": "diverse", "3": "diversely", "4": "diversify", "answer": "diverse", "question": "The union leader has been the person who reached out to a ___ group of workers for the past decade."}, "1313": {"1": "guarantee", "2": "deadline", "3": "correspondence", "4": "segment", "answer": "guarantee", "question": "If the product is not under ___ but is repairable, a repair quote will be proposed before repairs begin."}, "1314": {"1": "pertaining", "2": "following", "3": "including", "4": "considering", "answer": "considering", "question": "We provide not only home security systems but also commercial security, ___ security cameras, access control, and fire monitoring."}, "1315": {"1": "postponed", "2": "continued", "3": "addressed", "4": "featured", "answer": "postponed", "question": "Due to the strike at the World Library in Cleveland, the conference that was to be held there has been ___"}, "1316": {"1": "recommendations", "2": "agencies", "3": "fees", "4": "periods", "answer": "fees", "question": "All rental ___ must be paid 30 days prior to the event, or the event is subject to cancelation."}, "1317": {"1": "authentic", "2": "illustrious", "3": "unprecedented", "4": "monotonous", "answer": "unprecedented", "question": "Owing to ___ demand for the award -winning book, all copies are currently sold out."}, "1318": {"1": "Once", "2": "Despite", "3": "Ahead", "4": "Owing to", "answer": "Once", "question": "___ the sales interns have completed their training program, their personnel profiles will be updated accordingly."}, "1319": {"1": "committed", "2": "predicted", "3": "subjected", "4": "contributed", "answer": "committed", "question": "CDU Insurance is ___ to offering its customers the highest level of care and customer service possible."}, "1320": {"1": "implements", "2": "had implemented", "3": "to implement", "4": "will be implemented", "answer": "will be implemented", "question": "The traffic policy formulated by the city council to relieve traffic jams in the commercial district ___ as planned next month."}, "1321": {"1": "admired", "2": "announced", "3": "abandoned", "4": "authorized", "answer": "authorized", "question": "You cannot access the building unless you have been ___ by a member of the security team."}, "1322": {"1": "requirements", "2": "deliveries", "3": "developers", "4": "qualities", "answer": "requirements", "question": "Company executives are currently reviewing the annual budget ___ submitted to them by the Financial Planning department."}, "1323": {"1": "affordable", "2": "permitted", "3": "cutting", "4": "necessary", "answer": "affordable", "question": "The Physical Therapy Association is committed to keeping costs ___ for its certification programs."}, "1324": {"1": "involving", "2": "participating", "3": "implementing", "4": "producing", "answer": "implementing", "question": "Wynson Containers is ___ a yearly shutdown of its factory so that it can be evaluated for safety and efficiency."}, "1325": {"1": "systematic", "2": "eligible", "3": "familiar", "4": "successful", "answer": "eligible", "question": "Hotels and universities are ___ to recycle their used mattress through city's recycling program."}, "1326": {"1": "Reliability", "2": "Allowance", "3": "Dependence", "4": "Estiamtion", "answer": "Reliability", "question": "___ and cost factored equally in choosing Cantavox as our main supplier."}, "1327": {"1": "to apologize", "2": "apologized", "3": "apologize", "4": "will be apologizing", "answer": "apologized", "question": "Mr Khana made a phone call yesterday during which he ___ for the delay in the shipment of the clothing order."}, "1328": {"1": "coordination", "2": "attention", "3": "appreciation", "4": "consideration", "answer": "coordination", "question": "Our newest executive assistant will be responsible for ___ between the marketing and accounting departments."}, "1329": {"1": "analysis", "2": "analyze", "3": "analytic", "4": "analytically", "answer": "analytic", "question": "Mr. June consistently offers an ___ view during the team's weekly meetings."}, "1330": {"1": "address", "2": "begin", "3": "check", "4": "designate", "answer": "check", "question": "If you are the last person in the office at night, please ___ that the copier is turned off before you leave."}, "1331": {"1": "tasks", "2": "options", "3": "fees", "4": "answers", "answer": "options", "question": "Our team has designed several delicious food and beverage ___ to make your experience at Mosaic Stadium a memorable one."}, "1332": {"1": "authentic", "2": "famous", "3": "unprecedented", "4": "cooperative", "answer": "unprecedented", "question": "Due to the ___ demand for our services, we will no longer be able to accept new orders."}, "1333": {"1": "interests", "2": "interesting", "3": "interestingly", "4": "interested", "answer": "interested", "question": "Anyone ___ in volunteering to help out with the annual fun-run event is encouraged to contact Ms.Williams, the event coordinator."}, "1334": {"1": "Cancel", "2": "Cancelation", "3": "To cancel", "4": "Canceled", "answer": "Cancelation", "question": "___ of a reservation must be made at least 72 hours before your scheduled arrival date; otherwise, a charge will be incurred."}, "1335": {"1": "inclusively", "2": "obviously", "3": "exceptionally", "4": "affordably", "answer": "exceptionally", "question": "Mrs. Davies is an ___ skilled copywriter and fantastic addition to the team."}, "1336": {"1": "insurable", "2": "unwarranted", "3": "unintentional", "4": "enviable", "answer": "enviable", "question": "The superiority of Orange Ltd.'s product has earned it an ___ position among its competitors."}, "1337": {"1": "sensation", "2": "compensation", "3": "determination", "4": "promotion", "answer": "sensation", "question": "The new product caused a great ___ among the customers, and sales exceeded our expectations."}, "1338": {"1": "alphabetically", "2": "comparably", "3": "recently", "4": "regularly", "answer": "regularly", "question": "To ensure your personal wellbeing, you should take short breaks from your desk ___"}, "1339": {"1": "reliant", "2": "forceful", "3": "capable", "4": "effective", "answer": "effective", "question": "Tim Anderson will no longer be a member of the board, ___ immediately."}, "1340": {"1": "browse", "2": "subscribe", "3": "conform", "4": "retrieve", "answer": "subscribe", "question": "Please ___ to our monthly newsletter if you would like to learn about all the latest deals."}, "1341": {"1": "responsibility", "2": "touch", "3": "charge", "4": "supervision", "answer": "charge", "question": "Ms. Duncalf is currently in ___ of the firm's Osaka branch and manages all activities in the area."}, "1342": {"1": "suitable", "2": "durable", "3": "incapable", "4": "accessible", "answer": "suitable", "question": "Unless another ___ applicant is found, Mr.Joh ns will be transferred to the office in China."}, "1343": {"1": "pertaining", "2": "following", "3": "including", "4": "considering", "answer": "including", "question": "We provide not only home security systems but also commercial security, ___ security cameras, access control, and fire monitoring."}, "1344": {"1": "rival", "2": "partial", "3": "renewed", "4": "contrasting", "answer": "rival", "question": "Many fans were shocked when the team captain, John Turner, signed a two-year contract with a ___ team for an undisclosed amount."}, "1345": {"1": "popular", "2": "popularly", "3": "popularity", "4": "popularize", "answer": "popular", "question": "According to a national survey conducted by Interland Travels, Spain was the most ___ destination for vacationers this year."}, "1346": {"1": "having", "2": "has", "3": "not have", "4": "will have", "answer": "will have", "question": "Additional measures ___ to be implemented in the plant quarantine section at Houston Airport in order to prevent the spread of the new crop disease."}, "1347": {"1": "alone", "2": "except", "3": "through", "4": "alongside", "answer": "except", "question": "Smoking is prohibited both side and outside the building ___ in the designated areas."}, "1348": {"1": "physical", "2": "physically", "3": "physics", "4": "physician", "answer": "physician", "question": "Dr. Fergusson will be the new industrial ___ for Autocross Industries starting from next year."}, "1349": {"1": "up to", "2": "apart from", "3": "not only", "4": "as soon as", "answer": "not only", "question": "The corporate medical insurance policy covers the medical expenses of ___ the employees but also their spouses and children."}, "1350": {"1": "dedicated", "2": "accustomed", "3": "referred", "4": "compared", "answer": "compared", "question": "The upgraded printing system that has been released by Yaletown Solutions features greater maintenance efficiency ___ to previous models."}, "1351": {"1": "suitable", "2": "durable", "3": "incapable", "4": "accessible", "answer": "suitable", "question": "Mr.Jones is expected to be relocated to the office in China unless another ___ candidate is found."}, "1352": {"1": "effective", "2": "effect", "3": "effectiveness", "4": "effectively", "answer": "effectiveness", "question": "The organizing committee decided to allocate specific tasks to members to achieve its goals more ___"}, "1353": {"1": "extreme", "2": "feasible", "3": "vague", "4": "utmost", "answer": "extreme", "question": "The mountain routes are shut down this winter owing to the ___ snowfall in November."}, "1354": {"1": "pursue", "2": "initialize", "3": "endure", "4": "implicate", "answer": "pursue", "question": "Miners at Iron Supplies Co. will soon have to ___ other job opportunities because the local mines are closing down."}, "1355": {"1": "Method", "2": "Guide", "3": "Staff", "4": "Role", "answer": "Guide", "question": "The latest training ___ contains tips on teaching a second language to international students."}, "1356": {"1": "variously", "2": "mostly", "3": "faithfully", "4": "responsibly", "answer": "mostly", "question": "Gourmet Fresh sales manager Peter Wong said the business had grown ___ by word of mouth."}, "1357": {"1": "Problems", "2": "Concepts", "3": "Inquiries", "4": "Positions", "answer": "Inquiries", "question": "Since Mr. Kane is on vacation until next week, all product ___ should be made to Mr. Park in the customer service department."}, "1358": {"1": "attentive", "2": "oriented", "3": "eccentric", "4": "integral", "answer": "integral", "question": "The system failure hit an ___ part of Longbeach Industry's business operations, which causes them to stop all orders for 24 hours."}, "1359": {"1": "Convince", "2": "Achieve", "3": "Perform", "4": "Implement", "answer": "Implement", "question": "The government will ___ new policies today to obtain information about the entrepreneurs operating businesses online."}, "1360": {"1": "complied", "2": "observed", "3": "breached", "4": "adhered", "answer": "breached", "question": "Any employers or contractors who are found to have ___ safety laws will be subject to a heavy fine."}, "1361": {"1": "high", "2": "higher", "3": "highly", "4": "highest", "answer": "highly", "question": "Mr. Ashburton has been ___ recommended by all three of his references."}, "1362": {"1": "he", "2": "his", "3": "him", "4": "himself", "answer": "his", "question": "Mr. Choi wants to know when the illustrations will be ready for ___ review."}, "1363": {"1": "easy", "2": "easily", "3": "easier", "4": "ease", "answer": "easier", "question": "Smooth Tek's newest software makes it much ___ for business owners to create newsletters."}, "1364": {"1": "opening", "2": "opened", "3": "opens", "4": "open", "answer": "opening", "question": "By ___ offices in London, Paris, and Madrid, Sedgehill Ltd. has continued its growth into markets overseas."}, "1365": {"1": "So", "2": "If", "3": "But", "4": "Why", "answer": "If", "question": "___ the kiln's heat is set too high, the ceramic objects inside may be ruined."}, "1366": {"1": "wide", "2": "widen", "3": "most widely", "4": "more widely", "answer": "most widely", "question": "The National Overview is the fourth ___ distributed newspaper in the northeastern region."}, "1367": {"1": "leave", "2": "left", "3": "will leave", "4": "was left", "answer": "left", "question": "Two years ago, some of the athletes ___ school to pursue a professional career or the Olympics."}, "1368": {"1": "caused", "2": "departed", "3": "directed", "4": "operated", "answer": "caused", "question": "A road collapse has___ traffic delays on the main route between Mildura and Merbein."}, "1369": {"1": "her", "2": "she", "3": "hers", "4": "herself", "answer": "her", "question": "Ms. Kim asks that the marketing team e-mail the final draft to ___ before 5 p.m."}, "1370": {"1": "Behind", "2": "From", "3": "Between", "4": "During", "answer": "During", "question": "___ her vacation, Janet traveled to Hong Kong, Taipei, and Shanghai."}, "1371": {"1": "submit", "2": "submits", "3": "submitted", "4": "submissions", "answer": "submitted", "question": "Travel expenses should be ___ no later than 30 calendar days after returning from a business trip."}, "1372": {"1": "manufacturer", "2": "manufacturing", "3": "manufactures", "4": "manufactured", "answer": "manufacturer", "question": "Customers must contact the ___ directly for all warranty and repair issues."}, "1373": {"1": "both", "2": "either", "3": "as", "4": "if", "answer": "both", "question": "Before you can enterthe building, you must show ___ your passport and your airline ticket, so have them ready."}, "1374": {"1": "motivation", "2": "reality", "3": "prevention", "4": "consequence", "answer": "motivation", "question": "Our employee ___ program can boost employee morale and decrease employee turnover."}, "1375": {"1": "they", "2": "themselves", "3": "theirs", "4": "their", "answer": "themselves", "question": "California employers should familiarize ___ with significant labor and employment laws passed by the Legislature in ."}, "1376": {"1": "nearly", "2": "often", "3": "highly", "4": "ever", "answer": "often", "question": "Companies ___ send out their free samples with discount coupons to encourage consumers to buy their products."}, "1377": {"1": "compete", "2": "competition", "3": "competitive", "4": "competitively", "answer": "competitive", "question": "It is common practice for a firm to seek a ___ advantage in order to maintain its position in the marketplace."}, "1378": {"1": "whether", "2": "then", "3": "through", "4": "or", "answer": "or", "question": "Since no more information has been released, the game will probably not come out this year ___ even next year."}, "1379": {"1": "specific", "2": "to specify", "3": "specifically", "4": "specifications", "answer": "specifications", "question": "The bids must be reviewed by the engineers to make sure all engineering ___ for the project are met."}, "1380": {"1": "unlimited", "2": "personal", "3": "accurate", "4": "believable", "answer": "personal", "question": "Library users must remove all ___ belongings when they leave the library for more than a half hour."}, "1381": {"1": "prompt", "2": "promptness", "3": "promptly", "4": "prompter", "answer": "promptly", "question": "The new management recognized the importance of this business decision and ___ reorganized operational procedures."}, "1382": {"1": "signature", "2": "delivery", "3": "termination", "4": "completion", "answer": "signature", "question": "Please complete all the questions contained on the claim form and provide a ___ where requested."}, "1383": {"1": "emphasized", "2": "emphatic", "3": "emphasis", "4": "emphasize", "answer": "emphasis", "question": "The ___ has always been on ensuring a consistently high level of quality and outstanding service."}, "1384": {"1": "On", "2": "Among", "3": "Without", "4": "Over", "answer": "Without", "question": "___ presenting a valid parking permit, employees cannot park their cars on company property."}, "1385": {"1": "absolutely", "2": "around", "3": "entirely", "4": "anywhere", "answer": "anywhere", "question": "Visible from ___ in the city, the tower stands in the very center of the Turpis territory."}, "1386": {"1": "full", "2": "quick", "3": "enough", "4": "overall", "answer": "enough", "question": "At the current speed of production, Supreme Tech is not able to manufacture___ products to meet the demands of our purchase orders."}, "1387": {"1": "cleanly", "2": "finely", "3": "usually", "4": "exactly", "answer": "usually", "question": "People in NY are healthier because they walk a few blocks every day since the roads are ___ crowded with cars and taxis."}, "1388": {"1": "related to", "2": "through", "3": "up on", "4": "according to", "answer": "related to", "question": "Any questions ___ our products or services may be addressed to Ms. Davis."}, "1389": {"1": "wait", "2": "remain", "3": "expire", "4": "delay", "answer": "delay", "question": "At this point, Northeast suggests that we ___ the start of our road work until gas prices settle down."}, "1390": {"1": "closeness", "2": "closing", "3": "closely", "4": "close", "answer": "close", "question": "Marc Ecko is rumored to be ___ to signing a deal with the licensing firm, Icon ix."}, "1391": {"1": "by", "2": "about", "3": "at", "4": "before", "answer": "by", "question": "One of the duties of library assistants is to shelve books returned ___ borrowers or used by readers within the library."}, "1392": {"1": "reported", "2": "reportedly", "3": "reporting", "4": "reports", "answer": "reportedly", "question": "Bananas imported from the Philippines are dominating supermarket shelves ___ due to their attractive appearance."}, "1393": {"1": "proving", "2": "announcing", "3": "cooperating", "4": "designing", "answer": "announcing", "question": "Mr. Brown gave a bleak view of the Christmas retail sales picture before ___ sales figures a week ago."}, "1394": {"1": "assurance", "2": "commitment", "3": "collaboration", "4": "assignment", "answer": "commitment", "question": "Public and private investments are moving ahead rapidly as the country has shown a great ___ to stability and low inflation."}, "1395": {"1": "possibly", "2": "possibility", "3": "possibilities", "4": "possible", "answer": "possible", "question": "One ___ outcome of the current economic recession is that the growth of merger activity will slow down."}, "1396": {"1": "attributes", "2": "attributed", "3": "attributing", "4": "attribution", "answer": "attributed", "question": "Most of the companies surveyed ___ their growth to marketing and sales strategies."}, "1397": {"1": "until", "2": "only if", "3": "nevertheless", "4": "even though", "answer": "even though", "question": "We haven't heard from them yet ___ we sent an email for a quote of their product prices."}, "1398": {"1": "other", "2": "added", "3": "further", "4": "extra", "answer": "other", "question": "They can print more quality prints than most ___ printing stores, not to mention faster and better."}, "1399": {"1": "most eager", "2": "eagerness", "3": "eagerly", "4": "eager", "answer": "eagerly", "question": "We are pleased to announce that the ___ anticipated tablet computer brochure has now been launched on our website."}, "1400": {"1": "however", "2": "instead", "3": "separately", "4": "otherwise", "answer": "otherwise", "question": "Visitors to the central area are invited to visit Central Ottage, one of the few historic spots in the ___ modern town of Joplin."}, "1401": {"1": "they", "2": "one", "3": "what", "4": "it", "answer": "it", "question": "Pay Per Click advertising makes ___ easy to track how your advertising and marketing efforts are going."}, "1402": {"1": "ensured", "2": "realized", "3": "commended", "4": "incorporated", "answer": "commended", "question": "The contributions made by Dr. Victor Hettigoda to the product development research were ___ by her boss."}, "1403": {"1": "in", "2": "and", "3": "yet", "4": "which", "answer": "in", "question": "The design of the proposed project is one of the criteria the committee will evaluate ___ determining the recipient of the state grant."}, "1404": {"1": "undo", "2": "redeem", "3": "recall", "4": "unveil", "answer": "recall", "question": "The company will ___ all its products from retailers' shelves because of allergy concerns."}, "1405": {"1": "was decided", "2": "will be deciding", "3": "had decided", "4": "will have been decided", "answer": "will have been decided", "question": "By the time Mr. Greenfield returns from his business trip, the company's new pol icy ___ ."}, "1406": {"1": "invitation", "2": "irrelevance", "3": "fluctuation", "4": "repayment", "answer": "fluctuation", "question": "There has been so much ___ in the demand for high-priced luxury cars that a few companies are introducing a wide range of price options."}, "1407": {"1": "construction", "2": "constructed", "3": "constructs", "4": "constructive", "answer": "construction", "question": "Note that the hotel's pool and pool deck will be closed until ___ on them is completed later this month."}, "1408": {"1": "announced", "2": "have announced", "3": "announcing", "4": "announce", "answer": "announced", "question": "Aster Broadcasting Group ___ yesterday that it expects the semiconductor market to enter full recovery mode next year."}, "1409": {"1": "at", "2": "into", "3": "among", "4": "after", "answer": "at", "question": "Instructors wishing to place materials on reserve ___ the library should fill out a Reserve Request Form."}, "1410": {"1": "attract", "2": "attractive", "3": "attracted", "4": "attraction", "answer": "attractive", "question": "This apartment complex has an ___ exterior design and stylish interior furnishings."}, "1411": {"1": "perform", "2": "admit", "3": "attend", "4": "participate", "answer": "attend", "question": "The public is invited to ___ the dinner event, with proceeds from ticket sales benefiting a BMX scholarship fund."}, "1412": {"1": "regularize", "2": "regularity", "3": "regularities", "4": "regularly", "answer": "regularly", "question": "He ___ delivers keynote speeches and holds workshops on customer satisfaction strategy and the building of profitable customer relationships."}, "1413": {"1": "also", "2": "both", "3": "the same as", "4": "not only", "answer": "both", "question": "Attendees will be required to work___ alone and in groups when performing study sample analyses."}, "1414": {"1": "as", "2": "of", "3": "either", "4": "like", "answer": "as", "question": "Unfortunately, with the rise of the popularity of soft drinks, tea is not ___ popular as it used to be."}, "1415": {"1": "they", "2": "their", "3": "themselves", "4": "theirs", "answer": "their", "question": "As demand for ___ wheat-based products falls, local producers earn less and the total income of the country declines."}, "1416": {"1": "demonstrated", "2": "entrusted", "3": "agreed", "4": "congratulated", "answer": "congratulated", "question": "Ottawa Police Chief Vern White has ___ Mr. McDonald for securing $1 million for the city's drug treatment initiative."}, "1417": {"1": "no one", "2": "someone", "3": "one anther", "4": "everyone", "answer": "everyone", "question": "Ms. James stated that ___ must work together to make sure the committee is effective."}, "1418": {"1": "occupied", "2": "accountable", "3": "qualified", "4": "specific", "answer": "specific", "question": "When you are buying an adjustable bed, you should consider ___ features such as bed height, size, material, and warranty."}, "1419": {"1": "across", "2": "during", "3": "onto", "4": "next", "answer": "across", "question": "Currently, there is an increasing demand for Internet access ___ the telecommunications industry."}, "1420": {"1": "efficient", "2": "efficiency", "3": "efficiencies", "4": "efficiently", "answer": "efficiently", "question": "Needs assessment can help you identify areas for improvement and ultimately help you realize your goals more___ ."}, "1421": {"1": "records", "2": "qualifications", "3": "guidelines", "4": "behaviors", "answer": "records", "question": "Favera Pharmaceuticals sales representatives must keep careful ___ of samples distributed and orders taken from physicians and clinics."}, "1422": {"1": "competition", "2": "competitive", "3": "competitors", "4": "competitively", "answer": "competitive", "question": "The application process is highly ___ with only 5% of applicants ultimately selected for positions."}, "1423": {"1": "assist", "2": "remind", "3": "locate", "4": "conduct", "answer": "locate", "question": "The hotel installed a touchscreen computer to help guests ___ a restaurant, get weather updates, or obtain other useful information."}, "1424": {"1": "product", "2": "producer", "3": "produced", "4": "producing", "answer": "product", "question": "This waste-to-energy power plant is the ___ of a technologically-advanced process set to achieve outstanding environmental and economical performances."}, "1425": {"1": "openly", "2": "rigidly", "3": "approximately", "4": "frequently", "answer": "frequently", "question": "Sales of Ferrer Industry's tractors ___ increase during the autumn harvest season."}, "1426": {"1": "optimal", "2": "optimize", "3": "optimally", "4": "optimization", "answer": "optimal", "question": "It is advisable to keep your operating system and software updated for ___ computer performance and security."}, "1427": {"1": "exhibition", "2": "guide", "3": "portrait", "4": "creativity", "answer": "exhibition", "question": "After attending an ___ on traditional handicrafts at the Victoria Museum in London, a young unknown designer named Laura Ashley was inspired to make her own quilts."}, "1428": {"1": "convinces", "2": "convince", "3": "convincingly", "4": "convincing", "answer": "convincingly", "question": "Mr. Henny ___ presented the argument that the pricing policy of the retailer would be the financial ruin of the company."}, "1429": {"1": "without", "2": "almost", "3": "usually", "4": "already", "answer": "without", "question": "If the employee or employer terminates the contract of employment ___ giving advance notice, they will have to pay the other party a sum equivalent which matches the employee's salary."}, "1430": {"1": "advancement", "2": "opportunities", "3": "transmitting", "4": "openings", "answer": "advancement", "question": "All employees are entitled to have a fair and equal opportunity to be considered for ___ to management positions."}, "1431": {"1": "forward", "2": "ahead", "3": "initial", "4": "limited", "answer": "initial", "question": "Although ___ findings are encouraging, further research is needed to determine the effectiveness of the advertising campaign."}, "1432": {"1": "boldness", "2": "bolder", "3": "boldest", "4": "boldly", "answer": "bolder", "question": "I've read a couple of different,articles on Franklin Roosevelt, who was a much ___ president than Barack Obama has been so far."}, "1433": {"1": "if", "2": "which", "3": "until", "4": "despite", "answer": "if", "question": "The front desk staff requests photo identification ___ a visitor to the Chicago Graphics Offices is not holding a valid pass."}, "1434": {"1": "avoid", "2": "provide", "3": "show", "4": "allow", "answer": "allow", "question": "The Textcom software from Hahn-Keller Corporation will ___ users to automate numerous repetitive tasks."}, "1435": {"1": "exit", "2": "exits", "3": "exited", "4": "exiting", "answer": "exiting", "question": "All employees are asked to turn off the lights when ___ a vacant room to conserve electricity."}, "1436": {"1": "destination", "2": "variety", "3": "analysis", "4": "style", "answer": "analysis", "question": "An ___ of monthly sales figures is essential to setting future revenue goals."}, "1437": {"1": "fortunately", "2": "immediately", "3": "extensively", "4": "eventually", "answer": "extensively", "question": "In this ___ researched study, Good Jobs shows that Thote Ltd. has received more than $1 billion in economic development subsidies from state and local governments across the country."}, "1438": {"1": "will honor", "2": "to honor", "3": "would honor", "4": "to be honored", "answer": "to honor", "question": "The Charity Classic Committee chose ___ him for all of the support he has given the Saint Joseph Medical Center throughout the years."}, "1439": {"1": "Ahead of", "2": "Until now", "3": "With", "4": "Past", "answer": "With", "question": "___ 1 O years of experience in the field, Carolyn Snyder is an internationally recognized merger and acquisition consultant."}, "1440": {"1": "profitable", "2": "filled", "3": "unfamiliar", "4": "difficult", "answer": "unfamiliar", "question": "Although most of the consumers surveyed said they understood the importance of the new healthcare reform policy, many were___ with the details of that policy."}, "1441": {"1": "enthusiasts", "2": "enthusiastically", "3": "enthusiastic", "4": "enthused", "answer": "enthusiasts", "question": "Corsica is an undeniable paradise for ___ of sea and water sports, as well as for hiking."}, "1442": {"1": "considering", "2": "considered", "3": "consider", "4": "are considering", "answer": "consider", "question": "Mr. Powers has asked that the board of directors ___ the issues, strategies and solutions identified in response to the NHHRC final report."}, "1443": {"1": "in order to", "2": "in regard to", "3": "in light to", "4": "because", "answer": "in order to", "question": "Additional funds are needed for one previously approved project ___ complete the construction contract."}, "1444": {"1": "then", "2": "what", "3": "just", "4": "whereas", "answer": "whereas", "question": "With beautiful and panoramic views, the hotel's terrace can accommodate up to  people ___ the lounge can only accommodate up to 70 people."}, "1445": {"1": "emission", "2": "market", "3": "revision", "4": "purchase", "answer": "market", "question": "During a recent test drive around Boston, it became clear there will be a strong ___ for the car, which is manufactured by Daimler AG, the maker of Mercedes-Tote vehicles."}, "1446": {"1": "With", "2": "Both", "3": "Either", "4": "Neither", "answer": "Neither", "question": "___ personal checks nor credit cards will be accepted as payment for the products."}, "1447": {"1": "qualified", "2": "qualifies", "3": "qualifications", "4": "qualifying", "answer": "qualifications", "question": "Due to his impressive ___ and experience, Rajan was offered interviews with three of Australia's top food companies."}, "1448": {"1": "participate", "2": "complete", "3": "attend", "4": "release", "answer": "participate", "question": "Anyone who wants to ___ in the meeting is expected to send an e-mail to the following address within the next two weeks."}, "1449": {"1": "experiments", "2": "response", "3": "collection", "4": "flexibility", "answer": "flexibility", "question": "The introduction of debit cards gave consumers even more ___ with their money, allowing them to withdraw cash from both ATMs and bank tellers."}, "1450": {"1": "he", "2": "his", "3": "him", "4": "himself", "answer": "his", "question": "His goal has always been to provide the best possible service to ___ customers."}, "1451": {"1": "by", "2": "in", "3": "at", "4": "to", "answer": "by", "question": "Failure to deliver your merchandise ___ the estimated delivery date will give customers the right to cancel their order without written consent."}, "1452": {"1": "to provide", "2": "provided", "3": "provide", "4": "providing", "answer": "provided", "question": "The supervisor of the marketing department, Ms. Smith, ___ all the statistics that were needed for the report."}, "1453": {"1": "opening", "2": "open", "3": "opens", "4": "opened", "answer": "opening", "question": "It appears that Chef Roberts has succeeded in ___ a third restaurant which will match the quality of his other two locations."}, "1454": {"1": "Readily", "2": "Exactly", "3": "Unusually", "4": "Urgently", "answer": "Unusually", "question": "___ cold weather over the past two months has caused gas shortages as distribution networks have struggled to meet demand."}, "1455": {"1": "efficiency", "2": "efficiently", "3": "efficiencies", "4": "efficient", "answer": "efficient", "question": "Purchase order organizer software is a flexible sales and purchase record management utility that keeps track of all business-related activities in an ___ manner."}, "1456": {"1": "before", "2": "beside", "3": "between", "4": "behind", "answer": "before", "question": "To avoid additional charges and the embarrassment of repacking at the airport, please make sure you weigh your luggage ___ leaving home."}, "1457": {"1": "convenience", "2": "convenient", "3": "conveniently", "4": "conveniences", "answer": "conveniently", "question": "Derek's Sporting Goods now has over  stores ___ located in more than 40 states across the country."}, "1458": {"1": "assembly", "2": "development", "3": "approval", "4": "progress", "answer": "assembly", "question": "The Thoth foldable chair requires some ___ but detailed instructions are provided."}, "1459": {"1": "growing", "2": "be grown", "3": "will grow", "4": "has grown", "answer": "will grow", "question": "A market study by the ARC Advisory Group predicts that the geospatial industry ___ by 50% over the next five years."}, "1460": {"1": "visiting", "2": "visit", "3": "visitor", "4": "visited", "answer": "visit", "question": "Mr. Forbes has yet to make his official school-sponsored ___ to California, though he is planning to make it the first week of September."}, "1461": {"1": "distributed", "2": "supportable", "3": "serious", "4": "dedicated", "answer": "dedicated", "question": "DriveAgain is an organization ___ to helping people with injuries, disabilities or driving challenges regain their driving independence."}, "1462": {"1": "concluded", "2": "to conclude", "3": "concluding", "4": "conclusion", "answer": "concluded", "question": "The seminar ___ with discussions on research topics that need to be addressed further."}, "1463": {"1": "Despite", "2": "Once", "3": "Whereas", "4": "While", "answer": "Once", "question": "___ the position has been filled, all the other applicants will be notified."}, "1464": {"1": "along", "2": "as", "3": "that", "4": "with", "answer": "as", "question": "Most importantly, clients of Toka can use this product at the same cost ___ traditional environmentally-unfriendly materials."}, "1465": {"1": "extent", "2": "extension", "3": "extensive", "4": "extensively", "answer": "extensive", "question": "The district rules assessment team coordinated an ___ evaluation of performance standards and emerging technologies."}, "1466": {"1": "hardly", "2": "scarcely", "3": "skillfully", "4": "likely", "answer": "skillfully", "question": "The director of the planning department commended Mr. Ken Seo tor how ___ he drew up the blueprints tor the newly proposed power plant."}, "1467": {"1": "secure", "2": "notable", "3": "imperative", "4": "confident", "answer": "secure", "question": "We take every appropriate measure to ensure that your personal information is kept ___ ."}, "1468": {"1": "automatically", "2": "automaticity", "3": "automated", "4": "automatic", "answer": "automatically", "question": "Sign up to receive our tree newsletter and you will ___ receive update notifications and other news via e-mail."}, "1469": {"1": "in front of", "2": "across", "3": "within", "4": "nearby", "answer": "across", "question": "There are quite a few great shops which are all ___ walking distance."}, "1470": {"1": "alongside", "2": "everywhere", "3": "forward", "4": "together", "answer": "everywhere", "question": "Become a member of Thrifty Asia.com and be entitled to discounts ___ in Asia!"}, "1471": {"1": "interested", "2": "interests", "3": "interesting", "4": "interest", "answer": "interested", "question": "Personal information gathered about customers ___ in leasing a solar panel system is only accessible to appropriate personnel."}, "1472": {"1": "waits", "2": "reduces", "3": "expects", "4": "prevents", "answer": "expects", "question": "The management ___ that revenue from online games and advertising will increase in the second quarter compared to the prior quarter."}, "1473": {"1": "reliant", "2": "relied", "3": "relies", "4": "reliance", "answer": "reliance", "question": "Provisions of the new national health reform law could reduce patient___ on emergency departments tor non-urgent health problems."}, "1474": {"1": "quickly", "2": "shortly", "3": "currently", "4": "equally", "answer": "currently", "question": "There are ___ only a limited number of manufacturers able to supply TB products with sufficient guarantees of safety and efficacy."}, "1475": {"1": "signify", "2": "significant", "3": "significantly", "4": "significance", "answer": "significantly", "question": "When compared with the traditional method of cleaning by wet mopping, the new method was ___ more effective in removal of microbial contamination."}, "1476": {"1": "convince", "2": "achieve", "3": "perform", "4": "implement", "answer": "implement", "question": "The government will ___ new policies today to obtain information about entrepreneurs operating businesses on line."}, "1477": {"1": "rather", "2": "so", "3": "same", "4": "either", "answer": "so", "question": "As Rochester's product line continued to grow, ___ did the company's space needs."}, "1478": {"1": "fulfilled", "2": "willing", "3": "decisive", "4": "appreciative", "answer": "appreciative", "question": "Our fitness staff are ___ of your interest and participation in their respective classes."}, "1479": {"1": "reservations", "2": "specializations", "3": "reductions", "4": "indications", "answer": "reservations", "question": "The R&D department has ___ about conducting the new research because of budget cuts within the company."}, "1480": {"1": "Furthermore", "2": "In order to", "3": "As a result of", "4": "As to", "answer": "In order to", "question": "___ reserve tickets for this event, please fill in the form below and your tickets will be emailed to you."}, "1481": {"1": "frequent", "2": "estimated", "3": "innovative", "4": "reluctant", "answer": "innovative", "question": "Opera's free and ___ web browser allows you to experience the web on your own terms."}, "1482": {"1": "corrected", "2": "decided", "3": "distinguished", "4": "proposed", "answer": "distinguished", "question": "National fertilizers provided by True Organic Food can be ___ by their green labels."}, "1483": {"1": "although", "2": "when", "3": "during", "4": "afterward", "answer": "during", "question": "Gardens will also be featured as a tour option___ the conference on Friday."}, "1484": {"1": "had not considered", "2": "will not consider", "3": "were not considered", "4": "does not consider", "answer": "had not considered", "question": "Before Gallux Corporation was rated as one of the best telecommunications companies in the country, it___ expanding its operations worldwide."}, "1485": {"1": "investigations", "2": "configurations", "3": "substitutions", "4": "modifications", "answer": "investigations", "question": "This study follows yet another which carried out numerous ___ into using a precleaner to save money on freight costs."}, "1486": {"1": "they", "2": "them", "3": "their", "4": "themselves", "answer": "their", "question": "The company is experiencing significant growth and is looking to add a new member to ___ staff immediately."}, "1487": {"1": "training", "2": "importance", "3": "titles", "4": "helping", "answer": "training", "question": "All of our cleaning professionals have undergone extensive ___ and are fully insured."}, "1488": {"1": "never", "2": "none", "3": "not", "4": "no", "answer": "no", "question": "Every client is personally handled by one of our experts, ensuring a unique travel plan at ___ extra cost."}, "1489": {"1": "either", "2": "and", "3": "neither", "4": "both", "answer": "either", "question": "Young travelers below 18 years of age need to be accompanied by ___ a parent or a guardian."}, "1490": {"1": "coordination", "2": "coordinated", "3": "coordinate", "4": "coordinator", "answer": "coordination", "question": "Careful planning and ___ pave the way for a successful meeting."}, "1491": {"1": "persisted", "2": "persistent", "3": "persistently", "4": "persistence", "answer": "persistently", "question": "QIB will work___ to maintain sustainable growth and expansion plans."}, "1492": {"1": "each", "2": "any", "3": "every", "4": "all", "answer": "all", "question": "The employee in this position must wear steel-toed boots at ___ times while at work."}, "1493": {"1": "themselves", "2": "who", "3": "whose", "4": "they", "answer": "who", "question": "Automobile mechanics ___ have not kept up with these changes have left or been forced out of the industry."}, "1494": {"1": "operate", "2": "meet", "3": "arrange", "4": "produce", "answer": "operate", "question": "Most southbound and eastbound trains will ___ on an earlier schedule in and around Niagara Falls."}, "1495": {"1": "close", "2": "next", "3": "nearly", "4": "soon", "answer": "soon", "question": "Mr. Bolton would like to offer his employees a new contract as ___ as he returns from his trip overseas."}, "1496": {"1": "sharper", "2": "sharpness", "3": "sharpest", "4": "sharply", "answer": "sharply", "question": "The acquisition was completed for $ million, which indicates just how ___ the company's value had dropped."}, "1497": {"1": "retained", "2": "afforded", "3": "detailed", "4": "attached", "answer": "detailed", "question": "This is a more ___ report of budget authority and outlays for preceding, current, and upcoming fiscal years."}, "1498": {"1": "highly", "2": "early", "3": "after", "4": "many", "answer": "highly", "question": "A successful candidate must be ___ trainable in a fast-paced work environment, with exceptional communication and computer skills."}, "1499": {"1": "ever", "2": "anymore", "3": "briefly", "4": "extremely", "answer": "briefly", "question": "The manual ___ covers multiple topics including safety and loss control, vehicle policy, and work hours."}, "1500": {"1": "out", "2": "long", "3": "late", "4": "delay", "answer": "delay", "question": "It takes one month to fix these minor problems, so unfortunately there will be a one-month ___ in the transfer of fuel."}, "1501": {"1": "declare", "2": "achieve", "3": "promote", "4": "obtain", "answer": "obtain", "question": "The lease agreement says the tenant of this unit is required to ___ renter's insurance."}, "1502": {"1": "directing", "2": "directs", "3": "directly", "4": "directed", "answer": "directly", "question": "Wholesale buyers purchase merchandise___ from manufacturers and resell it to retail firms, commercial establishments, and other institutions."}, "1503": {"1": "among", "2": "plus", "3": "throughout", "4": "upon", "answer": "among", "question": "The Fresh Twister energy drink is made with fresh lemon juice and red wine and tends to be a bestseller ___ the ladies."}, "1504": {"1": "prepare", "2": "prepares", "3": "prepared", "4": "preparing", "answer": "prepares", "question": "Guests will be able to meet Taylor Swift as she ___ to perform a free show for her fans in Central Park."}, "1505": {"1": "frequent", "2": "frequented", "3": "frequenting", "4": "frequently", "answer": "frequent", "question": "The information below is being provided in response to ___ requests for teleconference referrals."}, "1506": {"1": "impulsively", "2": "approximately", "3": "consistently", "4": "readily", "answer": "consistently", "question": "Mr. Kwon attributed his ___ strong performance to the company's sound risk management and stable management team."}, "1507": {"1": "town", "2": "anger", "3": "list", "4": "rate", "answer": "list", "question": "There is a growing ___ of residents who oppose construction of a shopping center on Kingston and Flag avenues."}, "1508": {"1": "during", "2": "past", "3": "over", "4": "down", "answer": "past", "question": "To reach Puritan House, turn right and walk ___ the building with the white columns."}, "1509": {"1": "was advised", "2": "advises", "3": "advised", "4": "has advised", "answer": "has advised", "question": "During his 10 years with the firm, Mr. Martin ___ many financial institutions in Europe and Asia on strategy and mergers, acquisitions and alliances."}, "1510": {"1": "discussion", "2": "facility", "3": "agreement", "4": "publication", "answer": "facility", "question": "Funded by Hurricane Katrina money, the research ___ houses one million dollars worthy of lab equipment."}, "1511": {"1": "necessary", "2": "necessarily", "3": "necessitate", "4": "necessities", "answer": "necessary", "question": "It is ___ to attract attention by pricing products low enough to capture the interest of customers."}, "1512": {"1": "closely", "2": "vaguely", "3": "carefully", "4": "possibly", "answer": "carefully", "question": "Practice proper sanitation by ___ removing all infected plants as soon as possible."}, "1513": {"1": "donor", "2": "donates", "3": "donation", "4": "donated", "answer": "donation", "question": "Your generous ___ to the Global Conscience Initiative helps us further our mission to build a peace culture beyond borders."}, "1514": {"1": "Before", "2": "Yet", "3": "So that", "4": "Just as", "answer": "Before", "question": "___ actively seeking a specific web design, it is important that you are crystal clear on the goal of your website."}, "1515": {"1": "professionalism", "2": "professional", "3": "profession", "4": "professionally", "answer": "professionalism", "question": "A high sense of ___ often means individuals go well above the normal standard in various business situations."}, "1516": {"1": "interested", "2": "unprepared", "3": "exported", "4": "additional", "answer": "additional", "question": "Each passenger is usually given a 20Kg allowance and any baggage exceeding the designated weight will be charged an ___ fee."}, "1517": {"1": "has been led", "2": "have been led", "3": "has led", "4": "have led", "answer": "have led", "question": "Whether you ___ many discussions or are new to leading discussions, we trust that this guide will be helpful."}, "1518": {"1": "precise", "2": "equipped", "3": "assorted", "4": "estimated", "answer": "equipped", "question": "We have beautifully furnished apartments that are fully ___ with the latest appliances, and the electric bill is included in the rent."}, "1519": {"1": "is repairing", "2": "repairs", "3": "is being repaired", "4": "has repaired", "answer": "is being repaired", "question": "Alternative parking areas will be provided while the parking lot ___ ."}, "1520": {"1": "indications", "2": "perspectives", "3": "depths", "4": "images", "answer": "images", "question": "In order to meet the needs of our evergrowing user population, we need a broad diversity of ___ in the creation of our products."}, "1521": {"1": "fascinate", "2": "fascinating", "3": "fascination", "4": "fascinated", "answer": "fascinating", "question": "In a___ interview, The Jamaica Observer spoke with an anonymous manufacturer who was forced to retire."}, "1522": {"1": "as if", "2": "when", "3": "unless", "4": "because", "answer": "unless", "question": "The TV company is also preparing to cancel foreign channels ___ advertisers agree to substantial discounts."}, "1523": {"1": "nevertheless", "2": "since", "3": "regarding", "4": "except", "answer": "except", "question": "Make sure no one ___ you can access your computer while you are away from it!"}, "1524": {"1": "array", "2": "alleviation", "3": "origin", "4": "extension", "answer": "array", "question": "The marketers make an ___ of products that appeal to a wide variety of potential customers."}, "1525": {"1": "irrelevant", "2": "surplus", "3": "optional", "4": "urgent", "answer": "urgent", "question": "Due to ___ need, applications will be reviewed on a daily basis and candidates may be interviewed and positions filled before the closing date."}, "1526": {"1": "Invite", "2": "Invitations", "3": "Inviting", "4": "Invitation", "answer": "Invitations", "question": "___ for the money management seminar will be forwarded to all the managers tomorrow."}, "1527": {"1": "whole", "2": "inclusive", "3": "exceptional", "4": "multiple", "answer": "exceptional", "question": "The employee-of-the-year prizes will be awarded to employees who demonstrated ___ contribution to the company's overall sales."}, "1528": {"1": "their", "2": "they", "3": "themselves", "4": "theirs", "answer": "their", "question": "Those who have questions concerning fringe benefits are advised to consult ___ employee handbook."}, "1529": {"1": "description", "2": "attention", "3": "information", "4": "mistake", "answer": "description", "question": "The summary contains not only a technical ___ but also solutions to adverse effects of urban renewal developments."}, "1530": {"1": "variety", "2": "variably", "3": "variation", "4": "various", "answer": "various", "question": "The conference's keynote speaker addressed ___ impacts of digital technology on the current music industry."}, "1531": {"1": "relatively", "2": "slightly", "3": "usually", "4": "vaguely", "answer": "usually", "question": "Documents with a secret nature are ___ retained in each director's safety deposit box."}, "1532": {"1": "see", "2": "seen", "3": "seeing", "4": "has seen", "answer": "has seen", "question": "The fitness club ___ a steadily increasing number of customers and is eager to develop new programs."}, "1533": {"1": "overall", "2": "successful", "3": "wealthy", "4": "delighted", "answer": "successful", "question": "The job fair held in the City Center last week is considered the most ___ one so far, with over 3, people in attendance."}, "1534": {"1": "develops", "2": "developing", "3": "development", "4": "developed", "answer": "development", "question": "The effects of affordable housing ___ in rural areas will be discussed at the conference."}, "1535": {"1": "on", "2": "between", "3": "by", "4": "except", "answer": "by", "question": "Because the annual budget report must be submitted ___ the end of the month, employees are busy calculating figures."}, "1536": {"1": "leave", "2": "leaving", "3": "to leave", "4": "have left", "answer": "leave", "question": "Even though assigned tasks are somewhat complex, we will have to complete them before we ___ for the day."}, "1537": {"1": "practice", "2": "rewind", "3": "record", "4": "attend", "answer": "record", "question": "All workers are required to use the sheet provided to ___ their working hours and have their manager sign the form to verify the hours at the end of each day."}, "1538": {"1": "resisting", "2": "resistant", "3": "resisted", "4": "resistance", "answer": "resistance", "question": "Even if residents in the area have shown strong ___ to the project, the city government may not be hesitant to proceed with it."}, "1539": {"1": "following", "2": "more than", "3": "because", "4": "unless", "answer": "because", "question": "The team members have the same opinions on the matter ___ they shared the same information."}, "1540": {"1": "they", "2": "them", "3": "their", "4": "those", "answer": "their", "question": "The two divisions have unveiled ___ plan to set aside millions of dollars to invest in a very lucrative field."}, "1541": {"1": "Otherwise", "2": "Despite", "3": "Regarding", "4": "Although", "answer": "Although", "question": "___ proficiency in German would be of much help, it is not a requirement for the advertised position."}, "1542": {"1": "fortunate", "2": "fortunes", "3": "fortune", "4": "fortunately", "answer": "fortunately", "question": "We had to spend the whole month searching for better solutions, and ___ customers were impressed by our efforts."}, "1543": {"1": "involved", "2": "agreed", "3": "announced", "4": "maintained", "answer": "announced", "question": "The purchasing department ___ the drastic changes to the purchasing practice with outside suppliers."}, "1544": {"1": "If", "2": "Should", "3": "Whether", "4": "As though", "answer": "Should", "question": "___ anyone wish to access the information on the status of his or her order, the password should be entered."}, "1545": {"1": "destinations", "2": "treatments", "3": "goals", "4": "opinions", "answer": "goals", "question": "The ___ of the internship program are to help job seekers strengthen their professional skills and make them suitable for careers they are looking for."}, "1546": {"1": "impression", "2": "impress", "3": "impresses", "4": "impressed", "answer": "impressed", "question": "The more we spent with the sales team, the more ___ we were with their innovative marketing skills."}, "1547": {"1": "Whether", "2": "Since", "3": "For", "4": "Which", "answer": "Since", "question": "___ none of the participants has showed any interest, numerous outdoor activities have to be cancelled."}, "1548": {"1": "who", "2": "when", "3": "what", "4": "whom", "answer": "who", "question": "Customers ___ wish to return merchandise within 7 days of purchase must present the valid receipt to the store."}, "1549": {"1": "precaution", "2": "advice", "3": "rule", "4": "idea", "answer": "precaution", "question": "All laboratory employees make it a point to take every ___ to avoid potential hazards."}, "1550": {"1": "appropriate", "2": "appropriateness", "3": "appropriately", "4": "most appropriately", "answer": "appropriate", "question": "The manager said that it is ___ to test emergency equipment frequently to avoid any malfunction."}, "1551": {"1": "detain", "2": "associate", "3": "conduct", "4": "foresee", "answer": "conduct", "question": "It is necessary to ___ a thorough survey in order for us to obtain highly desirable sites for our new headquarters."}, "1552": {"1": "nearly", "2": "off", "3": "close", "4": "about", "answer": "about", "question": "Ms. Walters was ___ to make a presentation on how to increase revenue when I entered the room."}, "1553": {"1": "favorable", "2": "routine", "3": "sincere", "4": "recent", "answer": "routine", "question": "Mr. Lee takes care of several ___ tasks, such as sorting papers and filing documents in the cabinet."}, "1554": {"1": "Due to", "2": "While", "3": "In that", "4": "In case", "answer": "Due to", "question": "___ her hard work and commitment to the company, Ms. Ramirez was promoted to the head of the public relations department."}, "1555": {"1": "origin", "2": "original", "3": "originally", "4": "originated", "answer": "originally", "question": "The unexpected operating complexity was more serious than ___ anticipated."}, "1556": {"1": "rise", "2": "arisen", "3": "rose", "4": "rising", "answer": "rising", "question": "Due to ___ fuel prices, the company has decided to add a surcharge to all deliveries."}, "1557": {"1": "regularly", "2": "quickly", "3": "softly", "4": "tiredly", "answer": "quickly", "question": "As the company's strongest competitor released a new line of fall clothing, NTR Inc. moved ___ to introduce its new leather jackets."}, "1558": {"1": "propose", "2": "proposed", "3": "proposes", "4": "proposing", "answer": "proposed", "question": "The enclosed documents summarize ___ changes to the existing overtime regulations."}, "1559": {"1": "In spite of", "2": "Prior to", "3": "However", "4": "Yet", "answer": "In spite of", "question": "___ regular inspections, accidental system problems arise from time to time."}, "1560": {"1": "compare", "2": "compared", "3": "comparable", "4": "comparing", "answer": "comparable", "question": "Applicants must possess a master of business administration or ___ experience in a related field."}, "1561": {"1": "abbreviated", "2": "terminated", "3": "scheduled", "4": "postponed", "answer": "postponed", "question": "The recruitment advertising meeting that was scheduled for tomorrow has been ___ until next week."}, "1562": {"1": "probabilities", "2": "probability", "3": "probable", "4": "probably", "answer": "probably", "question": "The expansion of the natural history museum is most ___ the cause of significant revenue increases."}, "1563": {"1": "into", "2": "throughout", "3": "on", "4": "as", "answer": "throughout", "question": "Information on events occurring in the theater ___ the year is available through our website."}, "1564": {"1": "accommodation", "2": "policy", "3": "handling", "4": "measure", "answer": "policy", "question": "The library has announced a new ___ that all borrowed books must be returned 5 business days from the checkout date."}, "1565": {"1": "he", "2": "him", "3": "his", "4": "himself", "answer": "himself", "question": "Mr. Kurt Spienza appears to be the only person in our team who can finish the survey by ___ ."}, "1566": {"1": "will be", "2": "was", "3": "are", "4": "has been", "answer": "will be", "question": "All the storage rooms are scheduled to undergo renovations and ___ closed for several days next week."}, "1567": {"1": "directly", "2": "direct", "3": "directed", "4": "direction", "answer": "directly", "question": "Many science majors enter graduate school ___ after completing a bachelor of science degree."}, "1568": {"1": "reply", "2": "detect", "3": "construct", "4": "hire", "answer": "hire", "question": "Many companies interviewed plan to ___ more personnel, while 20 percent expect to reduce their payrolls."}, "1569": {"1": "they", "2": "them", "3": "themselves", "4": "their", "answer": "them", "question": "It seems that laborers in underdeveloped countries would rather have their children help ___ at work than enroll them in school."}, "1570": {"1": "issue", "2": "condition", "3": "price", "4": "promise", "answer": "issue", "question": "A new approach to information asset protection will be covered in the forthcoming March ___ of the magazine."}, "1571": {"1": "additional", "2": "addition", "3": "adding", "4": "additionally", "answer": "additional", "question": "Customers who purchase more than  dollars worth of items can request an HDTV cable box at no ___ charge."}, "1572": {"1": "They", "2": "It", "3": "There", "4": "That", "answer": "There", "question": "___ remain complicated economic problems to be resolved, while the economic conditions have been good."}, "1573": {"1": "repeat", "2": "repeatedly", "3": "repeater", "4": "repetition", "answer": "repeatedly", "question": "Mr. Garry Noxon in accounting was ___ warned about having too many numerical errors in the budget report."}, "1574": {"1": "interested", "2": "listed", "3": "hopeful", "4": "enclosed", "answer": "interested", "question": "Employers ___ in obtaining information concerning grants for technician certification may contact us at the e-mail address below."}, "1575": {"1": "survey", "2": "surveys", "3": "surveying", "4": "surveyed", "answer": "surveys", "question": "According to many ___ of the industry, the majority of small-sized firms are hoping to enter into lucrative businesses."}, "1576": {"1": "extremely", "2": "exclusively", "3": "continually", "4": "completely", "answer": "completely", "question": "During the one-week promotional period, we offer all the visitors and customers 1O dollars worth of kitchen appliances ___ free of charge."}, "1577": {"1": "informative", "2": "inform", "3": "information", "4": "informer", "answer": "informative", "question": "The first step in preparing a fairly ___ presentation is to do your research thoroughly on your topic."}, "1578": {"1": "Yet", "2": "Meanwhile", "3": "But", "4": "Although", "answer": "Although", "question": "___ understaffed and under tight budget,  centers are struggling to adequately provide emergency assistance to the citizens."}, "1579": {"1": "are required", "2": "require", "3": "requires", "4": "has required", "answer": "are required", "question": "Applicants for the managerial position ___ to possess high levels of motivation along with basic computer skills."}, "1580": {"1": "only if", "2": "until", "3": "not only", "4": "since", "answer": "only if", "question": "The applications submitted will be accepted ___ accompanied by photo identification."}, "1581": {"1": "attendant", "2": "attendance", "3": "attended", "4": "attendee", "answer": "attendance", "question": "It is likely that ___ of the annual conference will reach an all-time high this year, with more than 1, people planning to attend."}, "1582": {"1": "proficient", "2": "considerable", "3": "secondary", "4": "present", "answer": "considerable", "question": "Despite ___ efforts and partial success for the last few years, the unemployment rate is still on the rise."}, "1583": {"1": "maintaining", "2": "maintenance", "3": "maintained", "4": "maintains", "answer": "maintenance", "question": "A detailed quotation on the ongoing ___ will be provided for free any time upon request."}, "1584": {"1": "demonstrate", "2": "decline", "3": "face", "4": "ease", "answer": "ease", "question": "Attempts to ___ congestion during peak hours are being made, but seem to prove unfruitful at the moment."}, "1585": {"1": "since", "2": "then", "3": "here", "4": "much", "answer": "then", "question": "All the important files were organized first by color and ___ alphabetized by title and name,"}, "1586": {"1": "against", "2": "except", "3": "upon", "4": "throughout", "answer": "throughout", "question": "Pedestrians and motorists are advised to obey the traffic signs posted ___ Blackroad."}, "1587": {"1": "requests", "2": "request", "3": "requesting", "4": "requested", "answer": "requests", "question": "The customer service department is responsible tor fulfilling ___ from the public and has to forward them to the chief financial officer."}, "1588": {"1": "suited", "2": "conductive", "3": "forward", "4": "prior", "answer": "prior", "question": "Editors are extremely busy proofreading, editing and compiling materials ___ to publication date."}, "1589": {"1": "weaken", "2": "invalidate", "3": "verify", "4": "weigh", "answer": "invalidate", "question": "Customers have the right to ___ the order within 5 business days from the delivery of the product without providing reasons tor the cancellation."}, "1590": {"1": "as expensive", "2": "more expensive", "3": "so expensively", "4": "most expensively", "answer": "more expensive", "question": "As health care becomes ___ than it was a decade ago, companies are forced to spend more on benefits."}, "1591": {"1": "extension", "2": "production", "3": "grade", "4": "rise", "answer": "rise", "question": "The report on existing home sales showed an unexpected ___ in sales last year, but the number of unsold homes has increased."}, "1592": {"1": "will overcome", "2": "be overcome", "3": "to overcome", "4": "has overcome", "answer": "to overcome", "question": "Many researchers are doing research on how to reduce the time it takes ___ and forget an accident."}, "1593": {"1": "budget", "2": "prices", "3": "credits", "4": "expenses", "answer": "expenses", "question": "Accommodation costs and living ___ will vary, depending on individual requirements and work locations."}, "1594": {"1": "has presented", "2": "presenting", "3": "present", "4": "to present", "answer": "to present", "question": "Speakers should be prepared ___ their findings to the audience and be able to answer questions regarding them."}, "1595": {"1": "fallen", "2": "refused", "3": "performed", "4": "acquired", "answer": "fallen", "question": "As real estate prices have ___ dramatically in recent years, buyers have cancelled new-home contracts."}, "1596": {"1": "elevation", "2": "mobility", "3": "belief", "4": "popularity", "answer": "popularity", "question": "For years, domestically produced movies have been gaining ___ among people of all ages."}, "1597": {"1": "to", "2": "by", "3": "on", "4": "for", "answer": "to", "question": "They are required to inform the human resources department when resigning due ___ a disagreement over company policy."}, "1598": {"1": "practice", "2": "persist", "3": "cooperate", "4": "retain", "answer": "retain", "question": "No matter how drastically you revise your book, you must include photos of an artwork that you want to ___ from the previous edition."}, "1599": {"1": "exclusive", "2": "excluding", "3": "exclusively", "4": "excluded", "answer": "exclusively", "question": "Employees will be given bonuses and incentives ___ depending on their performance achievements, not based on their relationship with supervisors."}, "1600": {"1": "facing", "2": "progressing", "3": "playing", "4": "dealing", "answer": "facing", "question": "The internal audit is going to identify operational and financial risks our company is ___ at the moment."}, "1601": {"1": "Despite", "2": "Unless", "3": "In order to", "4": "As well as", "answer": "Despite", "question": "___ inclement weather conditions, employees must arrive at the beginning of their work shift."}, "1602": {"1": "such", "2": "either", "3": "with", "4": "and", "answer": "and", "question": "Refreshments are arranged in the lobby ___ meals will be served shortly thereafter."}, "1603": {"1": "seek", "2": "seeking", "3": "have sought", "4": "being sought", "answer": "being sought", "question": "Donations ___ for the purchase of necessities will help provide a brighter holiday season to people in need."}, "1604": {"1": "corresponds", "2": "expects", "3": "details", "4": "prepares", "answer": "details", "question": "All the accountants are required to compile a report which ___ annual corporate spending."}, "1605": {"1": "easy", "2": "easier", "3": "easily", "4": "easiness", "answer": "easily", "question": "You can ___ rebuild your credit by taking steps to repair your credit rating as soon as possible."}, "1606": {"1": "use", "2": "add", "3": "change", "4": "differ", "answer": "change", "question": "The company announced plans to ___ its corporate name to BATEL, Inc. for marketing and commercial purposes."}, "1607": {"1": "information", "2": "inform", "3": "informing", "4": "informed", "answer": "information", "question": "Make sure you provide the requested ___ when submitting advertising proposals since incomplete ones will not be accepted."}, "1608": {"1": "I", "2": "my", "3": "me", "4": "mine", "answer": "my", "question": "Thank you for offering me a position with the company I wish to work for, and I really appreciate the efforts you've made on ___ behalf."}, "1609": {"1": "broad", "2": "high", "3": "proud", "4": "round", "answer": "broad", "question": "The ideal candidate should not only perform well under tight deadline pressure but also have a ___ familiarity with technical standards."}, "1610": {"1": "promotes", "2": "promote", "3": "promoting", "4": "promoted", "answer": "promoting", "question": "People are aware of the importance of ___ physical activities which have a significant impact on reducing childhood obesity and chronic disease."}, "1611": {"1": "initially", "2": "originally", "3": "primarily", "4": "numerically", "answer": "primarily", "question": "Over the past three months, employees have been working ___ with support staff to accomplish their goals, working an average of eight hours per day."}, "1612": {"1": "critic", "2": "critically", "3": "critical", "4": "criticism", "answer": "critical", "question": "While smokers are highly ___ of the ban on smoking in workplaces, most nonsmokers support the ban."}, "1613": {"1": "or else", "2": "besides", "3": "on account of", "4": "either", "answer": "or else", "question": "All the forms you submit must be postmarked no later than the specified date ___ they will be considered untimely."}, "1614": {"1": "regulate", "2": "regulating", "3": "regulates", "4": "is regulated", "answer": "regulate", "question": "It looks like directors of the corporate finance division ___ the details of managerial compensation contracts."}, "1615": {"1": "knowledge", "2": "opinion", "3": "ability", "4": "collector", "answer": "knowledge", "question": "As a financial planner, Mr. Martin has a comprehensive ___ of the legal process, as well as financial and tax issues."}, "1616": {"1": "enthusiastic", "2": "serious", "3": "pertinent", "4": "appreciative", "answer": "pertinent", "question": "If you send the ___ information, I'll drop by your area to look for suitable housing."}, "1617": {"1": "which", "2": "in case", "3": "when", "4": "in order that", "answer": "when", "question": "Buses in the metropolitan area are rarely on schedule ___ traffic is busy and hectic."}, "1618": {"1": "ordinarily", "2": "currently", "3": "commonly", "4": "lately", "answer": "currently", "question": "We are ___ considering a wide variety of potential applicants, so please fill out your background information accurately."}, "1619": {"1": "in", "2": "of", "3": "at", "4": "for", "answer": "in", "question": "If you plan to rent equipment, delivery and collection times, plus insurance coverage for any damage should all be dealt with ___ advance."}, "1620": {"1": "Lengthy", "2": "Opportune", "3": "Surplus", "4": "Brief", "answer": "Surplus", "question": "___ parts stored in the warehouse may be procured at special sale prices, which are negotiable."}, "1621": {"1": "supported", "2": "supporter", "3": "supporting", "4": "support", "answer": "support", "question": "You can reach us either by phone or e-mail when you need technical ___ or have any questions about the product you purchased."}, "1622": {"1": "improper", "2": "reserved", "3": "extinct", "4": "anxious", "answer": "improper", "question": "Any ___ transaction or violations of the policy must be reported to your immediate supervisor."}, "1623": {"1": "changed", "2": "change", "3": "changes", "4": "changing", "answer": "changes", "question": "After hours of debate, the Review Committee created a list of ___ to the proposal drafted by administrators."}, "1624": {"1": "extend", "2": "extended", "3": "to extend", "4": "extension", "answer": "extended", "question": "I want to express my appreciation again for courtesies you and your staff have ___ to me."}, "1625": {"1": "exercises", "2": "exercising", "3": "exercised", "4": "exercise", "answer": "exercise", "question": "In recent years, most companies have been favoring rigid criteria systems that require employees to ___ discretion."}, "1626": {"1": "interests", "2": "benefits", "3": "forces", "4": "momentums", "answer": "benefits", "question": "According to many reports, the ___ of laughter range from lowering stress levels to boosting your immune system."}, "1627": {"1": "at", "2": "over", "3": "across", "4": "during", "answer": "at", "question": "Many branch offices were established in the suburbs 1Oyears ago, ___ which time the volume of traffic was also steadily increasing."}, "1628": {"1": "forwards", "2": "forward", "3": "forwarding", "4": "to forward", "answer": "forward", "question": "Please ___ any information, no matter how insufficient it may seem, to your client in the very near future."}, "1629": {"1": "availability", "2": "status", "3": "usage", "4": "technique", "answer": "technique", "question": "Any discarded electronic device can be recycled less harmfully, using an effective ___ developed by researchers."}, "1630": {"1": "when", "2": "where", "3": "in that", "4": "in it", "answer": "where", "question": "The Victoria Hotel, ___ we stayed during our summer vacation, will be torn down for extensive renovations."}, "1631": {"1": "except", "2": "next to", "3": "onto", "4": "until", "answer": "until", "question": "We are not happy to announce that due to recent cutbacks on members, we won't be able to accept new projects ___ further notice."}, "1632": {"1": "well", "2": "soon", "3": "already", "4": "never", "answer": "already", "question": "As most of the conference sessions are ___ fully booked, people are encouraged to find alternatives from other seminars."}, "1633": {"1": "economic", "2": "economically", "3": "economist", "4": "economy", "answer": "economic", "question": "The agreed-upon ___ sanctions are not limited to tariffs, trade barriers, and import or export quotas imposed on individual countries."}, "1634": {"1": "reviewed", "2": "searched", "3": "advised", "4": "reached", "answer": "reviewed", "question": "The proposed compensation plans have been ___ and will be amended to comply with new rules."}, "1635": {"1": "substantiate", "2": "substantially", "3": "substance", "4": "substantial", "answer": "substantial", "question": "The unions requested that they be offered ___ pay increases equaling about 40, dollars a year."}, "1636": {"1": "yours", "2": "your", "3": "yourself", "4": "your own", "answer": "yourself", "question": "The website sponsored by the city monitoring committee will help you protect ___ against Internet threats."}, "1637": {"1": "emerge", "2": "persist", "3": "endure", "4": "prolong", "answer": "prolong", "question": "Maintenance checks are regularly conducted to ___ the life of sophisticated equipment at the company's expense."}, "1638": {"1": "so much", "2": "sure", "3": "especially", "4": "particular", "answer": "especially", "question": "The new aquarium scheduled to be constructed in the center of town will be ___ attractive to people who have young children."}, "1639": {"1": "removed", "2": "replaced", "3": "sent", "4": "stored", "answer": "removed", "question": "We are sorry to tell you that your name will be ___ from our mailing list since we have not yet received your payment."}, "1640": {"1": "over", "2": "behind", "3": "from", "4": "out of", "answer": "from", "question": "This notice provides general guidance on how you can obtain the best available information ___ other sources."}, "1641": {"1": "choose", "2": "choice", "3": "choices", "4": "chose", "answer": "choice", "question": "You will have a full week at the resort of your ___ , departing on July 20 and arriving back in Tokyo on July 26."}, "1642": {"1": "Until", "2": "Despite", "3": "Although", "4": "Otherwise", "answer": "Although", "question": "___ inexperienced, individuals with the willingness to learn will make a difference in the foreseeable future."}, "1643": {"1": "toward", "2": "due", "3": "by", "4": "when", "answer": "by", "question": "It was likely that the results of our study were heavily influenced ___ individual experience and skills participants had, according to the report."}, "1644": {"1": "always", "2": "usually", "3": "still", "4": "yet", "answer": "still", "question": "Even if education is theoretically free of charge, parents ___ have to pay the increasingly high cost of school clothing, books, materials and transport costs."}, "1645": {"1": "us", "2": "ours", "3": "ourselves", "4": "our", "answer": "our", "question": "Considering the failure of ___ system to offer adequate support, we might have to provide refunds to our customers."}, "1646": {"1": "under", "2": "about", "3": "along", "4": "into", "answer": "about", "question": "Some managers are supposed to meet each other at the end of the month to talk ___ their monthly performance reviews."}, "1647": {"1": "growth", "2": "grows", "3": "grown", "4": "grower", "answer": "growth", "question": "There's another piece of evidence that there has been enormous ___ in the supply of customized services to customers."}, "1648": {"1": "competes", "2": "competitively", "3": "competitive", "4": "competition", "answer": "competition", "question": "Our aim is to increase the efficiency of the rail services both for freight and passengers by providing services on the network and increasing ___ among companies."}, "1649": {"1": "where", "2": "while", "3": "from", "4": "wherever", "answer": "from", "question": "People can obtain information ___ an article containing several cases of the implementation of the new technology and its impact."}, "1650": {"1": "Moreover", "2": "Because", "3": "Therefore", "4": "Nevertheless", "answer": "Because", "question": "___ we are under a tight deadline on product delivery, we will have to ask for assistance from other departments."}, "1651": {"1": "accepts", "2": "accepting", "3": "accept", "4": "accepted", "answer": "accept", "question": "We are sorry to announce that we will not ___ any credit cards starting next year since a cash deposit is required."}, "1652": {"1": "on", "2": "by", "3": "with", "4": "to", "answer": "on", "question": "The chairperson was trying to curtail a lengthy, heated discussion ___ the merits of work ethics due to the time constraint."}, "1653": {"1": "difficult", "2": "difficulty", "3": "more difficult", "4": "much difficult", "answer": "more difficult", "question": "Many on-line retailers state that it is ___ than they expected to set prices that attract more customers while boosting their profit margins."}, "1654": {"1": "total", "2": "product", "3": "registration", "4": "summary", "answer": "summary", "question": "Enclosed is a ___ of the company's current activities and future plans, so read it carefully and leave your comments on it."}, "1655": {"1": "was", "2": "were", "3": "is", "4": "are", "answer": "was", "question": "The revised version of an unpublished manuscript ___ due to arrive this morning at 10 o'clock, but unexpected problems delayed the shipping."}, "1656": {"1": "According to", "2": "Future", "3": "However", "4": "Instead of", "answer": "Instead of", "question": "___ searching for long-term economic growth, the government intends to study immediate solutions to avoid severe criticism from the public."}, "1657": {"1": "other", "2": "others", "3": "the other", "4": "another", "answer": "others", "question": "The company you work for is willing to take advantage of new technology, but ___ are concerned about adverse consequences."}, "1658": {"1": "reasonably", "2": "thoroughly", "3": "gratefully", "4": "virtually", "answer": "reasonably", "question": "The renovated French restaurant next to the post office attracted more customers as a result of its ___ priced, various food selections."}, "1659": {"1": "convenience", "2": "convenient", "3": "conveniently", "4": "conveniences", "answer": "conveniently", "question": "The elegant hotel known for its fabulous amenities is ___ located near the local airport."}, "1660": {"1": "attendance", "2": "sight", "3": "provision", "4": "supervision", "answer": "supervision", "question": "The launch of new software programs has been under the ___ of Mr. Lopez, who's famous for his dedication to the company."}, "1661": {"1": "who", "2": "anyone", "3": "whose", "4": "whichever", "answer": "who", "question": "Emma Jean, ___ was nominated for an Employee of the Month Award for her exceptional work performance, will deliver a speech this evening."}, "1662": {"1": "prepared", "2": "consumed", "3": "revised", "4": "replaced", "answer": "replaced", "question": "Our policy guarantees that any damaged products incurred in transit will be ___ immediately with new ones, or a full refund will be issued."}, "1663": {"1": "develop", "2": "revise", "3": "achieve", "4": "contribute", "answer": "develop", "question": "The planning officer was struggling to get a permit to ___ a residential area, which can easily cost a billion dollars even before the expense of buying the land."}, "1664": {"1": "limited", "2": "former", "3": "confidential", "4": "mandatory", "answer": "confidential", "question": "The chief executive officer is obligated to retain all the information of a ___ nature in relation to negotiations."}, "1665": {"1": "far", "2": "well", "3": "good", "4": "near", "answer": "well", "question": "Service occupations are prevalent in all sectors of the economy, such as in manufacturing as ___ as in the service sector."}, "1666": {"1": "enter", "2": "place", "3": "offer", "4": "create", "answer": "enter", "question": "Those individuals who want to gain automatic access to the information are advised to ___ the password that was sent to them by phone."}, "1667": {"1": "completely", "2": "completed", "3": "completing", "4": "complete", "answer": "complete", "question": "The newly appointed vice president is expected to earn the ___ trust of employees despite all indications to the contrary."}, "1668": {"1": "close", "2": "hold", "3": "wait", "4": "meet", "answer": "hold", "question": "The board of directors will ___ a regular employment session next Monday September 16th at 10 a.m. in the board room."}, "1669": {"1": "mistook", "2": "mistake", "3": "mistaken", "4": "mistakenly", "answer": "mistakenly", "question": "Many financial specialists ___ predicted that industries might encounter a decline in manufacturing investment in  by almost 15 percent."}, "1670": {"1": "Following", "2": "Except", "3": "Upon", "4": "At", "answer": "Following", "question": "___ months of tough negotiations, it was announced this morning that an agreement had finally been reached."}, "1671": {"1": "himself", "2": "herself", "3": "itself", "4": "themselves", "answer": "themselves", "question": "Our skilled and experienced service representatives will be able to resolve any problems you might encounter by ___ ."}, "1672": {"1": "sensitive", "2": "competitive", "3": "affordable", "4": "courteous", "answer": "sensitive", "question": "All employees should be informed explicitly of their responsibilities in relation to ___ client information."}, "1673": {"1": "approving", "2": "approved", "3": "approval", "4": "approves", "answer": "approval", "question": "Much of the expected boost in revenue is related to a transaction tax which has yet to receive final ___ from Congress."}, "1674": {"1": "hopefully", "2": "highly", "3": "probably", "4": "rarely", "answer": "highly", "question": "Since the corporate system has a ___ structured daily schedule, it would be nearly impossible to impair the work efficiency."}, "1675": {"1": "treating", "2": "has treated", "3": "treated", "4": "to treat", "answer": "to treat", "question": "In an effort ___ customers with respect we have changed our hours to accommodate customer needs."}, "1676": {"1": "infrequent", "2": "additional", "3": "ongoing", "4": "incidental", "answer": "additional", "question": "The local government is planning to construct ___ performing arts facilities in order to meet the cultural needs of the population."}, "1677": {"1": "reformed", "2": "reformer", "3": "reforms", "4": "reformatory", "answer": "reforms", "question": "The appointment of Mr. Murphy as prime minister was intended to accelerate the proposed economic ___ without any hesitation."}, "1678": {"1": "unfavorable", "2": "unwilling", "3": "opposing", "4": "reluctant", "answer": "unfavorable", "question": "Even though Peterson Group Inc. is one of the largest automobile manufacturing companies, it has yet to see any profits as a result of ___ market conditions."}, "1679": {"1": "are disappearing", "2": "will have disappeared", "3": "had disappeared", "4": "disappear", "answer": "had disappeared", "question": "When I closed the window, all of the files and folders on my desktop computer ___ except for the icon."}, "1680": {"1": "grade", "2": "feet", "3": "point", "4": "spot", "answer": "point", "question": "Mr. Conner's remarks concerning the results of last year's declining sales were concise and to the ___ ."}, "1681": {"1": "motivate", "2": "motivator", "3": "motivated", "4": "motivation", "answer": "motivated", "question": "Can-Do Engineering is searching for creative, ___ people who can produce excellent quality work that goes beyond customer expectations."}, "1682": {"1": "in spite of", "2": "so as", "3": "despite", "4": "though", "answer": "though", "question": "We want you to be aware that we're doing our utmost, ___ we will not be able to provide you with a personalized experience on our website."}, "1683": {"1": "expecting", "2": "expected", "3": "expects", "4": "expect", "answer": "expected", "question": "A new innovative program is ___ to be released, though some system failures happened at the beginning of the inspection."}, "1684": {"1": "occasionally", "2": "prematurely", "3": "marginally", "4": "uncommonly", "answer": "occasionally", "question": "Milky Cookies ___ enters into a contract with a third party vendor in order to fulfill its business operations."}, "1685": {"1": "or", "2": "neither", "3": "nor", "4": "both", "answer": "or", "question": "If you want to purchase a lower priced ticket, either contact us through regular mail ___ call our hotline and then we will send you an application immediately."}, "1686": {"1": "signing", "2": "signed", "3": "signature", "4": "to sign", "answer": "signature", "question": "In order to brand your business, you'd better include your ___ in every letter you send to customers, which helps remind them of whom they do business with."}, "1687": {"1": "deposited", "2": "predicted", "3": "operated", "4": "appointed", "answer": "appointed", "question": "We are proud to announce that Dax Shepard has been ___ as our new managing director to oversee corporate expansion in Europe."}, "1688": {"1": "suggested", "2": "suggesting", "3": "suggest", "4": "suggestion", "answer": "suggested", "question": "The general manager has ___ that any information customers enter be used only to respond to their inquiries and requests."}, "1689": {"1": "spectators", "2": "witnesses", "3": "participants", "4": "subscribers", "answer": "subscribers", "question": "This list is comprised of thousands of ___ to various magazines, including computers, automobiles, garments and electronics."}, "1690": {"1": "extend", "2": "extensive", "3": "extent", "4": "extension", "answer": "extensive", "question": "Additional information on ___ financial aid such as grants and scholarships can be obtained from career offices at each university."}, "1691": {"1": "conveniently", "2": "correctly", "3": "greatly", "4": "widely", "answer": "conveniently", "question": "We are opening a fully renovated condominium ___ located in a quiet setting, and complete with many amenities."}, "1692": {"1": "Competitively", "2": "Competition", "3": "Competitive", "4": "Competes", "answer": "Competition", "question": "___ for reconstruction contracts has been getting stiffer over the years since it can generate enormously lucrative earnings."}, "1693": {"1": "support", "2": "achieve", "3": "purchase", "4": "replace", "answer": "purchase", "question": "Many people were standing in line outside of the box office to ___ a limited number of low-cost tickets, which are offered as specials each month."}, "1694": {"1": "totally", "2": "total", "3": "totaled", "4": "totaling", "answer": "totally", "question": "The article provides readers with tips on how to get ___ out of debt by setting financial goals and eliminating unnecessary spending."}, "1695": {"1": "Like", "2": "Once", "3": "Unless", "4": "Despite", "answer": "Once", "question": "___ all the alterations to the plan have been approved, they should be submitted to the appropriate office no later than the end of the month."}, "1696": {"1": "herself", "2": "he", "3": "hers", "4": "she", "answer": "herself", "question": "Ms. Cordova was struggling to successfully complete the ta~k assigned to her by ___ ."}, "1697": {"1": "invests", "2": "invested", "3": "investing", "4": "invest", "answer": "investing", "question": "The general hospital was able to improve patient care significantly without hiring more staff by ___ in a new information system."}, "1698": {"1": "through", "2": "behind", "3": "above", "4": "except", "answer": "through", "question": "Automakers are recovering from weak results ___ a series of complicated restructuring processes, and experiencing increased revenues and profits as a result."}, "1699": {"1": "accident", "2": "accidental", "3": "accidents", "4": "accidentally", "answer": "accidentally", "question": "Our experienced and skilled technicians can be of much help in the event that you ___ delete something essential from the program."}, "1700": {"1": "to work", "2": "works", "3": "be working", "4": "will work", "answer": "to work", "question": "Most companies like all their employees ___ on innovative products and to believe passionately in their mission."}, "1701": {"1": "practice", "2": "reference", "3": "plot", "4": "resource", "answer": "practice", "question": "Researching an employer's organizational structure, products, services and reputation is a highly recommended ___ for those preparing for job interviews."}, "1702": {"1": "upon", "2": "without", "3": "until", "4": "along", "answer": "without", "question": "Under no circumstances may you copy or distribute any secret information ___ appropriate written permission from us."}, "1703": {"1": "concerning", "2": "over", "3": "so", "4": "since", "answer": "so", "question": "It .is important to look through the documents ___ that everyone in charge can know at which stage they should be completed."}, "1704": {"1": "throughout", "2": "from", "3": "about", "4": "between", "answer": "throughout", "question": "Most of the hotels have their own pool and sun terrace with a pool-side bar which serves drinks and snacks ___ the day."}, "1705": {"1": "proposing", "2": "propose", "3": "proposes", "4": "proposal", "answer": "proposal", "question": "When the ___ for this new safety policy was under consideration by the managers, a number of experts were asked for their comments."}, "1706": {"1": "unavailable", "2": "related", "3": "stylish", "4": "disinterested", "answer": "unavailable", "question": "We do apologize for the inconvenience resulting from the service which is now temporarily ___ ."}, "1707": {"1": "will provide", "2": "provide", "3": "providing", "4": "to provide", "answer": "will provide", "question": "The restaurant, closed for extensive renovations, assured customers that it ___ them with better-quality food and exceptional service."}, "1708": {"1": "consistently", "2": "steadily", "3": "sensibly", "4": "exactly", "answer": "consistently", "question": "Any employees who are ___ late or absent from work may be subject to disciplinary actions, regardless of their position."}, "1709": {"1": "ours", "2": "their", "3": "theirs", "4": "ourselves", "answer": "their", "question": "Most of the employees are entitled to a maximum of one hour for a lunch break, depending on ___ assigned work schedule."}, "1710": {"1": "affect", "2": "contain", "3": "fulfill", "4": "mention", "answer": "fulfill", "question": "Your personal information, including credit card numbers, mailing address, e-mail address and phone numbers, will be collected in order for us to ___ your order for products."}, "1711": {"1": "shopping", "2": "shoppers", "3": "to shop", "4": "shopper", "answer": "shoppers", "question": "A questionnaire asked ___ to evaluate the appearance and the overall brightness of the new merchandise."}, "1712": {"1": "complete", "2": "entire", "3": "whole", "4": "total", "answer": "complete", "question": "When the installation process is ___ and an \"OK\" screen appears on the computer, please remove the last CD and click \"reboot.\""}, "1713": {"1": "periodic", "2": "periodical", "3": "periodically", "4": "period", "answer": "periodically", "question": "All the workers are required to ___ verify that the proper maintenance of storage facilities is conducted with extreme care."}, "1714": {"1": "sale", "2": "place", "3": "advertisement", "4": "market", "answer": "market", "question": "The growing number of vacant housing units on the ___ for more than 6 months implies that excessive supply still exists."}, "1715": {"1": "spacing", "2": "spacious", "3": "spaciousness", "4": "spaces", "answer": "spacious", "question": "The elegant hotel we stayed at was ___ and bright and had a private entrance and patio with a view of the ocean."}, "1716": {"1": "Whether", "2": "According", "3": "In order", "4": "How", "answer": "In order", "question": "___ to focus resources and investment on this rapidly growing business, we have to make a strategic decision."}, "1717": {"1": "precisely", "2": "respectively", "3": "punctually", "4": "mutually", "answer": "mutually", "question": "We, one of the leading manufacturing companies, would like to build a ___ beneficial relationship with your esteemed company."}, "1718": {"1": "replacement", "2": "complaint", "3": "receipt", "4": "promotion", "answer": "replacement", "question": "Please read the terms and conditions carefully to determine whether or not you can request a refund or ___ for the p~oducts you ordered."}, "1719": {"1": "repeating", "2": "repetitive", "3": "repetition", "4": "repeat", "answer": "repetitive", "question": "Applicants are advised to fill out an application form concisely to impress potential employers, without being too ___ or boring."}, "1720": {"1": "as if", "2": "while", "3": "because", "4": "even though", "answer": "even though", "question": "Passengers will get to their destination on time ___ our departure time is a little late due to a mechanical problem."}, "1721": {"1": "misinterpret", "2": "misinterpretation", "3": "misinterpreted", "4": "misinterpreting", "answer": "misinterpreted", "question": "All the terms of the agreement must be clear so that the meaning and intent won't be ___ by either party."}, "1722": {"1": "now that", "2": "in case", "3": "therefore", "4": "otherwise", "answer": "therefore", "question": "People don't put much importance into a powerful marketing tool and ___ miss the opportunity to gain more potential customers."}, "1723": {"1": "for", "2": "next", "3": "while", "4": "onto", "answer": "for", "question": "The plans are under serious consideration ___ extension of better garbage collection, street maintenance and adequate sewage services into the province."}, "1724": {"1": "enlisted", "2": "opportune", "3": "international", "4": "appropriate", "answer": "appropriate", "question": "You'd better consider the factors that assess the effectiveness of the ___ training system and implement corrective actions in a timely manner."}, "1725": {"1": "positions", "2": "assignments", "3": "subscriptions", "4": "appointments", "answer": "appointments", "question": "Those individuals who want to reschedule their ___ with a doctor should contact us two days in advance."}, "1726": {"1": "their", "2": "theirs", "3": "they", "4": "them", "answer": "their", "question": "The report shows that builders reserve the right to control the volume of the construction project on ___ own."}, "1727": {"1": "cautious", "2": "distinguished", "3": "secure", "4": "strict", "answer": "secure", "question": "Information on customers' details can be stored on one diskette, as can the whole spreadsheet, and the diskettes can then be kept in a ___ place."}, "1728": {"1": "attends", "2": "attention", "3": "attended", "4": "attendant", "answer": "attention", "question": "Superb ___ has been paid to even the smallest detail, as the project was expected to cost billions of dollars."}, "1729": {"1": "so", "2": "nor", "3": "or", "4": "and", "answer": "or", "question": "Mr. Hatcher is now curious about the general opinion on the matter of formatting a standard ___ deluxe system instead of formatting a premiere one."}, "1730": {"1": "additions", "2": "additionally", "3": "additional", "4": "addition", "answer": "additional", "question": "If you need to hire ___ help for your growing business, our experts can assist with the hiring process from start to finish."}, "1731": {"1": "prevent", "2": "upgrade", "3": "ignore", "4": "improve", "answer": "prevent", "question": "Another computer system failure is going to happen again unless appropriate steps are taken to ___ it."}, "1732": {"1": "visit", "2": "visitations", "3": "visitors", "4": "visiting", "answer": "visitors", "question": "All ___ to our fabulous national park will be given a complimentary lunch at the top of the hill."}, "1733": {"1": "values", "2": "customs", "3": "refunds", "4": "expenses", "answer": "expenses", "question": "Once you've decided to reduce ___ , there should be additional ways to halve the marketing costs."}, "1734": {"1": "amaze", "2": "amazing", "3": "amazement", "4": "amazingly", "answer": "amazing", "question": "Paulin Cornwall Inc. has made an ___ discovery people can share in no time in the field of information technology."}, "1735": {"1": "beyond", "2": "until", "3": "that", "4": "but", "answer": "but", "question": "The first draft of workshop proposals was due yesterday, ___ the director has granted us a short extension to our surprise."}, "1736": {"1": "you", "2": "your", "3": "yourself", "4": "yours", "answer": "your", "question": "The company is going to carry out the proposal based on the information provided in your letter of intent, so please submit ___ application under this note."}, "1737": {"1": "lastly", "2": "at first", "3": "meanwhile", "4": "finally", "answer": "finally", "question": "After the introduction of collaboration tool programs, the company, which was in temporary financial trouble, was ___ able to increase its market share."}, "1738": {"1": "predicting", "2": "predicted", "3": "predictable", "4": "predictably", "answer": "predictable", "question": "Many people call fairy tales too ___ and obvious, but that's why they are needed."}, "1739": {"1": "only", "2": "easily", "3": "simply", "4": "merely", "answer": "only", "question": "New recycling programs indicate that ___ the landlord or the property owners may schedule an appointment to get bulk pickup service in the same building."}, "1740": {"1": "establish", "2": "establishing", "3": "establishes", "4": "established", "answer": "establishing", "question": "During the sessions, speakers will discuss the process of ___ a global service by opening doors to economic opportunities."}, "1741": {"1": "advise", "2": "urge", "3": "comply", "4": "submit", "answer": "submit", "question": "Please ___ your survey results to the director by the date specified at the bottom of the screen."}, "1742": {"1": "conduct", "2": "conducted", "3": "to conduct", "4": "will conduct", "answer": "conducted", "question": "OFA representatives recently ___ on-line tours and found those kinds of tours to promote their products the most effective."}, "1743": {"1": "provide", "2": "hesitate", "3": "qualify", "4": "compete", "answer": "hesitate", "question": "Please do not ___ to share your opinions in the comment space below so that people can find and consider possible alternatives."}, "1744": {"1": "regular", "2": "regularity", "3": "regularly", "4": "regulate", "answer": "regularly", "question": "Our GTA phone roaming service is suited for individuals who travel ___ anywhere in the world for business."}, "1745": {"1": "across", "2": "over", "3": "at", "4": "for", "answer": "for", "question": "A banquet was held for researchers to be honored ___ their exceptional achievements in creative research activities."}, "1746": {"1": "participation", "2": "participated", "3": "participating", "4": "participate", "answer": "participation", "question": "We are proud to announce their upcoming ___ in an event whose purpose is to educate attendees on e-mail management tools."}, "1747": {"1": "off", "2": "from", "3": "by", "4": "with", "answer": "with", "question": "Anyone who has questions concerning our community service can leave a message ___ my secretary or our answering service."}, "1748": {"1": "retailing", "2": "retail", "3": "retailer", "4": "retailed", "answer": "retail", "question": "Requirements for the open position include basic computer skills and managerial experience in ___ sales."}, "1749": {"1": "altogether", "2": "alone", "3": "also", "4": "almost", "answer": "also", "question": "According to the medical report released today, cholesterol fighting medicines may ___ have protective effects against numerous uncured diseases."}, "1750": {"1": "every", "2": "both", "3": "either", "4": "whether", "answer": "both", "question": "Employees who participate in this training program can learn a great deal about themselves as well as experience in ___ personal and profession growth."}, "1751": {"1": "increase", "2": "impression", "3": "access", "4": "accent", "answer": "increase", "question": "According to studies released yesterday, a significant number of organizations experienced a dramatic ___ in electronic crime and data intrusions over the past year."}, "1752": {"1": "regretting", "2": "regretted", "3": "regretfully", "4": "regretful", "answer": "regretfully", "question": "The president of Kasara Inc. ___ announced that Lopez Davis, who has served the company for more than 30 years, would retire at the end of next month."}, "1753": {"1": "remain", "2": "grant", "3": "serve", "4": "provide", "answer": "provide", "question": "The new training program is intended to ___ leadership to develop professional competence through involvement in a range of professional development activities."}, "1754": {"1": "to discontinue", "2": "will discontinue", "3": "discontinued", "4": "have discontinued", "answer": "will discontinue", "question": "Due to recent changes, Nordon Express ___ delivery of equipment effective the first day of the coming year."}, "1755": {"1": "before", "2": "until", "3": "from", "4": "during", "answer": "before", "question": "Employees must get approval from their supervisors ___ deleting data even if the data seem unused."}, "1756": {"1": "launched", "2": "launching", "3": "launch", "4": "launches", "answer": "launching", "question": "In addition to ___ a separate online site, new products will be available through traditional retailers all over the world."}, "1757": {"1": "intended", "2": "based", "3": "agreed", "4": "invited", "answer": "intended", "question": "Tomorrow's one-to-one training session held in a boardroom is ___ for supervisors and new staff members."}, "1758": {"1": "why", "2": "if", "3": "due to", "4": "about", "answer": "if", "question": "You are advised to contact us immediately ___ technical problems with your computer system don't seem to be resolved."}, "1759": {"1": "Soon", "2": "Then", "3": "Later", "4": "Once", "answer": "Once", "question": "___ all the provisions of the merger are fully implemented, the two companies will expand their partnerships to provide an even higher level of quality."}, "1760": {"1": "nominate", "2": "nominations", "3": "nominating", "4": "nominated", "answer": "nominations", "question": "This letter is to solicit ___ of candidates to be considered for the vacant positions in sales that should be filled right away."}, "1761": {"1": "economics", "2": "harvest", "3": "productivity", "4": "measures", "answer": "productivity", "question": "Our investment will lead to more improved public services, considerable cost reductions as well as further ___ ."}, "1762": {"1": "whom", "2": "whoever", "3": "what", "4": "where", "answer": "whom", "question": "The names of upper management to ___ you must report will be provided in order to get budgets approved for projects."}, "1763": {"1": "uniform", "2": "even", "3": "far", "4": "equal", "answer": "equal", "question": "Successful candidates will receive a competitive salary and maximum benefits ___ to those which they have received from their previous jobs."}, "1764": {"1": "predominant", "2": "predominantly", "3": "predominating", "4": "predominated", "answer": "predominantly", "question": "It is ___ through broadcast media such as television and radio that companies place an advertisement to attract prospective customers."}, "1765": {"1": "schedule", "2": "scheduled", "3": "schedules", "4": "schedulers", "answer": "schedule", "question": "Employees must reserve a time to copy by writing their names on the ___ on the lid of the photocopiers."}, "1766": {"1": "painted", "2": "charged", "3": "alternated", "4": "transferred", "answer": "painted", "question": "Most of the cabins situated at the bottom of the hill are ___ grey and white."}, "1767": {"1": "caution", "2": "cautious", "3": "cautiously", "4": "cautiousness", "answer": "cautious", "question": "Workshop participants were required to be ___ not to choose any reserved front-row seats."}, "1768": {"1": "or", "2": "and", "3": "neither", "4": "nor", "answer": "nor", "question": "If you won't be able to present a valid receipt, neither may the products be returned ___ are you refunded."}, "1769": {"1": "clearness", "2": "clear", "3": "clearly", "4": "clearest", "answer": "clearly", "question": "Road and street signs must be ___ visible even in the distance in order for drivers to know where they are heading."}, "1770": {"1": "over", "2": "within", "3": "down", "4": "behind", "answer": "behind", "question": "To be safe, don't use bank cash machines located ___ pillars or away from public view."}, "1771": {"1": "ensure", "2": "ensuring", "3": "ensured", "4": "be ensured", "answer": "ensure", "question": "So as to ___ that your medical treatment will be paid for, you must present a note from your doctor."}, "1772": {"1": "speedy", "2": "available", "3": "presentable", "4": "limited", "answer": "limited", "question": "Since supplies are ___ , you are invited to order this gorgeous laptop model on sale before it is sold out."}, "1773": {"1": "agreement", "2": "agrees", "3": "agreements", "4": "agreed", "answer": "agreement", "question": "The two companies signed an ___ on the acquisition in spite of a few differing opinions."}, "1774": {"1": "quickly", "2": "precisely", "3": "currently", "4": "temperately", "answer": "currently", "question": "This e-mail is to let you know that the book you ordered is ___ on back order."}, "1775": {"1": "we", "2": "us", "3": "our", "4": "ourselves", "answer": "we", "question": "As soon as the shipment of computer equipment comes in, ___ will ship it to you promptly."}, "1776": {"1": "recalled", "2": "memorized", "3": "reminded", "4": "identified", "answer": "reminded", "question": "New employees were ___ to be photographed immediately in order to have their new identification made."}, "1777": {"1": "is", "2": "been", "3": "are", "4": "being", "answer": "are", "question": "As portable audio items ___ currently unavailable in the store, you'd better check the Internet for more information."}, "1778": {"1": "adoption", "2": "policy", "3": "exhibit", "4": "regard", "answer": "policy", "question": "Our ___ is not to issue refunds on software programs used on a trial basis."}, "1779": {"1": "exception", "2": "exceptionally", "3": "exceptional", "4": "except", "answer": "exceptionally", "question": "We have worked ___ hard on health insurance plans to enhance employee satisfaction."}, "1780": {"1": "among", "2": "toward", "3": "after", "4": "during", "answer": "among", "question": "Funds from the government grant will be allocated to or distributed ___ the affected areas."}, "1781": {"1": "if", "2": "since", "3": "how", "4": "than", "answer": "since", "question": "More efforts to accomplish the objectives for reducing costs have been made ___ they were set out at the beginning of this year."}, "1782": {"1": "technician", "2": "factory", "3": "certificate", "4": "generator", "answer": "technician", "question": "As the desktop printer was out of service, we called a skilled ___ yesterday for repairs."}, "1783": {"1": "them", "2": "they", "3": "itself", "4": "its", "answer": "its", "question": "The head of the marketing department attributed success in the overseas market to ___ motivated and hard-working employees."}, "1784": {"1": "notify", "2": "present", "3": "assign", "4": "permit", "answer": "present", "question": "We require all club members to ___ their membership cards to the service desk in order to use the fitness room."}, "1785": {"1": "complete", "2": "completes", "3": "completely", "4": "completed", "answer": "completely", "question": "All the required application forms must be filled out ___ before they are turned in to the appropriate office."}, "1786": {"1": "chaired", "2": "performed", "3": "reserved", "4": "presided", "answer": "reserved", "question": "A few executive positions have been ___ for women as part of corporate efforts to place women in upper-level positions."}, "1787": {"1": "before", "2": "therefore", "3": "until", "4": "because", "answer": "before", "question": "You are advised to check documents related to the continuation of health insurance coverage ___ leaving your current job."}, "1788": {"1": "residence", "2": "right", "3": "endeavor", "4": "encompass", "answer": "right", "question": "Lightware Kitchen Goods Ltd. reserves the ___ to deny any liability for damages caused by abnormal use."}, "1789": {"1": "Defective", "2": "Defect", "3": "Defects", "4": "Defected", "answer": "Defective", "question": "___ merchandise may be exchanged for the same item in compliance with our exchange policy."}, "1790": {"1": "handled", "2": "replied", "3": "attended", "4": "exempted", "answer": "handled", "question": "Questions concerning the billing process will be ___ by customer service representatives while the billing department is closed."}, "1791": {"1": "rigor", "2": "rigors", "3": "rigorous", "4": "rigorously", "answer": "rigorously", "question": "The medications widely used for patients should be ___ evaluated for long-term use."}, "1792": {"1": "with", "2": "across", "3": "beside", "4": "from", "answer": "with", "question": "Along the shore of the lake is a recreational family camping site, complete ___ fire places, showers and refrigerators."}, "1793": {"1": "submitting", "2": "submitted", "3": "submit", "4": "submission", "answer": "submitted", "question": "Employment application forms completed by applicants must be ___ to Mr. Keith by Friday at noon."}, "1794": {"1": "finally", "2": "distinctively", "3": "extremely", "4": "predominantly", "answer": "finally", "question": "After weeks of intensive negotiations, they have ___ agreed upon a minimum wage for on-site workers."}, "1795": {"1": "Enclosed", "2": "Enclose", "3": "Enclosure", "4": "Enclosing", "answer": "Enclosed", "question": "___ please find the documents that contain confidential data on the visibility of operations."}, "1796": {"1": "various", "2": "apparent", "3": "redundant", "4": "comprehensive", "answer": "comprehensive", "question": "If you are looking for a good restaurant in your area, look it up in our ___ directory of local restaurants."}, "1797": {"1": "accommodates", "2": "accommodate", "3": "accommodating", "4": "accommodation", "answer": "accommodate", "question": "In order to ___ the needs of demanding customers, the telecommunications industry is considering developing better functions."}, "1798": {"1": "promptly", "2": "vocally", "3": "openly", "4": "neutrally", "answer": "promptly", "question": "Installing air-cooling systems is scheduled to begin ___ at 10 A.M. and end at 3 P.M."}, "1799": {"1": "beneficial", "2": "benefits", "3": "beneficiary", "4": "benefit", "answer": "beneficial", "question": "The recent findings indicate that the effects of weight loss associated with calorie restriction are quite ___ ."}, "1800": {"1": "meaning", "2": "belief", "3": "excursion", "4": "abstract", "answer": "abstract", "question": "The finished report should not exceed 20 pages, including a one-page ___ , and should be turned in by this Friday."}, "1801": {"1": "performing", "2": "performed", "3": "perform", "4": "performance", "answer": "performance", "question": "The newly launched cell phones were designed to deliver exceptional ___ in various functions."}, "1802": {"1": "selective", "2": "expressive", "3": "definitive", "4": "competitive", "answer": "definitive", "question": "Diamond Getaway travel agency is considered to be the ___ source of worldwide trips among travelers."}, "1803": {"1": "nearing", "2": "nears", "3": "nearly", "4": "neared", "answer": "nearly", "question": "It appears to be a ___ impossible plan to charge fees to cars visiting the city park on the weekend."}, "1804": {"1": "whereas", "2": "as if", "3": "whether", "4": "assuming that", "answer": "assuming that", "question": "People who have wanted to buy a home but couldn't afford to will be able to qualify, ___ interest rates remain moderate."}, "1805": {"1": "for", "2": "from", "3": "onto", "4": "off", "answer": "for", "question": "We need to reserve a restaurant ___ a celebration party in honor of a newly appointed personnel manager."}, "1806": {"1": "She", "2": "Her", "3": "Hers", "4": "Herself", "answer": "She", "question": "___ habitually answers incoming phone calls and signs for packages while in the office."}, "1807": {"1": "sent", "2": "delayed", "3": "arrived", "4": "examined", "answer": "arrived", "question": "A new shipment of popular bargain books has just ___ here in perfect condition and will be on display this afternoon."}, "1808": {"1": "server", "2": "service", "3": "servicing", "4": "serve", "answer": "service", "question": "The Catering & Event Department enjoys a solid reputation for extraordinary ___ provided to customers."}, "1809": {"1": "currently", "2": "significantly", "3": "completely", "4": "slightly", "answer": "currently", "question": "It is anticipated that those ___ looking for employment will be successful in the coming months."}, "1810": {"1": "earning", "2": "valuing", "3": "benefiting", "4": "dedicating", "answer": "dedicating", "question": "Hart House Inc. is widely recognized for ___ all its energy and resources to supporting social activities."}, "1811": {"1": "to", "2": "after", "3": "of", "4": "about", "answer": "to", "question": "According to a new study by Single Click, online shoppers search the Internet at least one week prior ___ actually purchasing their products."}, "1812": {"1": "offering", "2": "be offered", "3": "to offer", "4": "are offering", "answer": "are offering", "question": "Most stores ___ special discounts, coupons on gifts, and personalized gifts to retain their existing customers."}, "1813": {"1": "Since", "2": "If", "3": "So", "4": "Unless", "answer": "Since", "question": "___ there are so many stores throughout the district, any type of bad publicity carries a lot of risk."}, "1814": {"1": "higher", "2": "highest", "3": "more highly", "4": "most highly", "answer": "highest", "question": "HPR Press achieved the ___ overall rating from its customers in a recent independent survey of nearly 10, customers."}, "1815": {"1": "greatly", "2": "especially", "3": "unusually", "4": "positively", "answer": "especially", "question": "I would not like to recommend the Westin Orlando Hotel, ___ considering that it has poor quality room service."}, "1816": {"1": "their", "2": "theirs", "3": "they", "4": "themselves", "answer": "their", "question": "Drivers are required to carry ___ liability insurance policy at all times in their carsin case of an accident."}, "1817": {"1": "Rather than", "2": "Despite", "3": "Although", "4": "In order that", "answer": "Although", "question": "___ the two copy machines differ in a few of their functions, you will be soon accustomed to operating them."}, "1818": {"1": "grower", "2": "grow", "3": "grown", "4": "growth", "answer": "growth", "question": "Mr. Tanaka decided to resign, because a significant drop in customer satisfaction has had an adverse impact on sales ___ ."}, "1819": {"1": "declining", "2": "declined", "3": "decline", "4": "to decline", "answer": "declining", "question": "Most of the automobile companies are likely to face ___ sales in midsize and large cars as a result of the continuing recession."}, "1820": {"1": "comparing", "2": "comparable", "3": "compare", "4": "compares", "answer": "comparable", "question": "Although some studies report different effects of overtime work, they are ___ with respect to productivity levels."}, "1821": {"1": "distinguish", "2": "range", "3": "refrain", "4": "prohibit", "answer": "range", "question": "Your membership renewal will entitle you to a wide variety of benefits that ___ from innovative services to effective programs."}, "1822": {"1": "prefer", "2": "preferred", "3": "preferable", "4": "preferring", "answer": "preferred", "question": "Applicants who possess interpersonal skills and strong analytical skills to gather and analyze information for reports will be especially ___ ."}, "1823": {"1": "proceeding", "2": "facilitating", "3": "installing", "4": "undergoing", "answer": "undergoing", "question": "Now that our site is currently ___ essential maintenance work, we apologize for the inconvenience and ask that you try again later on."}, "1824": {"1": "retirement", "2": "retire", "3": "retires", "4": "retired", "answer": "retirement", "question": "You are cordially invited to attend a ___ party thrown in honor of employees who have served the company for more than thirty years."}, "1825": {"1": "much", "2": "such", "3": "very", "4": "too", "answer": "much", "question": "Questions concerning whether international trade is ___ more beneficial to lower income economies have been raised for years."}, "1826": {"1": "selling", "2": "have been selling", "3": "will be sold", "4": "have been sold", "answer": "will be sold", "question": "Fat-blocking weight loss pills ___ over the counter effective immediately."}, "1827": {"1": "evaluations", "2": "attempts", "3": "medicines", "4": "contributions", "answer": "contributions", "question": "Compact List Inc. appreciates the ___ you have made to this annual event."}, "1828": {"1": "highly", "2": "most likely", "3": "slightly", "4": "timely", "answer": "most likely", "question": "A group of established corporations will ___ carry out the downsizing program, which represents the biggest reduction in jobs since ."}, "1829": {"1": "During", "2": "Despite", "3": "Besides", "4": "Into", "answer": "Despite", "question": "___ fulfilling the requirements and receiving unanimous approval from the committee, Ms. Norton was not accepted for the position."}, "1830": {"1": "secure", "2": "security", "3": "securely", "4": "more secure", "answer": "securely", "question": "Please make sure that all the volts in overhead compartments are tightened ___ ."}, "1831": {"1": "factors", "2": "sides", "3": "senses", "4": "portions", "answer": "factors", "question": "Your salaries and earnings vary greatly, depending on several ___ such as your specialty area, degree, and sector of employment."}, "1832": {"1": "to rewrite", "2": "rewriting", "3": "rewritten", "4": "should rewrite", "answer": "rewriting", "question": "Although revised reports are better than they were last week, Mr. Dan Gum, the program director, suggested ___ them."}, "1833": {"1": "conditional", "2": "partial", "3": "temporary", "4": "discontinued", "answer": "discontinued", "question": "We are obligated to retain all the manuals, even for ___ appliances."}, "1834": {"1": "they", "2": "their", "3": "them", "4": "themselves", "answer": "themselves", "question": "Drivers are asked to park their cars by ___ rather than using a valet parking system."}, "1835": {"1": "offer", "2": "provide", "3": "serve", "4": "reflect", "answer": "serve", "question": "DTS has undergone drastic changes designed to better ___ its valued customers."}, "1836": {"1": "according", "2": "physical", "3": "native", "4": "approximate", "answer": "native", "question": "Companies expanding into other regions prefer hiring workers ___ to the targeted region."}, "1837": {"1": "receipt", "2": "admission", "3": "ownership", "4": "membership", "answer": "receipt", "question": "The warranty attached to the product you purchased will be valid for two years from the date of ___ ."}, "1838": {"1": "has been starting", "2": "will be starting", "3": "is started", "4": "is being started", "answer": "will be starting", "question": "The corporate monitoring committee ___ an inspection in any violation of security codes in a week."}, "1839": {"1": "Analyst", "2": "Analysis", "3": "Analyze", "4": "Analytical", "answer": "Analysis", "question": "___ of survey data revealed distinct differences between the two proposed projects."}, "1840": {"1": "Once", "2": "Nevertheless", "3": "Despite", "4": "Still", "answer": "Once", "question": "___ the first session has been successfully completed, the subsequent topics won't be difficult to understand."}, "1841": {"1": "That", "2": "Should", "3": "Even", "4": "Whether", "answer": "Whether", "question": "___ you are here for corporate workshops or need to host a meeting, we can offer conference rooms, food services, and lodging."}, "1842": {"1": "promising", "2": "completed", "3": "favorite", "4": "immature", "answer": "promising", "question": "After further research on breast cancer treatment, pharmaceutical companies are investing in medicine development areas that look more ___ ."}, "1843": {"1": "so has", "2": "even so", "3": "whereas", "4": "as to", "answer": "so has", "question": "The sales of new wireless electronic products have significantly increased and ___ customer satisfaction."}, "1844": {"1": "up to", "2": "while", "3": "as of", "4": "concerning", "answer": "concerning", "question": "The hygiene department will provide you with information ___ stringent safety criteria."}, "1845": {"1": "use", "2": "used", "3": "using", "4": "will use", "answer": "using", "question": "The head of the department ___ the banquet room for a party should submit a required form to the Catering Department."}, "1846": {"1": "While", "2": "Since", "3": "Once", "4": "Now that", "answer": "Since", "question": "___ providing an extraordinary service to our patrons, overall sales have almost tripled."}, "1847": {"1": "offer", "2": "give", "3": "select", "4": "cater", "answer": "offer", "question": "In order to ___ a wide variety of dining pleasures, we have hired extra kitchen help."}, "1848": {"1": "negotiation", "2": "determination", "3": "states", "4": "summary", "answer": "summary", "question": "The terms and conditions on the plane ticket are a ___ of the agreement between the airline and passengers."}, "1849": {"1": "entered", "2": "honored", "3": "allowed", "4": "separated", "answer": "allowed", "question": "For safety reasons, visi~ors not accompanied by security staff will not be ___ into the laboratory."}, "1850": {"1": "include", "2": "provide", "3": "renew", "4": "entail", "answer": "renew", "question": "Please mention my name in order for you to ___ the subscription to the journal on my behalf."}, "1851": {"1": "send", "2": "sent", "3": "to send", "4": "sending", "answer": "sent", "question": "A complete list of our hotel amenities will be ___ to you upon request."}, "1852": {"1": ".precise", "2": "precision", "3": "precisely", "4": "preciseness", "answer": "precisely", "question": "Events in celebration of our 10th anniversary will begin ___ at 1OA.M. tomorrow morning."}, "1853": {"1": "stringent", "2": "founded", "3": "delighted", "4": "dependent", "answer": "stringent", "question": "Jen's Business designed a ___ inspection program to assure its members that their stay is a safe and enjoyable one."}, "1854": {"1": "require", "2": "requiring", "3": "required", "4": "requirements", "answer": "requirements", "question": "We regularly monitor the quality of products and services in order to meet strict ___ ."}, "1855": {"1": "all", "2": "even", "3": "any", "4": "almost", "answer": "even", "question": "If the company had been under better circumstances, it could have obtained an ___ more favorable outcome."}, "1856": {"1": "if", "2": "whether", "3": "despite", "4": "that", "answer": "if", "question": "Service employees are exempt from overtime ___ the position meets specific circumstances."}, "1857": {"1": "attend", "2": "represent", "3": "conduct", "4": "express", "answer": "represent", "question": "Most companies hire attorneys to ___ them in case they encounter any trouble."}, "1858": {"1": "Except", "2": "Also", "3": "Unless", "4": "Therefore", "answer": "Unless", "question": "___ we find a comprehensive approach to dealing with traffic congestion, it will continue to worsen."}, "1859": {"1": "negotiates", "2": "negotiator", "3": "negotiations", "4": "negotiable", "answer": "negotiations", "question": "The head of the legal department is searching for experts who have a lot of experience with contract ___ ."}, "1860": {"1": "prosperous", "2": "customized", "3": "found", "4": "appointed", "answer": "customized", "question": "Ace Training Group excels in providing the best professional course that can be ___ to your unique needs."}, "1861": {"1": "professionally", "2": "professional", "3": "professionalism", "4": "profession", "answer": "professional", "question": "Many ___ agricultural advisors were hired to boost the significantly declining industry."}, "1862": {"1": "sincere", "2": "original", "3": "estimated", "4": "completed", "answer": "sincere", "question": "We will hold a raffle event in all our department stores next week to extend our ___ thanks to our valuable customers."}, "1863": {"1": "correct", "2": "correcting", "3": "correction", "4": "correctly", "answer": "correctly", "question": "Please note that payment statements must be addressed ___ to the recipients."}, "1864": {"1": "receive", "2": "receipt", "3": "receipts", "4": "receiving", "answer": "receipt", "question": "Any errors in the payroll slip should be reported to the proper department within five days of ___ ."}, "1865": {"1": "spoken", "2": "reported", "3": "notified", "4": "required", "answer": "notified", "question": "When the construction workers were ___ of the arrival date of materials, they expressed concerns over the delay."}, "1866": {"1": "how", "2": "when", "3": "which", "4": "what", "answer": "what", "question": "Researchers in a broad range of fields were asked to review ___ the proposed project may entail."}, "1867": {"1": "once", "2": "whoever", "3": "sometimes", "4": "unless", "answer": "once", "question": "Shipping details will be entered into the computer ___ we have received the authorization."}, "1868": {"1": "mature", "2": "up-to-date", "3": "proficient", "4": "exclusive", "answer": "up-to-date", "question": "Award-winning publications to keep you ___ on current trends will be provided if you join Marsh Group Inc."}, "1869": {"1": "confirmed", "2": "reached", "3": "determined", "4": "arrived", "answer": "reached", "question": "I can be ___ at the number below if you encounter any trouble requiring my attention."}, "1870": {"1": "detail", "2": "detailed", "3": "detailing", "4": "in detail", "answer": "detailing", "question": "Please complete the return list ___ the reason for the return and it will be processed promptly."}, "1871": {"1": "qualification", "2": "qualified", "3": "more qualified", "4": "most qualified", "answer": "most qualified", "question": "Of the 6 candidates, Ms. Sally Marson seemed the ___ for the position."}, "1872": {"1": "outdoors", "2": "starting", "3": "afterwards", "4": "as to", "answer": "starting", "question": "Tickets to the newly refurbished amusement park will be sold online ___ on Monday."}, "1873": {"1": "be", "2": "are", "3": "have been", "4": "will be", "answer": "be", "question": "A few flight attendants have requested that some loose volts in the overhead bins ___ tightened."}, "1874": {"1": "opens", "2": "openness", "3": "openings", "4": "opener", "answer": "openings", "question": "Hamas Investment placed an advertisement on temporary employment ___ for certified financial advisors."}, "1875": {"1": "economy", "2": "market", "3": "discount", "4": "criteria", "answer": "discount", "question": "Now that the company has gained a noticeable increase in net profits, it is offering customers a thirty percent ___ ."}, "1876": {"1": "economy", "2": "economic", "3": "economical", "4": "economically", "answer": "economically", "question": "Further studies will be conducted to develop ___ sound guidelines for year-round training."}, "1877": {"1": "your own", "2": "yourself", "3": "your", "4": "yours", "answer": "your own", "question": "If you have difficulty preparing for a presentation on ___ , ask Mr. Jacobs for help."}, "1878": {"1": "accompanies", "2": "accompanying", "3": "accompanied", "4": "will accompany", "answer": "accompanied", "question": "A letter ___ by a copy of the press release was mailed to the public relations department yesterday."}, "1879": {"1": "will be", "2": "has", "3": "will have", "4": "were", "answer": "will be", "question": "In order to demonstrate our appreciation, a party ___ held at a Chinese restaurant."}, "1880": {"1": "confirm", "2": "confirming", "3": "confirmation", "4": "confirmed", "answer": "confirmation", "question": "The conference's keynote speaker called this morning for ___ that everything has been set for his presentation."}, "1881": {"1": "repeat", "2": "repeated", "3": "repeating", "4": "repetition", "answer": "repeated", "question": "After ___ requests by residents, the city's board members decided to install additional traffic lights."}, "1882": {"1": "inasmuch as", "2": "them", "3": "about", "4": "that", "answer": "that", "question": "Please note ___ prices for not yet published books are tentative and final pricing will be determined at publication."}, "1883": {"1": "during", "2": "in", "3": "while", "4": "afterward", "answer": "while", "question": "Employees are advised to refrain from using mobile phones ___ on duty, since it causes distraction."}, "1884": {"1": "profession", "2": "professional", "3": "professor", "4": "profess", "answer": "professional", "question": "The Society for Communication seeks to advance technical support systems and provide services for the education and ___ development of its members."}, "1885": {"1": "had better", "2": "had rather", "3": "would have", "4": "are better", "answer": "had better", "question": "If you would like to lose weight, you ___ replace high-calorie side dishes with healthier alternatives."}, "1886": {"1": "entail", "2": "compare", "3": "diminish", "4": "serve", "answer": "compare", "question": "Those who wish to get the best deal from their shopping are advised to ___ product features, prices and read customer reviews carefully."}, "1887": {"1": "doubtful", "2": "genuine", "3": "fluctuating", "4": "assorted", "answer": "fluctuating", "question": "The successful candidate may work in an environment with frequent interruptions and ___ deadlines rather than in a stable environment."}, "1888": {"1": "compare", "2": "comparing", "3": "compared", "4": "comparison", "answer": "compared", "question": "According to the preliminary analysis by the labor department, the recovery of the economy this year led to an increase in employment, ___ with the same period last year."}, "1889": {"1": "who", "2": "which", "3": "whose", "4": "that", "answer": "whose", "question": "Customers ___ products are provided and maintained through an existing arrangement should contact us immediately."}, "1890": {"1": "also", "2": "except", "3": "therefore", "4": "unless", "answer": "unless", "question": "You will need to pay for the cost of shipping, ___ given alternative instructions from our customer service department."}, "1891": {"1": "continue", "2": "continuous", "3": "continuing", "4": "continued", "answer": "continuing", "question": "We are looking forward to ___ to provide the highest-quality programs consistently for years to come."}, "1892": {"1": "them of", "2": "that of", "3": "this of", "4": "those of", "answer": "those of", "question": "Increasingly powerful computer graphics have enabled domestic filmmakers to create screen images that rival ___ Hollywood."}, "1893": {"1": "critic", "2": "appreciative", "3": "understanding", "4": "reflective", "answer": "reflective", "question": "I recommend that the presentation you will give next week be ___ of the overall market trends."}, "1894": {"1": "doubt", "2": "doubted", "3": "doubtful", "4": "doubtfully", "answer": "doubtful", "question": "Mr. Jackson is ___ that he is authorized to fly business class to get to the trade fair in Chicago."}, "1895": {"1": "comprehensive", "2": "comprehension", "3": "comprehensively", "4": "comprehend", "answer": "comprehensive", "question": "We will help you find ___ and costeffective solutions to drive your business to a higher level of success."}, "1896": {"1": "return", "2": "returns", "3": "returned", "4": "returning", "answer": "returning", "question": "If you need further information or have any questions about ___ your merchandise, please send an e-mail to the sales department or contact us."}, "1897": {"1": "base", "2": "basing", "3": "based", "4": "basement", "answer": "based", "question": "The V.S. Center database will allow you to find the best volunteer opportunities ___ on your preference."}, "1898": {"1": "barely", "2": "gradually", "3": "necessarily", "4": "presumably", "answer": "necessarily", "question": "The increase in the overall sales volume does not ___ indicate a high level of customer satisfaction."}, "1899": {"1": "better", "2": "improved", "3": "enhanced", "4": "superior", "answer": "superior", "question": "Ms. Gail Hutson, systems manager, made internal corporate biogs ___ to other traditional forms of communications."}, "1900": {"1": "common", "2": "even", "3": "genuine", "4": "accurate", "answer": "common", "question": "It is fairly ___ for employees to receive full compensation for their overtime work."}, "1901": {"1": "temporary", "2": "minor", "3": "duplicate", "4": "harsh", "answer": "temporary", "question": "We need to appoint a ___ replacement for Mr. Hwang, who handles classes on nutrition to attendees. -"}, "1902": {"1": "limited", "2": "partial", "3": "regular", "4": "first", "answer": "limited", "question": "If you purchase our outstanding laptop with a full one-year ___ warranty, we will ship it today."}, "1903": {"1": "prospective", "2": "approaching", "3": "displaced", "4": "available", "answer": "available", "question": "We are sorry that the product you have searched for is no longer ___ for sale."}, "1904": {"1": "restored", "2": "restoring", "3": "to restore", "4": "restoration", "answer": "restored", "question": "I am sorry that you experienced a temporary interruption in our services, but all services were ___ a moment ago."}, "1905": {"1": "custom", "2": "customary", "3": "customers", "4": "customized", "answer": "customers", "question": "To demonstrate our appreciation to our valued ___ ,we are offering free tickets to new plays which received outstanding reviews from critics."}, "1906": {"1": "altogether", "2": "plus", "3": "though", "4": "only", "answer": "plus", "question": "A survey of consumers shows that respondents want convenience ___ enjoyable experience when shopping."}, "1907": {"1": "exaggeration", "2": "challenges", "3": "cause", "4": "allowances", "answer": "challenges", "question": "The rapid growth of an aging population is posing tough ___ to the social security system of most countries."}, "1908": {"1": "accused", "2": "presented", "3": "blamed", "4": "attributed", "answer": "attributed", "question": "Gas explosions are often ___ to negligence and are usually caused by violations of standards or safe practices."}, "1909": {"1": "indicators", "2": "objectives", "3": "compromises", "4": "directions", "answer": "indicators", "question": "Despite a large number of ___ that companies are facing a serious shortage of skilled workers, proper action has not been taken."}, "1910": {"1": "Whether", "2": "So that", "3": "Even if", "4": "Nonetheless", "answer": "Even if", "question": "___ most workers are working collaboratively, it looks like they will fail to meet the deadline."}, "1911": {"1": "alignment", "2": "momentum", "3": "conjunction", "4": "relation", "answer": "conjunction", "question": "This discount offer may not be used in ___ with any other coupons. ."}, "1912": {"1": "write", "2": "writing", "3": "written", "4": "for writing", "answer": "writing", "question": "The employees in the planning department spend most of their time ___ proposals for a better management structure."}, "1913": {"1": "complied", "2": "observed", "3": "breached", "4": "adhered", "answer": "breached", "question": "Any employers or contractors who are found to have ___ safety laws will be subject to a heavy fine."}, "1914": {"1": "size", "2": "proportion", "3": "equivalent", "4": "condition", "answer": "proportion", "question": "A large ___ of low-income populations rely on farming and fishing for their living."}, "1915": {"1": "worry", "2": "worrying", "3": "worried", "4": "worries", "answer": "worrying", "question": "One of the most ___ consequences of worldwide climate change is the steady rise of sea levels."}, "1916": {"1": "it", "2": "themselves", "3": "those", "4": "itself", "answer": "itself", "question": "APT Electronics has proved ___ capable of achieving impressive revenues just in the first quarter."}, "1917": {"1": "obligation", "2": "promise", "3": "means", "4": "precaution", "answer": "obligation", "question": "Managers who meet specific requirements are exempt from ___ to attend the workshop."}, "1918": {"1": "Advance", "2": "Advancement", "3": "Advances", "4": "Advancing", "answer": "Advances", "question": "___ in satellite technology have significantly altered the appearance of the country's communication antenna facilities."}, "1919": {"1": "implement", "2": "implementing", "3": "implemented", "4": "being implemented", "answer": "implementing", "question": "The government prepared for the coming drought season, ___ water conservation plans."}, "1920": {"1": "alert", "2": "attract", "3": "mount", "4": "apply", "answer": "attract", "question": "The urban renewal development plan is expected to ___ many investors from around the country."}, "1921": {"1": "interfere", "2": "contribute", "3": "benefit", "4": "pretend", "answer": "benefit", "question": "Mr. Bernard accepted the terms of the agreement, which could ___ his company in the long term."}, "1922": {"1": "accommodate", "2": "charge", "3": "decline", "4": "preserve", "answer": "accommodate", "question": "Should any arrangements be changed, we will do everything possible to ___ your requests."}, "1923": {"1": "another", "2": "other", "3": "each other", "4": "one", "answer": "another", "question": "Mr. Chu will demonstrate how to switch from one server to ___ this afternoon."}, "1924": {"1": "or", "2": "neither", "3": "nor", "4": "both", "answer": "or", "question": "Successful candidates will be posted to either New York ___ Paris."}, "1925": {"1": "signing", "2": "signed", "3": "signature", "4": "to sign", "answer": "signature", "question": "Please remember to include your ___ at the bottom of the order form."}, "1926": {"1": "deposits", "2": "appoints", "3": "predicts", "4": "operates", "answer": "appoints", "question": "Every two years, the board of directors ___ a new financial officer to oversee the company's domestic operations."}, "1927": {"1": "suggest", "2": "suggestion", "3": "suggested", "4": "suggesting", "answer": "suggested", "question": "Ms. Yakamoto has ___ that the department meeting be postponed until everyone returns from vacation."}, "1928": {"1": "subscribers", "2": "spectators", "3": "witnesses", "4": "participants", "answer": "subscribers", "question": "Market Solutions is one of Europe's leading international business magazines, with ___ in over 50 countries."}, "1929": {"1": "extend", "2": "extent", "3": "extensive", "4": "extending", "answer": "extensive", "question": "Employees on international assignment with Daniel Windmere Corporation receive ___ financial support when finding a place to live."}, "1930": {"1": "conveniently", "2": "correctly", "3": "greatly", "4": "widely", "answer": "conveniently", "question": "According to the Cosmopolitan News, Gemstone Records will soon be opening a store ___ located on Grand Avenue."}, "1931": {"1": "competitively", "2": "competitive", "3": "competes", "4": "competition", "answer": "competition", "question": "Mr. Garcia has a good chance of getting the marketing job, although ___ for it will be fierce."}, "1932": {"1": "support", "2": "purchase", "3": "achieve", "4": "replace", "answer": "purchase", "question": "Some fans lined up outside the box office for as long as fourteen hours to ___ tickets for the concert."}, "1933": {"1": "total", "2": "totaling", "3": "totally", "4": "totaled", "answer": "totally", "question": "A new production device takes manufacturers one step closer to making electronic displays ___ out of plastic."}, "1934": {"1": "Like", "2": "Once", "3": "Unless", "4": "Despite", "answer": "Once", "question": "___ the change-of-address form had been submitted to the billing department, the invoices began arriving at the proper location."}, "1935": {"1": "her", "2": "hers", "3": "herself", "4": "she", "answer": "herself", "question": "Ms. Jackson said she would prefer to work on the report by ___ before submitting a draft for the committee's approval."}, "1936": {"1": "invests", "2": "investing", "3": "invested", "4": "invest", "answer": "investing", "question": "Mr. Riyadh, a successful local businessman, made his fortune by ___ in real estate."}, "1937": {"1": "behind", "2": "above", "3": "except", "4": "through", "answer": "through", "question": "Margaret Nelson was hired to lead the company ___ the complicated process of organizational restructuring."}, "1938": {"1": "accident", "2": "accidental", "3": "accidents", "4": "accidentally", "answer": "accidentally", "question": "The newscaster ___ mispronounced the name of the Tolberg Book Prize winner on television last night."}, "1939": {"1": "works", "2": "be working", "3": "to work", "4": "will work", "answer": "to work", "question": "Mr. Osaki would like the entire staff ___ together and complete the task by the deadline."}, "1940": {"1": "reference", "2": "plot", "3": "resource", "4": "practice", "answer": "practice", "question": "Sending a letter of thanks immediately after a job interview is a highly recommended ___"}, "1941": {"1": "upon", "2": "until", "3": "without", "4": "along", "answer": "without", "question": "JHB Bank cannot process a loan application ___ the proper documentation."}, "1942": {"1": "so", "2": "concerning", "3": "over", "4": "since", "answer": "so", "question": "Please notify Ms. Chen that the meeting has been rescheduled ___ that tomorrow's visitors from the overseas office can attend."}, "1943": {"1": "from", "2": "about", "3": "between", "4": "throughout", "answer": "throughout", "question": "If you experience difficulties with the installation process, technical support is available ___ the day."}, "1944": {"1": "proposing", "2": "propose", "3": "proposes", "4": "proposal", "answer": "proposal", "question": "Please review the ___ for new safety procedures, and add your comments."}, "1945": {"1": "related", "2": "stylish", "3": "disinterested", "4": "unavailable", "answer": "unavailable", "question": "The jacket you ordered is currently ___ in the color you requested, but we will send the rest of your order promptly."}, "1946": {"1": "ours", "2": "theirs", "3": "their", "4": "ourselves", "answer": "their", "question": "Although multiple studies were conducted by market research groups, it is still uncertain whether customers are ready to purchase ___ groceries on the Internet."}, "1947": {"1": "affect", "2": "contain", "3": "fulfill", "4": "mention", "answer": "fulfill", "question": "Neblus, Inc., will have to add staff if it expects to ___ all of the orders by the end of the year."}, "1948": {"1": "shoppers", "2": "shopping", "3": "to shop", "4": "shopper", "answer": "shoppers", "question": "Department store managers have asked ___ not to bring food or beverages into the store."}, "1949": {"1": "total", "2": "entire", "3": "complete", "4": "whole", "answer": "complete", "question": "When the copying process is , a ___ small \"Done\" window appears on the computer screen."}, "1950": {"1": "periodic", "2": "periodically", "3": "periodical", "4": "period", "answer": "periodically", "question": "All Seneca area residents are requested to clean the recycling bins ___ with hot, soapy water."}, "1951": {"1": "sale", "2": "place", "3": "market", "4": "advertisement", "answer": "market", "question": "Retail properties in the downtown area generally stay on the ___ for periods of three to six weeks before they are sold."}, "1952": {"1": "spacious", "2": "spacing", "3": "spaciousness", "4": "spaces", "answer": "spacious", "question": "In keeping with Barrett International's effort to provide a comfortable work environment, the company's new buildings are ___ and well lit."}, "1953": {"1": "In order", "2": "Whether", "3": "According", "4": "How", "answer": "In order", "question": "___ to ensure timely delivery, make certain the address and phone number are clearly printed at the top of the form."}, "1954": {"1": "mutually", "2": "punctually", "3": "respectively", "4": "precisely", "answer": "mutually", "question": "We at TPG Financial Planning welcome the opportunity to assist you in your business and look forward to a ___ beneficial relationship."}, "1955": {"1": "complaint", "2": "receipt", "3": "replacement", "4": "promotion", "answer": "replacement", "question": "Customers unhappy with the performance of their stereo equipment have two months to request a refund or ___ ."}, "1956": {"1": "repetitive", "2": "repeating", "3": "repetition", "4": "repeat", "answer": "repetitive", "question": "The division manager revised the report because the language in it was too ___ ."}, "1957": {"1": "as if", "2": "even though", "3": "while", "4": "because", "answer": "even though", "question": "Dr. Suzuki arrived for the awards ceremony on time ___ her train had left twenty minutes late."}, "1958": {"1": "misinterpret", "2": "misinterpreted", "3": "misinterpretation", "4": "misinterpreting", "answer": "misinterpreted", "question": "Mr. Lee's conciliatory comments appear to have been ___ by some of his readers."}, "1959": {"1": "therefore", "2": "now that", "3": "in case", "4": "otherwise", "answer": "therefore", "question": "Nonaka Consultancy's strength lies in its accomplished team of data analysts, and ___ the company highlights its analytic services when seeking new clients."}, "1960": {"1": "for", "2": "next", "3": "while", "4": "onto", "answer": "for", "question": "Plans are under way ___ the extension of the San Pedro Valley water pipeline."}, "1961": {"1": "enlisted", "2": "opportune", "3": "intentional", "4": "appropriate", "answer": "appropriate", "question": "The sales representatives consider the size of the space before recommending an ___ air-conditioning system."}, "1962": {"1": "appointments", "2": "positions", "3": "assignments", "4": "subscriptions", "answer": "appointments", "question": "Patients who wish to reschedule their ___ must give at least 24 hours advance notice."}, "1963": {"1": "theirs", "2": "they", "3": "them", "4": "their", "answer": "their", "question": "All shipments arrive at the receiving dock, where a warehouse worker checks ___ tracking labels."}, "1964": {"1": "cautious", "2": "secure", "3": "distinguished", "4": "strict", "answer": "secure", "question": "Because this document contains confidential information, please keep it in a ___ location."}, "1965": {"1": "attends", "2": "attended", "3": "attendant", "4": "attention", "answer": "attention", "question": "Fred's superb ___ to detail is his best attribute as a graphic artist."}, "1966": {"1": "so", "2": "nor", "3": "and", "4": "or", "answer": "or", "question": "Please indicate on the envelope whether you would prefer regular ___ deluxe photo processing for your film."}, "1967": {"1": "addition", "2": "additions", "3": "additional", "4": "additionally", "answer": "additional", "question": "The decision to hire ___ help was based largely on the concerns expressed by the employees."}, "1968": {"1": "upgrade", "2": "ignore", "3": "prevent", "4": "improve", "answer": "prevent", "question": "National Bank officials announced that they have taken the necessary steps to ___ another computer system failure."}, "1969": {"1": "visit", "2": "visitation", "3": "visitors", "4": "visiting", "answer": "visitors", "question": "All ___ to the auto production plant must register at the security checkpoint before entering."}, "1970": {"1": "values", "2": "expenses", "3": "customs", "4": "refunds", "answer": "expenses", "question": "In an effort to reduce ___ , Barsom Cosmetics has halved its advertising budget."}, "1971": {"1": "amaze", "2": "amazing", "3": "amazement", "4": "amazingly", "answer": "amazing", "question": "The advertising team made an ___ recovery from a late start to finish the project a week ahead of schedule."}, "1972": {"1": "but", "2": "beyond", "3": "until", "4": "that", "answer": "but", "question": "The proposal for the parking garage was due yesterday, ___ the program director has agreed to a short extension."}, "1973": {"1": "he", "2": "himself", "3": "his", "4": "him", "answer": "his", "question": "We will have to inform Mr. Yamamoto that ___ application cannot be accepted at this time."}, "1974": {"1": "lastly", "2": "at first", "3": "finally", "4": "meanwhile", "answer": "finally", "question": "After the meeting with the accountant, Mr. Mitchell was ___ able to complete the budget report."}, "1975": {"1": "predicting", "2": "predicted", "3": "predictable", "4": "predictably", "answer": "predictable", "question": "Critics of the recent movie with Michelle Zhao have called the plot too ___ ."}, "1976": {"1": "only", "2": "easily", "3": "simply", "4": "merely", "answer": "only", "question": "Ms. Rivera made it clear that ___ the landowner may authorize improvements to the property."}, "1977": {"1": "establish", "2": "establishes", "3": "established", "4": "establishing", "answer": "establishing", "question": "The management of Eurosan Enterprises is in the process of ___ a new set of guidelines for customer service."}, "1978": {"1": "comply", "2": "submit", "3": "urge", "4": "advise", "answer": "submit", "question": "If you would like to be considered for a position in our advertising division, please ___ an application to the director of human resources."}, "1979": {"1": "conduct", "2": "conducted", "3": "to conduct", "4": "will conduct", "answer": "conducted", "question": "The plant supervisor, Mr. Lee, recently ___ a tour of the company's main production facility for our clients."}, "1980": {"1": "provide", "2": "qualify", "3": "hesitate", "4": "compete", "answer": "hesitate", "question": "If you require additional information about our products, please do not ___ to contact the customer service department."}, "1981": {"1": "regular", "2": "regularly", "3": "regularity", "4": "regulate", "answer": "regularly", "question": "Mr. Lopez travels ___ for business and uses the corporate accounts at hotels as well as car rental agencies."}, "1982": {"1": "for", "2": "at", "3": "across", "4": "over", "answer": "for", "question": "Each month, we will select five outstanding employees to be honored ___ their exceptional contributions to the company's performance."}, "1983": {"1": "participate", "2": "participated", "3": "participating", "4": "participation", "answer": "participation", "question": "According to Star Watch magazine, singer-songwriter Kylie Norton has announced her upcoming ___ in a charity concert."}, "1984": {"1": "with", "2": "off", "3": "from", "4": "by", "answer": "with", "question": "Customers who cannot call the service department during normal business hours may leave a message ___ our answering service."}, "1985": {"1": "retailing", "2": "retailer", "3": "retailed", "4": "retail", "answer": "retail", "question": "Applicants for the position of store manager must have at least five years of experience in ___ sales."}, "1986": {"1": "altogether", "2": "also", "3": "alone", "4": "almost", "answer": "also", "question": "Our company believes that employees should always work hard, yet they must ___ have time for their families."}, "1987": {"1": "every", "2": "both", "3": "either", "4": "whether", "answer": "both", "question": "Our store offers a complete line of computer software packages for ___ personal and business applications."}, "1988": {"1": "increase", "2": "impression", "3": "access", "4": "accent", "answer": "increase", "question": "According to the commerce report released today, retail sales in apparel declined in August after a significant ___ in July."}, "1989": {"1": "regretful", "2": "regretfully", "3": "regretting", "4": "regretted", "answer": "regretfully", "question": "The president of Tennom Advertising ___ announces the cancellation of plans to open an office in Toronto."}, "1990": {"1": "remain", "2": "serve", "3": "grant", "4": "provide", "answer": "provide", "question": "The International Society of Economists will ___ leadership to develop and launch a collection of electronic journals."}, "1991": {"1": "to discontinue", "2": "will discontinue", "3": "discontinued", "4": "have discontinued", "answer": "will discontinue", "question": "After the current model year, the automobile manufacturer CFG ___ three older models and introduce two new ones."}, "1992": {"1": "before", "2": "until", "3": "from", "4": "during", "answer": "before", "question": "Personnel must sign the register ___ removing any confidential papers from the organization's vaults."}, "1993": {"1": "displayed", "2": "displaying", "3": "display", "4": "displays", "answer": "displaying", "question": "In addition to ___ recent phone numbers, the new IF20 mobile phone shows the temperature, the time, and the user's location on a map."}, "1994": {"1": "based", "2": "intended", "3": "agreed", "4": "invited", "answer": "intended", "question": "Tomorrow's training is ___ for employees who have been with the company for less than one year."}, "1995": {"1": "if", "2": "why", "3": "due to", "4": "about", "answer": "if", "question": "Tenants should call the property owner directly ___ problems with heating or plumbing are not resolved by the on-site manager."}, "1996": {"1": "Soon", "2": "Then", "3": "Later", "4": "Once", "answer": "Once", "question": "___ the probationary three months are completed, employees will be eligible for full company benefits."}, "1997": {"1": "nominate", "2": "nominations", "3": "nominating", "4": "to have nominated", "answer": "nominations", "question": "Tappan Literature Foundation is soliciting ___ for this year's best youth novelist."}, "1998": {"1": "economies", "2": "harvest", "3": "measures", "4": "productivity", "answer": "productivity", "question": "The new graphic design software program has improved the quality of the designers' work as well as their ___ ."}, "1999": {"1": "whoever", "2": "whom", "3": "what", "4": "where", "answer": "whom", "question": "The names of the department heads to ___ the monthly reports should be sent are located on the last page of the manual."}, "2000": {"1": "equal", "2": "uniform", "3": "even", "4": "fair", "answer": "equal", "question": "Sinna Motors' sales figures this year were nearly ___ to those recorded in the company's most successful period five years ago."}, "2001": {"1": "predominant", "2": "predominantly", "3": "predominating", "4": "predominated", "answer": "predominantly", "question": "NJC Surveys recently determined that, despite advances in audio technology, it is still ___ through radio broadcasts that listeners are exposed to new music."}, "2002": {"1": "schedule", "2": "scheduled", "3": "schedules", "4": "schedulers", "answer": "schedule", "question": "The ___ for the MacNeill project is hanging on the wall in the first floor conference room."}, "2003": {"1": "changed", "2": "painted", "3": "alternated", "4": "transferred", "answer": "painted", "question": "When Howland Bakery first began using larger trucks for delivery, all of them were ___ white and brown."}, "2004": {"1": "cautious", "2": "caution", "3": "cautiously", "4": "cautiousness", "answer": "cautious", "question": "Staff members who work with chemicals should remember to be ___ and always wear protective gear in the lab."}, "2005": {"1": "or", "2": "nor", "3": "and", "4": "neither", "answer": "nor", "question": "Neither taking photographs ___ eating is allowed in the theater."}, "2006": {"1": "clearness", "2": "clear", "3": "clearly", "4": "clearest", "answer": "clearly", "question": "The display panel has been designed to ensure that the warning lights are ___ visible."}, "2007": {"1": "over", "2": "behind", "3": "within", "4": "down", "answer": "behind", "question": "Even after the stadium's renovation, some seats remain ___ pillars that partially obstruct the view."}, "2008": {"1": "finish", "2": "finishing", "3": "finished", "4": "be finished", "answer": "finish", "question": "In order to ___ the editing work, the review team will need at least two more days."}, "2009": {"1": "limited", "2": "speedy", "3": "available", "4": "presentable", "answer": "limited", "question": "Because our supplies are ___ , we can only make this offer to the first fifty customers who come to the store."}, "2010": {"1": "agrees", "2": "agreement", "3": "agreements", "4": "agreed", "answer": "agreement", "question": "Polabian Bank signed an ___ for the financing of the A2 highway connecting Bistrica and Nove Pola."}, "2011": {"1": "quickly", "2": "currently", "3": "precisely", "4": "temperately", "answer": "currently", "question": "Due to technical problems, Nelson's Electronic Auctions is ___ not accepting any picture submissions via e-mail."}, "2012": {"1": "us", "2": "we", "3": "our", "4": "ourselves", "answer": "we", "question": "In order for Mr. Song's group to complete the data collection project on time, ___ will need even more administrative support."}, "2013": {"1": "recalled", "2": "memorized", "3": "reminded", "4": "identified", "answer": "reminded", "question": "To avoid leaving anyone behind, the tour operator ___ all the visitors to be in the front lobby by 7 A.M."}, "2014": {"1": "are", "2": "is", "3": "been", "4": "being", "answer": "are", "question": "Please use the color printer sparingly, since the ink cartridges it requires ___ currently unavailable."}, "2015": {"1": "policy", "2": "adoption", "3": "exhibit", "4": "regard", "answer": "policy", "question": "Our ___ is not to offer refunds to customers unless they return the item, accompanied by a receipt, within 30 days of the purchase date."}, "2016": {"1": "exceptionally", "2": "exception", "3": "exceptional", "4": "except", "answer": "exceptionally", "question": "The students enrolled in the painting course at the Model Art School have worked ___ hard over the past year."}, "2017": {"1": "toward", "2": "among", "3": "after", "4": "during", "answer": "among", "question": "The faculty committee will distribute funds from the research grant ___ its various science departments."}, "2018": {"1": "if", "2": "since", "3": "how", "4": "than", "answer": "since", "question": "Arten Publishing has experienced an average annual growth of over 7 percent in sales ___ it went public twenty years ago."}, "2019": {"1": "technician", "2": "factory", "3": "certificate", "4": "generator", "answer": "technician", "question": "The fax machine is out of service, and an experienced ___ has been called in to see if it can be repaired."}, "2020": {"1": "them", "2": "they", "3": "its", "4": "itself", "answer": "its", "question": "With ___ new building and expanded hours. First Bank of Stubenville is once again ahead of the competition."}, "2021": {"1": "notify", "2": "assign", "3": "permit", "4": "present", "answer": "present", "question": "We require all visitors to ___ photo identification prior to entering the building."}, "2022": {"1": "complete", "2": "completes", "3": "completed", "4": "completely", "answer": "completely", "question": "Employment applications must be filled out ___ before being submitted to J&J Enterprises."}, "2023": {"1": "chaired", "2": "reserved", "3": "substituted", "4": "performed", "answer": "reserved", "question": "Workshop participants may choose any seat in the auditorium except those in the front row, which are ___ for the presenters."}, "2024": {"1": "until", "2": "then", "3": "before", "4": "because", "answer": "before", "question": "Any employee working late on a Friday must remember to turn off all computer equipment ___ leaving for the night."}, "2025": {"1": "importance", "2": "right", "3": "goal", "4": "selection", "answer": "right", "question": "Super Discounts, Inc., reserves the ___ to limit quantities of certain sale items purchased by each customer."}, "2026": {"1": "defect", "2": "defective", "3": "defects", "4": "defectively", "answer": "defective", "question": "Hatfield Sporting Goods returned the ___ merchandise to the manufacturer."}, "2027": {"1": "expired", "2": "handled", "3": "replied", "4": "attended", "answer": "handled", "question": "While the accounting department is closed, all billing questions will be ___ by the customer service department."}, "2028": {"1": "rigor", "2": "rigors", "3": "rigorous", "4": "rigorously", "answer": "rigorously", "question": "The executive board sent out a reminder to division heads that all contracts must be ___ reviewed by the legal department before they are signed."}, "2029": {"1": "across", "2": "beside", "3": "with", "4": "from", "answer": "with", "question": "Next to the Rostovsky Hotel is a luxurious recreational area, complete ___ a golf course and a swimming pool."}, "2030": {"1": "submitting", "2": "submit", "3": "submitted", "4": "submission", "answer": "submitted", "question": "All orders for office supplies must be ___ to Ms. Reaton by Thursday at noon."}, "2031": {"1": "since", "2": "soon", "3": "yet", "4": "finally", "answer": "finally", "question": "After three years of intense negotiation, Megali Corporation and Liggman Industries have ___ agreed on the terms of their merger."}, "2032": {"1": "enclose", "2": "enclosed", "3": "enclosing", "4": "enclosure", "answer": "enclosed", "question": "Please accept the ___ coupon book as thanks for opening your personal savings account with South Branch Bank."}, "2033": {"1": "variable", "2": "apparent", "3": "redundant", "4": "comprehensive", "answer": "comprehensive", "question": "Baxter Consulting intends to combine information from various sources in order to provide a single ___ directory of local businesses."}, "2034": {"1": "accommodation", "2": "accommodates", "3": "accommodate", "4": "accommodating", "answer": "accommodate", "question": "In order to ___ overseas clients, the Majeski Group will open offices in both Europe and Asia."}, "2035": {"1": "promptly", "2": "vocally", "3": "openly", "4": "neutrally", "answer": "promptly", "question": "The training class on Internet security begins ___ at 8:00 A.M. and ends at 5:00 P.M., with a one-hour break for lunch."}, "2036": {"1": "benefit", "2": "benefits", "3": "benefitting", "4": "beneficial", "answer": "beneficial", "question": "Many of our employees have reported that they have found the new computer program to be quite ___ ."}, "2037": {"1": "meaning", "2": "belief", "3": "excursion", "4": "abstract", "answer": "abstract", "question": "Research grant proposals must be submitted by next Friday and should include a budget and a one-page ___ ."}, "2038": {"1": "performing", "2": "performed", "3": "performer", "4": "performance", "answer": "performance", "question": "The GSX offers exceptional ___ while still achieving a fuel efficiency rating better than that of most other vehicles in its class."}, "2039": {"1": "selective", "2": "expressive", "3": "definitive", "4": "competitive", "answer": "definitive", "question": "Because it covers nearly every aspect of French cooking, the Bleu School Guide is considered the ___ resource for preparing authentic French cuisine."}, "2040": {"1": "nears", "2": "nearing", "3": "nearly", "4": "neared", "answer": "nearly", "question": "Judges for the science competition stated that choosing a winner from the finalists was a ___ impossible task."}, "2041": {"1": "as if", "2": "whereas", "3": "whether", "4": "assuming that", "answer": "assuming that", "question": "The company's revenue during the next quarter will increase, ___ the lucrative contract with Kang Securities can be finalized before next month."}, "2042": {"1": "in", "2": "by", "3": "from", "4": "with", "answer": "with", "question": "As you instructed, we have enclosed the damaged merchandise together ___ a written request for a full refund."}, "2043": {"1": "special", "2": "specialize", "3": "specially", "4": "specializing", "answer": "special", "question": "Mr. Matthews, a reporter for the International Daily newspaper, will be on ___ assignment until further notice."}, "2044": {"1": "sent", "2": "arrived", "3": "delayed", "4": "examined", "answer": "arrived", "question": "The August shipment has just ___ from Busan and is waiting in the receiving dock."}, "2045": {"1": "wrong", "2": "wronging", "3": "wrongly", "4": "wronged", "answer": "wrongly", "question": "Before the situation was explained to him. Franco ___ believed that the automobile prototype was the finished product."}, "2046": {"1": "deduct", "2": "deducted", "3": "deduction", "4": "deducting", "answer": "deducted", "question": "The advertisement said that 20 percent would be ___ from the regular price at the time of purchase."}, "2047": {"1": "he", "2": "him", "3": "himself", "4": "his", "answer": "him", "question": "Mr. Adams will not be able to complete the report by himself and would appreciate it if someone would volunteer to help ___ ."}, "2048": {"1": "significantly", "2": "currently", "3": "completely", "4": "slightly", "answer": "currently", "question": "___ We are seeking volunteers to participate in an upcoming consumer research study for Mayfee Marketing,"}, "2049": {"1": "If", "2": "So", "3": "Unless", "4": "Since", "answer": "Since", "question": "___ she loves animals, Ms. Peters is a technician at the Eldridge Veterinary Center."}, "2050": {"1": "instead of", "2": "no later than", "3": "although", "4": "otherwise", "answer": "no later than", "question": "All members of the design team are expected to submit their completed drafts to Ms. Conroy ___ next Friday."}, "2051": {"1": "safety", "2": "safe", "3": "safely", "4": "safer", "answer": "safety", "question": "For reasons of ___ , anyone entering the construction area must wear a hard hat."}, "2052": {"1": "greatly", "2": "unusually", "3": "especially", "4": "positively", "answer": "especially", "question": "Hua Husing's achievements in biochemistry were remarkable, ___ considering that he was only twenty-six at the time."}, "2053": {"1": "their", "2": "theirs", "3": "they", "4": "themselves", "answer": "their", "question": "Drivers are asked to park ___ cars within the white lines."}, "2054": {"1": "recognition", "2": "accomplishment", "3": "capability", "4": "balance", "answer": "recognition", "question": "Ms. Kushida's managers feel that she deserves special ___ for her performance in the last sales campaign."}, "2055": {"1": "clear", "2": "clearly", "3": "clearing", "4": "clearness", "answer": "clear", "question": "Financial experts note that the mild weather in the last few years has had a ___ effect on agricultural productivity."}, "2056": {"1": "describe", "2": "include", "3": "contain", "4": "involve", "answer": "include", "question": "Please remember to ___ your account number and signature on all payment checks."}, "2057": {"1": "compares", "2": "comparing", "3": "comparison", "4": "comparable", "answer": "comparable", "question": "Although the two computer processors differ in price, they are ___ in terms of their quality."}, "2058": {"1": "division", "2": "category", "3": "selection", "4": "separation", "answer": "division", "question": "The Cornwall Times is published weekly by OYC Newspapers, Inc., a ___ of Woodbridge Media Holdings."}, "2059": {"1": "fast", "2": "about", "3": "closely", "4": "fairly", "answer": "about", "question": "Dr. Kim's acceptance speech is expected to last ___ ten minutes, after which dessert will be served."}, "2060": {"1": "recovered", "2": "recover", "3": "recovering", "4": "recovery", "answer": "recovered", "question": "Our office secretary had made a backup of the computer files, so the information was ___ successfully after the power failure."}, "2061": {"1": "remove", "2": "oppose", "3": "prevent", "4": "forbid", "answer": "prevent", "question": "All commercial catering businesses refrigerate perishable food to ___ it from spoiling."}, "2062": {"1": "accomplished", "2": "illustrated", "3": "observed", "4": "influenced", "answer": "accomplished", "question": "LTD Enterprises is currently seeking an ___ individual to replace the current director, who will be retiring at the end of the month."}, "2063": {"1": "bring", "2": "be brought", "3": "brought", "4": "bringing", "answer": "be brought", "question": "Due to new restrictions on international travelers, certain types of plants cannot ___ into most countries without a permit."}, "2064": {"1": "elaborating", "2": "useful", "3": "tracking", "4": "increasing", "answer": "increasing", "question": "In order to keep up with the ___ demand for our products, we will have to hire a minimum of four additional workers."}, "2065": {"1": "habit", "2": "adoption", "3": "trade", "4": "reservation", "answer": "adoption", "question": "The ___ of the new inventory process has had a significant impact on our management of resources."}, "2066": {"1": "secure", "2": "more secure", "3": "securely", "4": "security", "answer": "securely", "question": "All loose objects, such as bags and laptop computers, must be placed ___ in the overhead bins prior to takeoff."}, "2067": {"1": "Into", "2": "Upon", "3": "About", "4": "During", "answer": "During", "question": "___ her time at the university, Dr. LeFleur built a solid reputation for leadership among both students and faculty."}, "2068": {"1": "While", "2": "That", "3": "Either", "4": "Even", "answer": "While", "question": "___ Ms. Fukui is willing to continue working part-time, she hopes to be offered full-time employment eventually."}, "2069": {"1": "encourage", "2": "encourages", "3": "encouraged", "4": "encouraging", "answer": "encouraging", "question": "It is ___ to hear that our sales department has started to pursue overseas markets aggressively."}, "2070": {"1": "conduct", "2": "principle", "3": "character", "4": "order", "answer": "principle", "question": "Genter Electronics has always followed the ___ that the risk involved in developing new technology is one that is worth taking."}, "2071": {"1": "it", "2": "both", "3": "that", "4": "which", "answer": "both", "question": "The home sales and rental markets should strengthen soon, as ___ usually benefit when the local economy improves."}, "2072": {"1": "regard", "2": "appear", "3": "follow", "4": "anticipate", "answer": "anticipate", "question": "I do not ___ that the shipment schedule will change when our factories relocate, but if it does, I will notify you immediately."}, "2073": {"1": "On behalf of", "2": "With regard to", "3": "In order to", "4": "In hopes of", "answer": "In order to", "question": "___ maintain a stable production facility for the next ten years, Vartacorp is currently negotiating access to new computer technologies."}, "2074": {"1": "receipt", "2": "admission", "3": "ownership", "4": "membership", "answer": "receipt", "question": "All resumes submitted to our human resources department will remain on record for one year from the date of ___ ."}, "2075": {"1": "has been starting", "2": "will be starting", "3": "was started", "4": "is being started", "answer": "will be starting", "question": "We are pleased to announce that Ms. Vieri ___ her new position as market analyst on September 30."}, "2076": {"1": "specific", "2": "specify", "3": "specification", "4": "specifically", "answer": "specifically", "question": "We may share your mailing address with our subsidiaries for marketing purposes unless you ___ request in writing that we not do so."}, "2077": {"1": "immediate", "2": "imperative", "3": "ultimate", "4": "conclusive", "answer": "imperative", "question": "It is ___ - that the documents be meticulously examined before they are sent out to clients."}, "2078": {"1": "elementary", "2": "element", "3": "elements", "4": "elemental", "answer": "element", "question": "A key ___ still missing from the upcoming presentation to the client is an estimate of the total project cost."}, "2079": {"1": "as long as", "2": "whereas", "3": "so does", "4": "as to", "answer": "so does", "question": "As the number of local residents' visits to public swimming facilities climbs, ___ the demand for lifeguards to supervise them."}, "2080": {"1": "honored", "2": "achieved", "3": "took", "4": "won", "answer": "won", "question": "It was Joanne Huber's groundbreaking work on the photoelectric effect that ___ her the lifetime excellence award."}, "2081": {"1": "affiliate", "2": "affiliated", "3": "affiliating", "4": "affiliates", "answer": "affiliates", "question": "Neither Kato Business Service nor any of its ___ are responsible for the accuracy of this brochure."}, "2082": {"1": "use", "2": "using", "3": "used", "4": "will use", "answer": "using", "question": "Travelers ___ the local airport in Hopkins complain that there is an urgent need for more parking."}, "2083": {"1": "respond", "2": "appoint", "3": "reserve", "4": "connect", "answer": "reserve", "question": "In order to ___ a table for the luncheon, we need to call the cafe by noon."}, "2084": {"1": "she", "2": "her", "3": "hers", "4": "herself", "answer": "her", "question": "The younger staff look up to Ms. Itoh because of ___ years of experience in the field of multimedia and graphic design."}, "2085": {"1": "Whether", "2": "Despite", "3": "If", "4": "For", "answer": "If", "question": "___ you wish to see a complete list of hotel amenities, please refer to the informational binder on the desk in your guest room."}, "2086": {"1": "precisely", "2": "preciseness", "3": "precise", "4": "precision", "answer": "precisely", "question": "The financial briefing for our investors will begin ___ at 9:30 A.M. on Thursday."}, "2087": {"1": "dependent", "2": "withheld", "3": "stringent", "4": "founded", "answer": "stringent", "question": "Falco Brand engine parts are put through a ___ inspection process."}, "2088": {"1": "determine", "2": "determines", "3": "determining", "4": "determination", "answer": "determine", "question": "After thoroughly reviewing all of the resumes, we will ___ which candidates to interview."}, "2089": {"1": "facilities", "2": "qualities", "3": "conventions", "4": "categories", "answer": "facilities", "question": "Tower Apartments plans to add a recreation complex that will accommodate a swimming pool and other ___ ."}, "2090": {"1": "requires", "2": "requirements", "3": "require", "4": "requiring", "answer": "requirements", "question": "Unfortunately, the newly manufactured electronic components do not meet the quality ___ of Gem Associates."}, "2091": {"1": "all", "2": "very", "3": "any", "4": "even", "answer": "even", "question": "For the period ending June 30, the Horizon Stadium Corporation recorded unprecedented revenues from ticket sales, and ___ more from advertising."}, "2092": {"1": "favorable", "2": "favorably", "3": "favor", "4": "favorite", "answer": "favorable", "question": "Under more ___ circumstances, the board of trustees would have approved the budget increase, but this year it was not possible."}, "2093": {"1": "in", "2": "for", "3": "over", "4": "from", "answer": "for", "question": "Daniel will be checking the report ___ mistakes before it is submitted to the group manager."}, "2094": {"1": "itself", "2": "herself", "3": "themselves", "4": "himself", "answer": "himself", "question": "Mr. Shin updated the company's Web site by ___ because the other programmer had a problem with her password."}, "2095": {"1": "attend", "2": "perform", "3": "express", "4": "represent", "answer": "represent", "question": "Beginning August 1, Carla Frist will ___ the company as its attorney in all dealings with the local government."}, "2096": {"1": "happier", "2": "happily", "3": "happiest", "4": "happy", "answer": "happy", "question": "Ms. Chu was extremely ___ to receive the award for outstanding sales performance."}, "2097": {"1": "Unless", "2": "Also", "3": "Except", "4": "Therefore", "answer": "Unless", "question": "___ something is done, traffic congestion on the Winfield Parkway will continue to worsen."}, "2098": {"1": "negotiates", "2": "negotiations", "3": "negotiator", "4": "negotiable", "answer": "negotiations", "question": "Mr. Shmidov hired two lawyers to help with future contract ___ ."}, "2099": {"1": "original", "2": "estimated", "3": "sincere", "4": "completed", "answer": "sincere", "question": "Please accept our ___ thanks for the fine work you are doing in our sales department."}, "2100": {"1": "prompt", "2": "promptly", "3": "prompted", "4": "prompting", "answer": "promptly", "question": "Any changes in your tax status should be reported to the payroll division ___ so that corrections can be made in a timely fashion."}, "2101": {"1": "speak", "2": "notify", "3": "report", "4": "attend", "answer": "notify", "question": "Please check in with Ms. Nakamura's assistant when you arrive so he can ___ her of your arrival."}, "2102": {"1": "what", "2": "how", "3": "when", "4": "which", "answer": "what", "question": "Jenkins Business Review has asked thousands of people in a wide range of professions to describe ___ their jobs entail."}, "2103": {"1": "Since", "2": "While", "3": "Once", "4": "Because", "answer": "Since", "question": "___ receiving notice that the director of the Deerfield Orchestra will retire, the board of directors has been searching for a replacement."}, "2104": {"1": "more easily", "2": "easiest", "3": "most easily", "4": "easy", "answer": "easiest", "question": "Of the subway lines that stop in the central business district, the green line is the ___ to walk to from the Franklin Building."}, "2105": {"1": "outside", "2": "starting on", "3": "afterward", "4": "instead of", "answer": "starting on", "question": "Employees of Reconnaissance Corporation who share rides to work will be eligible for special parking privileges ___ Wednesday."}, "2106": {"1": "meet", "2": "met", "3": "have met", "4": "will meet", "answer": "meet", "question": "The senior project manager will be on-site next Thursday and has requested that the editors ___ him in his office at 9:30 A.M."}, "2107": {"1": "of", "2": "under", "3": "at", "4": "in", "answer": "in", "question": "All hair-care products will be 25 percent off this week ___ celebration of Trey Salon's fifth anniversary."}, "2108": {"1": "opens", "2": "openings", "3": "openness", "4": "opener", "answer": "openings", "question": "The Manila Wellness Center has part-time and temporary employment ___ for certified nursing attendants in our Makati branch."}, "2109": {"1": "continuous", "2": "prosperous", "3": "mature", "4": "straight", "answer": "continuous", "question": "Companies need to provide year-round training to technical support staff due to ___ improvements in technology."}, "2110": {"1": "finance", "2": "finances", "3": "financial", "4": "financially", "answer": "financially", "question": "Residents argue that another new shopping center in the heart of the city is not ___ sound."}, "2111": {"1": "economy", "2": "retail", "3": "market", "4": "discount", "answer": "discount", "question": "Metropolitan Herald, the city's leading newspaper, is offering new customers a twenty percent ___ ."}, "2112": {"1": "yours", "2": "yourself", "3": "your own", "4": "you", "answer": "your own", "question": "Answering customer questions is sometimes difficult to do on ___ , so we have created a list of frequently asked questions."}, "2113": {"1": "to", "2": "by", "3": "along", "4": "in", "answer": "to", "question": "Maria Gomez submitted her plan for the new transit system ___ the city's board of directors for review."}, "2114": {"1": "schedule", "2": "appointment", "3": "authority", "4": "condition", "answer": "schedule", "question": "Although our employees did not write the correct address on the shipping form, the machine parts arrived at the dairy farm on ___ ."}, "2115": {"1": "will accompany", "2": "accompanying", "3": "to accompany", "4": "accompanied", "answer": "accompanied", "question": "A thunderstorm ___ by gusty winds is expected to arrive in the northeast region by late afternoon."}, "2116": {"1": "confirm", "2": "confirming", "3": "confirmation", "4": "confirmed", "answer": "confirmation", "question": "Mr. Garcia called earlier today for ___ that the package he sent on Monday had been received."}, "2117": {"1": "repeated", "2": "repeating", "3": "repetition", "4": "repeatedly", "answer": "repeated", "question": "After ___ requests by local residents, the private library was opened to the public."}, "2118": {"1": "barely", "2": "highly", "3": "gradually", "4": "necessarily", "answer": "necessarily", "question": "Advertisements placed by merchants in The Weekly Roundup do not ___ imply endorsement by the management of the newspaper."}, "2119": {"1": "states", "2": "marks", "3": "points", "4": "records", "answer": "records", "question": "Sanford Electronics recently installed a new data management system to keep better ___ of customers' orders."}, "2120": {"1": "under", "2": "within", "3": "directly", "4": "only", "answer": "within", "question": "When using the building's side entrance, remember that an alarm will sound if your security code is not entered on the keypad ___ 30 seconds."}, "2121": {"1": "minor", "2": "lower", "3": "partial", "4": "limited", "answer": "limited", "question": "The Gallo Museum's display of Mexican silver crafts will remain open for a ___ time only."}, "2122": {"1": "him", "2": "himself", "3": "he", "4": "his", "answer": "him", "question": "Mr. Kato left the hotel's telephone number with the airport staff so they could notify ___ when the luggage is found."}, "2123": {"1": "unless", "2": "both", "3": "either", "4": "without", "answer": "either", "question": "Conference participants can get to the Wyatt Hotel ___ by train or by bus."}, "2124": {"1": "reviews", "2": "reviewed", "3": "reviewer", "4": "reviewers", "answer": "reviews", "question": "Please be aware that annual ___ of job performance will take place during the third week of January."}, "2125": {"1": "decide", "2": "continue", "3": "attend", "4": "regard", "answer": "attend", "question": "As of January 1, all managers will be required to ___ at least three professional development seminars per year."}, "2126": {"1": "simple", "2": "frequent", "3": "common", "4": "eager", "answer": "eager", "question": "Gryphon Solutions is a growing computer support company ___ to expand its business in East Asia."}, "2127": {"1": "specific", "2": "specifics", "3": "specify", "4": "specifying", "answer": "specific", "question": "We have been given ___ instructions on how Ms. Crane wants this task to be completed."}, "2128": {"1": "also", "2": "than", "3": "moreover", "4": "while", "answer": "while", "question": "Mario DAmico has been assigned to check the facts ___ Sean McCree types a draft of the report."}, "2129": {"1": "themselves", "2": "them", "3": "their", "4": "they", "answer": "they", "question": "The mechanics became more efficient as ___ began using the new technology."}, "2130": {"1": "honor", "2": "ovation", "3": "expression", "4": "invitation", "answer": "invitation", "question": "Mr. Ortega has received an ___ to attend the awards ceremony in Brussels next month."}, "2131": {"1": "anticipates", "2": "anticipating", "3": "anticipation", "4": "to anticipate", "answer": "anticipates", "question": "The Milestone Corporation ___ significant revenue increases in several major metropolitan areas over the next decade."}, "2132": {"1": "attract", "2": "value", "3": "capture", "4": "observe", "answer": "attract", "question": "The new science museum is expected to ___ many tourists to the city."}, "2133": {"1": "complete", "2": "completing", "3": "completely", "4": "completion", "answer": "completely", "question": "Mr. Perlmutter has assured the management team that the prototype will be ___ functional by June 9."}, "2134": {"1": "owing", "2": "due", "3": "payable", "4": "mature", "answer": "due", "question": "As of October 1, all books borrowed from the Queenstown Library will be ___ three weeks from the checkout date."}, "2135": {"1": "she", "2": "her", "3": "hers", "4": "herself", "answer": "her", "question": "After her retirement, Lillian will certainly be missed by the numerous colleagues who have benefited from ___ steady judgment in the field of finance."}, "2136": {"1": "merit", "2": "service", "3": "advantage", "4": "improvement", "answer": "advantage", "question": "To take ___ of the company's free software-upgrade program, customers should mail a copy of their receipt to the address provided."}, "2137": {"1": "necessary", "2": "necessarily", "3": "necessity", "4": "necessitating", "answer": "necessary", "question": "Passengers should have all ___ boarding documents ready to present to airline personnel."}, "2138": {"1": "However", "2": "During", "3": "Because", "4": "Yet", "answer": "Because", "question": "___ the order was placed after the sale had ended, no discount will be given."}, "2139": {"1": "interview", "2": "interviews", "3": "interviewing", "4": "interviewed", "answer": "interviewing", "question": "Ms. Baxter would like to meet with all members of the hiring committee again after ___ candidates."}, "2140": {"1": "control", "2": "center", "3": "look", "4": "need", "answer": "need", "question": "The environmental commission concluded that there is a ___ for immediate funding to repair the dam."}, "2141": {"1": "remarks", "2": "remarkably", "3": "remarkable", "4": "remarked", "answer": "remarkably", "question": "The quality of the furniture designed at Oak Valley Company has remained ___ consistent for the  years that the firm has operated."}, "2142": {"1": "respond", "2": "benefit", "3": "commute", "4": "deliver", "answer": "deliver", "question": "Ms. Ishimura generously offered to ___ the invitation in person rather than send it through the mail."}, "2143": {"1": "cautious", "2": "cautiously", "3": "cautioning", "4": "caution", "answer": "cautious", "question": "Mr. Jefferson has a reputation for taking risks, but his coworkers describe him as reasonably ___ in most aspects of his job."}, "2144": {"1": "at", "2": "by", "3": "over", "4": "from", "answer": "at", "question": "Club members are allowed to attend the Healthy Living seminar ___ no cost."}, "2145": {"1": "chances", "2": "results", "3": "matters", "4": "events", "answer": "results", "question": "On Thursday, Ms. Cornado should receive the of the ___ recent survey conducted by the research and development department."}, "2146": {"1": "discuss", "2": "discussion", "3": "discussing", "4": "discussed", "answer": "discussed", "question": "As ___ in our telephone conversation this morning, Mr. Fox will arrive at your factory at 2 P.M. on Wednesday, March 14."}, "2147": {"1": "receive", "2": "inquire", "3": "grant", "4": "retain", "answer": "retain", "question": "Swabian Motors will ___ its current name even after it merges with a rival company."}, "2148": {"1": "it", "2": "anyone", "3": "yourself", "4": "theirs", "answer": "anyone", "question": "The business consultant stressed that long-term planning is an important consideration for ___ doing business internationally."}, "2149": {"1": "capable", "2": "variable", "3": "flexible", "4": "eligible", "answer": "eligible", "question": "According to company guidelines, new employees are ___ to receive vacation benefits after three months of full-time employment."}, "2150": {"1": "desire", "2": "desiring", "3": "desirably", "4": "desirable", "answer": "desirable", "question": "Maxwell Real Estate is pleased to announce that prime retail space is now available in two highly ___ properties located in midtown Springfield."}, "2151": {"1": "across", "2": "between", "3": "throughout", "4": "among", "answer": "throughout", "question": "Please make every effort to welcome the new trainees as you encounter them ___ the next few weeks."}, "2152": {"1": "precautions", "2": "rules", "3": "abilities", "4": "guidelines", "answer": "precautions", "question": "Safety ___ must be taken by all laboratory employees while working with chemicals that are potentially harmful."}, "2153": {"1": "regard", "2": "regards", "3": "regarding", "4": "regarded", "answer": "regarding", "question": "Please contact Ms. Blackwell in the personnel office if you have not received information ___ company reimbursement procedures."}, "2154": {"1": "exclusively", "2": "impulsively", "3": "mutually", "4": "generously", "answer": "exclusively", "question": "Jane Wiseman has her own publishing company dealing almost ___ with biographies."}, "2155": {"1": "dlstinguishably", "2": "distinguishability", "3": "distinguished", "4": "distinguish", "answer": "distinguished", "question": "Enclosed is the latest listing of the ___ companies and institutions that use our firm's specialized consulting services."}, "2156": {"1": "on", "2": "as", "3": "by", "4": "to", "answer": "as", "question": "Deal Travel, inc., acts ___ an agent for the vacation products presented in the brochure."}, "2157": {"1": "components", "2": "importance", "3": "agreement", "4": "concerns", "answer": "concerns", "question": "A tax expert will come to our company tomorrow to respond to any ___ you have about recent changes in the law."}, "2158": {"1": "complain", "2": "complaining", "3": "complainer", "4": "complaints", "answer": "complaints", "question": "Our service department has received numerous ___ about the new TZ- processor overheating."}, "2159": {"1": "Almost", "2": "Nevertheless", "3": "Seldom", "4": "However", "answer": "However", "question": "___ uncomfortable they may be, helmets, goggles, and gloves absolutely must be worn by anyone entering the construction zone."}, "2160": {"1": "evaluate", "2": "persuade", "3": "object", "4": "compensate", "answer": "evaluate", "question": "In order for US to ___ Ms. Brown's suitability as a candidate, she has been asked to supply several letters of reference."}, "2161": {"1": "approve", "2": "approvingly", "3": "approving", "4": "approval", "answer": "approval", "question": "All advertising at the National Textile and Garment Convention is subject to ___ by the board of directors."}, "2162": {"1": "through", "2": "along", "3": "up", "4": "to", "answer": "up", "question": "Try and be a little more cheerful because if you don't bear ___soon, you'll make everyone else miserable."}, "2163": {"1": "down", "2": "across", "3": "over", "4": "under", "answer": "down", "question": "We were in a small rowing boat and were terrified that the steamer hadn't seen us as it was bearing ___onus."}, "2164": {"1": "brain", "2": "mind", "3": "thought", "4": "sense", "answer": "mind", "question": "I fully understand your comments and bearing those in___, I have made the appropriate decision."}, "2165": {"1": "produce", "2": "benefits", "3": "yields", "4": "fruit", "answer": "fruit", "question": "As we have all worked very hard this year, I'm hoping that our efforts will bear ___"}, "2166": {"1": "problems", "2": "situations", "3": "crosses", "4": "results", "answer": "crosses", "question": "We all have our ___to bear so I should be grateful if you would stop complaining all the time."}, "2167": {"1": "scorn", "2": "grin", "3": "laugh", "4": "smile", "answer": "grin", "question": "There is really nothing much you can do to stop it and I'm afraid you'll just have to___ and bear it."}, "2168": {"1": "by", "2": "on", "3": "at", "4": "with", "answer": "with", "question": "I hope you can be patient for a little longer and bear ___me while I try and solve the problem."}, "2169": {"1": "out", "2": "to", "3": "for", "4": "onto", "answer": "out", "question": "She has been proved right in everything she did as the report quite clearly bears ___."}, "2170": {"1": "to", "2": "on", "3": "into", "4": "by", "answer": "on", "question": "The judge dismissed the new evidence completely because it had no bearing ___the trial."}, "2171": {"1": "confirmation", "2": "contrast", "3": "comprehension", "4": "comparison", "answer": "comparison", "question": "Quite honestly the two cases are so completely different that they really don't bear ___"}, "2172": {"1": "acquired", "2": "got", "3": "attained", "4": "controlled", "answer": "attained", "question": "CinemasHer latest film ___its object in a very short space of time, which was to shock."}, "2173": {"1": "run", "2": "continue", "3": "persist", "4": "insist", "answer": "continue", "question": "The critics ___to praise the work of this director whatever films he makes."}, "2174": {"1": "influence", "2": "hold", "3": "infect", "4": "show", "answer": "influence", "question": "The film was the first to show conditions in which poor people lived and as such was to ___future directors."}, "2175": {"1": "internment", "2": "involvement", "3": "engrossment", "4": "entertainment", "answer": "entertainment", "question": "The only reason for them going to the cinema on that day was to find some form of ___"}, "2176": {"1": "report", "2": "reprehend", "3": "represent", "4": "comprehend", "answer": "represent", "question": "The director's intention in making the film was to try and ___simplicity as seen by a child."}, "2177": {"1": "dispose", "2": "displace", "3": "discover", "4": "disperse", "answer": "disperse", "question": "The fans outside the cinema on the first showing of the film were unwilling to ___until all the stars had gonehome."}, "2178": {"1": "replacing", "2": "repeating", "3": "releasing", "4": "reporting", "answer": "releasing", "question": "The delay in ___the film to the general public was because certain scenes were considered tasteless."}, "2179": {"1": "construction", "2": "continuation", "3": "continuum", "4": "continuing", "answer": "continuation", "question": "The theme of the second film is quite simply a___ of the first."}, "2180": {"1": "separate", "2": "separation", "3": "separately", "4": "separates", "answer": "separate", "question": "In the making of the film the direction is quite ___from the financing of the project."}, "2181": {"1": "describing", "2": "describes", "3": "described", "4": "description", "answer": "description", "question": "Very often someone will give a ___of a film and when you see it for yourself, it's quite different."}, "2182": {"1": "4", "2": "5", "3": "6", "4": "7", "answer": "7", "question": "ClichesShe's got the kind of job that seems to keep her occupied all the time  24-___"}, "2183": {"1": "Totally", "2": "Clearly", "3": "Finally", "4": "Absolutely", "answer": "Absolutely", "question": "___, I couldn't agree with you more."}, "2184": {"1": "advise", "2": "speak", "3": "address", "4": "talk", "answer": "address", "question": "I really think we should talk about the subject we wanted to in the first place and ___the issue."}, "2185": {"1": "around", "2": "across", "3": "through", "4": "into", "answer": "around", "question": "It's difficult to say exactly how many people are involved but I would say ___."}, "2186": {"1": "fine", "2": "awesome", "3": "interesting", "4": "clear", "answer": "awesome", "question": "It was one of those sights that you never forget it was___"}, "2187": {"1": "ball field", "2": "ball place", "3": "ball park", "4": "ball game", "answer": "ball park", "question": "We don't know precisely how much it will cost but I could give a ___figure of 6 million dollars."}, "2188": {"1": "stand", "2": "base", "3": "size", "4": "basis", "answer": "basis", "question": "You fill in those forms on a weekly ___"}, "2189": {"1": "stay", "2": "hold", "3": "bear", "4": "maintain", "answer": "bear", "question": "I hope you will be patient and ___with me a minute."}, "2190": {"1": "difficult", "2": "hard", "3": "soft", "4": "firm", "answer": "hard", "question": "It's difficult to see how to get out of this situation because we're between a rock and a ___place."}, "2191": {"1": "obtained for this job", "2": "applied for this job", "3": "intended for this job", "4": "asked for this job", "answer": "applied for this job", "question": "Mistaken IdentityInterviewer: Perhaps you could start by telling us why you've ___"}, "2192": {"1": "the free air", "2": "the clear air", "3": "the pure air", "4": "the open air", "answer": "the open air", "question": "Candidate: I think the main reason is because I like working in ___"}, "2193": {"1": "air control", "2": "air managment", "3": "air conditioning", "4": "air condition", "answer": "air conditioning", "question": "Interviewer: You mean you like the idea of an office with ___"}, "2194": {"1": "in about", "2": "on about", "3": "for about", "4": "off about", "answer": "on about", "question": "Candidate: I'm sorry I don't understand what you're ___"}, "2195": {"1": "clear obvious", "2": "mostly obvious", "3": "pretty obvious", "4": "mainly obvious", "answer": "pretty obvious", "question": "Interviewer: I should have thought this was ___"}, "2196": {"1": "it isn't", "2": "it can't be", "3": "it won't be", "4": "it will be", "answer": "it isn't", "question": "Candidate: Not to me, ___"}, "2197": {"1": "put it you're Mr Johnson", "2": "take it you're Mr Johnson", "3": "place it you're Mr Johnson", "4": "try it you're Mr Johnson", "answer": "take it you're Mr Johnson", "question": "Interviewer: I think there must be a mistake, I ___"}, "2198": {"1": "mistaken personality", "2": "mistaken character", "3": "mistaken person", "4": "mistaken identity", "answer": "mistaken identity", "question": "Candidate: I'm Mr Jensen. I'm afraid it's a case of ___"}, "2199": {"1": "I presume", "2": "I pretend", "3": "I prefer", "4": "I preview", "answer": "I presume", "question": "Interviewer: So you're not after the job of guardian, ___"}, "2200": {"1": "if you don't care", "2": "if you don't agree", "3": "if you don't mind", "4": "if you don't see", "answer": "if you don't mind", "question": "Candidate: No, sorry as I said I like working outside, I want to be a gardener, ___"}, "2201": {"1": "sitting", "2": "standing", "3": "waiting", "4": "remaining", "answer": "standing", "question": "Speaking: At the StationThe train now ___at the platform 6 is the 10.45 for London."}, "2202": {"1": "waiting", "2": "lateness", "3": "space", "4": "delay", "answer": "delay", "question": "Unfortunately it is now 11 o'clock and so there is a___of 15 minutes already."}, "2203": {"1": "intended", "2": "expected", "3": "proposed", "4": "awaited", "answer": "expected", "question": "The train for London at platform 6 is still there and is not___ to leave for at least 20 minutes."}, "2204": {"1": "discharging", "2": "dispensing", "3": "offering", "4": "disposing", "answer": "offering", "question": "The small cafe situated near platform 6 is now ___free cups of tea to those waiting for the London train."}, "2205": {"1": "waterlogged", "2": "waterproof", "3": "water soaked", "4": "waterfall", "answer": "waterlogged", "question": "Severe storms last night together with heavy rainfall means that some of the lines of the station are now___"}, "2206": {"1": "wrong", "2": "false", "3": "difficult", "4": "general", "answer": "false", "question": "We thought for a moment that the 10.45 for London might be about to catch fire but it was a ___alarm."}, "2207": {"1": "concord", "2": "conduit", "3": "concourse", "4": "condition", "answer": "concourse", "question": "This is a general notice for all passengers: the restaurant in the main ___is now open."}, "2208": {"1": "distinguished", "2": "dampened", "3": "saturated", "4": "extinguished", "answer": "extinguished", "question": "There was in fact a small fire in the train on platform 6 but we're glad to tell you that the flames have been___"}, "2209": {"1": "breakdown", "2": "low down", "3": "breakout", "4": "low break", "answer": "breakdown", "question": "We regret to announce that the 10.45 for London is now out of service because the driver is having a nervous___"}, "2210": {"1": "send", "2": "move", "3": "take", "4": "tow", "answer": "move", "question": "Speaking: At the SupermarketWill the driver of the blue Ford Fiesta XYZ  please___ their car."}, "2211": {"1": "holding", "2": "keeping", "3": "preventing", "4": "promoting", "answer": "preventing", "question": "The reason for this is that the Fiesta is ___our delivery lorry from leaving the premises."}, "2212": {"1": "possessor", "2": "possessing", "3": "ownership", "4": "owner", "answer": "owner", "question": "We ask the___ of this vehicle to go back to their car as soon as possible and park their car in another space."}, "2213": {"1": "audition", "2": "announcement", "3": "statement", "4": "prediction", "answer": "announcement", "question": "This is a customer___ We have a special offer at the moment on bananas."}, "2214": {"1": "bunch", "2": "branch", "3": "hand", "4": "group", "answer": "bunch", "question": "For the next hour it will be possible to buy just one ___of bananas and get one more free."}, "2215": {"1": "saying", "2": "asking", "3": "request", "4": "question", "answer": "request", "question": "Further to our ___for the Ford Fiesta to be reparked, this matter is now very urgent. Our lorry cannot get out."}, "2216": {"1": "o'clock", "2": "time", "3": "hour", "4": "duration", "answer": "time", "question": "We have to inform our customers that the store will be closing in half an hour's___"}, "2217": {"1": "remember", "2": "retake", "3": "repeat", "4": "remind", "answer": "remind", "question": "We would like to ___our customers that over the Christmas period we will be closing an hour earlier thanusual."}, "2218": {"1": "purchases", "2": "buying", "3": "sales", "4": "selling", "answer": "purchases", "question": "There are now only ten minutes remaining for you to make your ___and go to the checkout."}, "2219": {"1": "note", "2": "message", "3": "saying", "4": "hint", "answer": "message", "question": "A final ___for the driver of the Ford Fiesta: there is no need now to repark as our delivery lorry has done thatfor you!"}, "2220": {"1": "appearance", "2": "appreciation", "3": "appeasement", "4": "apparition", "answer": "appreciation", "question": "Speaking: At the TheatreLadies and gentlemen, I want to thank you for your ___of our performance."}, "2221": {"1": "appointment", "2": "application", "3": "apposition", "4": "applause", "answer": "applause", "question": "We have done this play many times in different towns but your ___has been the greatest so far."}, "2222": {"1": "clapped", "2": "clopped", "3": "clipped", "4": "clammed", "answer": "clapped", "question": "We will always remember the way you stood up and ___at some of the speeches in the play."}, "2223": {"1": "overtaken", "2": "overdrawn", "3": "overcome", "4": "overturned", "answer": "overcome", "question": "Our leading actor is unable to come on the stage at the moment because he is___ with emotion."}, "2224": {"1": "temperate", "2": "temporary", "3": "contemporary", "4": "temporarily", "answer": "temporary", "question": "Don't worry I'm sure it's only ___and that he'll soon recover before the next performance."}, "2225": {"1": "speak", "2": "speaking", "3": "spoke", "4": "speech", "answer": "speech", "question": "That is the reason why I am standing here and making this short ___"}, "2226": {"1": "sobbing", "2": "soaking", "3": "spitting", "4": "calling", "answer": "sobbing", "question": "The leading lady is also absent from our stage and you can probably hear her ___her heart out as I speak."}, "2227": {"1": "ratio", "2": "reason", "3": "ration", "4": "rate", "answer": "reason", "question": "I think that the main ___for all this emotion is probably the way you have reacted to the play."}, "2228": {"1": "currant", "2": "curious", "3": "current", "4": "curtain", "answer": "current", "question": "You see throughout our ___season we have never received so much laughter as we have from you."}, "2229": {"1": "comic", "2": "comedy", "3": "comedian", "4": "comely", "answer": "comedy", "question": "The reason for this is possibly that you thought it was a ___but in fact it is a tragedy."}, "2230": {"1": "reviewer", "2": "reporter", "3": "announcer", "4": "introducer", "answer": "reporter", "question": "Welcome to Radio News and now over to our___ who's covering the procession this morning."}, "2231": {"1": "cat's", "2": "dog's", "3": "bird's", "4": "rat's", "answer": "bird's", "question": "Hi listeners, I should explain that I have a ___eye view of this magnificent sight as the parade passesunderneath me."}, "2232": {"1": "caught", "2": "catching", "3": "cornered", "4": "perched", "answer": "perched", "question": "To tell you the truth I shouldn't be ___up here on top of this large statue of Field Marshal Smith."}, "2233": {"1": "copper", "2": "brass", "3": "zinc", "4": "aluminium", "answer": "brass", "question": "There is a long line of soldiers on horseback marching to the sound of a ___band."}, "2234": {"1": "spying", "2": "guiding", "3": "staring", "4": "starring", "answer": "staring", "question": "It really is quite uncomfortable up here and there's a policeman ___at me, which I don't like."}, "2235": {"1": "members", "2": "doers", "3": "actors", "4": "performers", "answer": "performers", "question": "After the soldiers I can see a group of circus ___who are jumping and dancing as they go."}, "2236": {"1": "highchairs", "2": "low chairs", "3": "wheelchairs", "4": "pushchairs", "answer": "wheelchairs", "question": "Next I can see some pensioners slowly moving along the road and some can't walk and are in ___"}, "2237": {"1": "notebook", "2": "exercise book", "3": "storybook", "4": "copybook", "answer": "notebook", "question": "That policeman is getting out his ___and walking near the statue I'm sitting on."}, "2238": {"1": "sunk", "2": "suited", "3": "stuck", "4": "soaked", "answer": "soaked", "question": "It has started to rain and I shall get ___to the skin if I stay much longer up here."}, "2239": {"1": "seize", "2": "arrest", "3": "grasp", "4": "hold", "answer": "arrest", "question": "Oh dear, listeners, I shall have to return you to the studio because the policeman says he is going to ___me."}, "2240": {"1": "let me to pay later", "2": "permit me pay later", "3": "allow me to pay later", "4": "grant me to pay later", "answer": "allow me to pay later", "question": "I would be most obliged if you ___"}, "2241": {"1": "leave my watch as a present", "2": "leave my watch as a token", "3": "leave my watch as a gift", "4": "leave my watch as a deposit", "answer": "leave my watch as a deposit", "question": "The other thing I could do is ___"}, "2242": {"1": "you don't really like the thought", "2": "you don't really like the concept", "3": "you don't really like the idea", "4": "you don't really like the belief", "answer": "you don't really like the idea", "question": "I can see by the expression on your face ___"}, "2243": {"1": "take me the money", "2": "bring me the money", "3": "carry me the money", "4": "gain me the money", "answer": "bring me the money", "question": "I could phone someone to ___"}, "2244": {"1": "I'm holding up your trade", "2": "I'm holding off your trade", "3": "I'm holding on your trade", "4": "I'm holding in your trade", "answer": "I'm holding up your trade", "question": "I see. So what you are saying is ___"}, "2245": {"1": "you're being very indistinct", "2": "you're being very unclear", "3": "you're being very unfavourable", "4": "you're being very unreasonable", "answer": "you're being very unreasonable", "question": "Well, I did say I was sorry and I think ___"}, "2246": {"1": "collect the manager", "2": "call the manager", "3": "deliver the manager", "4": "present the manager", "answer": "call the manager", "question": "You say you have no choice but to ___"}, "2247": {"1": "symbolise", "2": "energise", "3": "sympathise", "4": "eulogise", "answer": "sympathise", "question": "That sounds a good idea. I'm sure he'll ___"}, "2248": {"1": "of course I'll wash the dishes in the kitchen", "2": "inevitably I'll wash the dishes in the kitchen", "3": "understandably I'll wash the dishes in the kitchen", "4": "indubitably I'll wash the dishes in the kitchen", "answer": "of course I'll wash the dishes in the kitchen", "question": "All right, all right Mr manager. Just as you say, ___"}, "2249": {"1": "detailed", "2": "particular", "3": "specialized", "4": "itemized", "answer": "itemized", "question": "AccountsIn order to check all the telephone calls made during the month I want the account to be ___"}, "2250": {"1": "expensive", "2": "expending", "3": "expense", "4": "expenses", "answer": "expense", "question": "All the representatives are allowed to spend money for entertaining with their___account."}, "2251": {"1": "credible", "2": "credit", "3": "credited", "4": "credulous", "answer": "credit", "question": "To spread the cost of spending on articles you buy many big departments let you open a ___"}, "2252": {"1": "open", "2": "start", "3": "begin", "4": "commence", "answer": "open", "question": "Once you are earning money and you want to keep it safe, you can always ___an account with a bank."}, "2253": {"1": "arrange", "2": "finish", "3": "end", "4": "settle", "answer": "settle", "question": "At the end of thirty days the company will ask you to___ the account."}, "2254": {"1": "holding", "2": "keeping", "3": "taking", "4": "finding", "answer": "keeping", "question": "The finance director is responsible for ___the accounts for the business."}, "2255": {"1": "print", "2": "edit", "3": "publish", "4": "direct", "answer": "publish", "question": "At the end of the financial year it is the responsibility of the chief finance officer to ___the accounts."}, "2256": {"1": "united", "2": "joint", "3": "unified", "4": "combined", "answer": "joint", "question": "Before they got married, they decided to open a ___account."}, "2257": {"1": "heap", "2": "pile", "3": "lump", "4": "deposit", "answer": "deposit", "question": "If you have saved some money, it is a good idea to put the money into a ___account."}, "2258": {"1": "with", "2": "to", "3": "for", "4": "by", "answer": "for", "question": "However hard I try, I find it impossible to account ___this missing sum of money."}, "2259": {"1": "comparing", "2": "comparison", "3": "compares", "4": "comparative", "answer": "comparison", "question": "AdvertisingIn order to make a sensible ___ among the different vacuum cleaners available, it is important to do someresearch."}, "2260": {"1": "satisfy", "2": "satisfaction", "3": "satisfies", "4": "satisfying", "answer": "satisfy", "question": "The local department store has to make a sustained effort at this time of the year to ___ customer demand forsummer clothing."}, "2261": {"1": "inspiring", "2": "inspiration", "3": "inspires", "4": "inspire", "answer": "inspire", "question": "A good team leader must be able to ___ his colleagues to face the challenge of a downturn in business."}, "2262": {"1": "currant", "2": "current", "3": "occuring", "4": "occured", "answer": "current", "question": "The ___ trend in children's desire to wear designer label clothes should be exploited."}, "2263": {"1": "convict", "2": "conviction", "3": "convince", "4": "convincing", "answer": "convince", "question": "You have to ___ the public that it is in their own interest to read the instructions on all our medicines."}, "2264": {"1": "competition", "2": "competing", "3": "competitor", "4": "competitive", "answer": "competitive", "question": "In order to survive in this business you must adopt a ___ stance."}, "2265": {"1": "consumer", "2": "consumption", "3": "consuming", "4": "consumes", "answer": "consumption", "question": "The ___ of alcohol is not allowed in any of the company's premises in order to present a clean image."}, "2266": {"1": "attraction", "2": "attractive", "3": "attract", "4": "attracts", "answer": "attract", "question": "When you are setting out to ___ new customers in an advertisement, choose the right words."}, "2267": {"1": "persuades", "2": "persuasion", "3": "persuasive", "4": "persuading", "answer": "persuades", "question": "The really effective television commercial is the one that ___ you of its authenticity."}, "2268": {"1": "producer", "2": "product", "3": "production", "4": "produce", "answer": "product", "question": "I can strongly recommend this ___ as the best available on the market today."}, "2269": {"1": "follow", "2": "adhere", "3": "abide", "4": "stick", "answer": "abide", "question": "AgreementsThe contract was signed by the three partners who thus agreed to ___ by terms and conditions contained init."}, "2270": {"1": "pointed", "2": "specified", "3": "printed", "4": "developed", "answer": "specified", "question": "There was nothing in the contract that ___ who would be responsible in the event that one of the partnersbecame seriously ill."}, "2271": {"1": "result", "2": "retake", "3": "restrain", "4": "resolve", "answer": "resolve", "question": "An independent adviser was called in after the collapse of the company to ___ some of the issues that werenot clear."}, "2272": {"1": "partakers", "2": "participants", "3": "particles", "4": "parties", "answer": "parties", "question": "One of the ___ mentioned in the original agreement has decided that she does not want to continue with theprofit-sharing scheme."}, "2273": {"1": "throw", "2": "reject", "3": "cancel", "4": "deter", "answer": "cancel", "question": "In view of the serious problems associated with the takeover the newspaper company has decided to ___ itsoffer of financial help."}, "2274": {"1": "call", "2": "engage", "3": "enter", "4": "register", "answer": "engage", "question": "The main problem was that the newly formed organisation was not attracting enough work and so theydecided to ___ the services of a public relations expert."}, "2275": {"1": "grounded", "2": "established", "3": "found", "4": "invented", "answer": "established", "question": "That company has been in business for over  years and in fact was ___ in ."}, "2276": {"1": "paper", "2": "insurance", "3": "assurance", "4": "conviction", "answer": "assurance", "question": "After the complaint had been received from the customer about poor service, she was given a written ___ thatthe matter would be put right."}, "2277": {"1": "foresight", "2": "forecast", "3": "providing", "4": "provision", "answer": "provision", "question": "They were very careful to make sure in the original agreement that ___ would be made to pay for staffredundancies."}, "2278": {"1": "decipher", "2": "decide", "3": "defer", "4": "determine", "answer": "determine", "question": "We decided to employ a solicitor who would be able to ___ the extent of our liability in this matter."}, "2279": {"1": "entering", "2": "working", "3": "applying", "4": "writing", "answer": "applying", "question": "Applying for that JobI would be very interested in___ for that job."}, "2280": {"1": "stand", "2": "sit", "3": "go", "4": "try", "answer": "stand", "question": "Do you want to ___as a candidate in the local elections?"}, "2281": {"1": "tired", "2": "fed", "3": "sick", "4": "ill", "answer": "fed", "question": "They are completely___ up with all the noise in the centre of town."}, "2282": {"1": "hit", "2": "stop", "3": "strike", "4": "leave", "answer": "strike", "question": "The reason there are no buses is because the drivers are on ___"}, "2283": {"1": "view", "2": "opinion", "3": "mind", "4": "heart", "answer": "heart", "question": "The government has changed its policy and had a complete change of ___"}, "2284": {"1": "target", "2": "persuade", "3": "encourage", "4": "trap", "answer": "target", "question": "This supermarket is trying to___ young shoppers by offering fashionable clothes."}, "2285": {"1": "taken out", "2": "sold off", "3": "bought up", "4": "taken over", "answer": "bought up", "question": "You should have ___those shares when they were cheap."}, "2286": {"1": "running", "2": "racing", "3": "pacing", "4": "turning", "answer": "running", "question": "You must try and hurry up because my patience is ___out."}, "2287": {"1": "arm", "2": "finger", "3": "hand", "4": "leg", "answer": "hand", "question": "Have you ever tried your ___at running a business?"}, "2288": {"1": "leave", "2": "finishing", "3": "departure", "4": "retirement", "answer": "retirement", "question": "After all these years she has decided to take early ___"}, "2289": {"1": "burst", "2": "spree", "3": "flight", "4": "day", "answer": "spree", "question": "Are You in Debt?Going on a spending ___ with your credit card and no concern about how you pay back the money youborrow, is a growing habit these days."}, "2290": {"1": "overhauled", "2": "overseen", "3": "overlooked", "4": "overtaken", "answer": "overhauled", "question": "There is a popular demand for the system that allows credit companies to offer unlimited credit to youngpeople to be ___"}, "2291": {"1": "distinguished", "2": "deciphered", "3": "dissolved", "4": "disclosed", "answer": "disclosed", "question": "It has been ___ by a government agency that the percentage of under 25 year olds owing large sums tocompanies is on the increase."}, "2292": {"1": "step over", "2": "step through", "3": "step down", "4": "step out", "answer": "step down", "question": "One director of a major credit company has already been forced to ___ because of the bad publicity hiscompany has attracted."}, "2293": {"1": "step under", "2": "step up", "3": "step by", "4": "step across", "answer": "step up", "question": "One solution that has been suggested to control credit is to ___ the regulations to make it more difficult to getcredit in the first place."}, "2294": {"1": "cultivation", "2": "cult", "3": "cultivate", "4": "culture", "answer": "culture", "question": "The main problem is that a debt ___ has developed recently believing that it is cool to owe large sums ofmoney."}, "2295": {"1": "revealed", "2": "restored", "3": "replied", "4": "responded", "answer": "revealed", "question": "Recent reports have ___ that being in debt is not now looked upon as a disgrace but rather as an attractiveway of life."}, "2296": {"1": "hail", "2": "halt", "3": "haul", "4": "help", "answer": "haul", "question": "In reality it's a very long ___ to get from owing to paying off all your debts."}, "2297": {"1": "collisions", "2": "clashes", "3": "claims", "4": "crashes", "answer": "clashes", "question": "There are frequently ___ in the family home between parents and children about whether you should enterinto credit agreements."}, "2298": {"1": "frights", "2": "fearful", "3": "fears", "4": "afraid", "answer": "fears", "question": "What concerns people most are the mounting ___ among governments that it will take at least a generationfor us to be rid of excessive debt."}, "2299": {"1": "reach", "2": "access", "3": "obtain", "4": "find", "answer": "access", "question": "At the ComputerWithout the right software I'm afraid you can't ___ that particular program."}, "2300": {"1": "arrange", "2": "accord", "3": "allocate", "4": "organize", "answer": "allocate", "question": "The aim of the office manager is to ___ enough room on the building plans so that each employee can havespace for a personal computer."}, "2301": {"1": "shut out", "2": "shut up", "3": "shut in", "4": "shut down", "answer": "shut down", "question": "Remember that before you leave your workstation, always ___ your computer."}, "2302": {"1": "seeking", "2": "searching", "3": "looking", "4": "checking", "answer": "searching", "question": "It's quite easy if you want to find folders and files on the computer, all you do is click here and it immediatelystarts ___"}, "2303": {"1": "look out", "2": "check out", "3": "figure out", "4": "bring out", "answer": "figure out", "question": "I have tried and tried again and again and no matter what I do it still shows \"error\"  I just can't ___ what'swrong."}, "2304": {"1": "illustrate", "2": "depict", "3": "display", "4": "delineate", "answer": "display", "question": "It's a really clever piece of software because it enables you to ___ on your screen all the information incolumns."}, "2305": {"1": "amicable", "2": "compatible", "3": "adaptable", "4": "amenable", "answer": "compatible", "question": "Unfortunately this program is not ___ with the operating system on my computer."}, "2306": {"1": "indicating", "2": "checking", "3": "briefing", "4": "warning", "answer": "warning", "question": "When you see that particular symbol on the screen, you have to take that as a ___ that something is wrong."}, "2307": {"1": "provision", "2": "producer", "3": "provisional", "4": "provider", "answer": "provider", "question": "The main ___ of stationery for the office suddenly announced there would be an overall increase in theirprices."}, "2308": {"1": "recur", "2": "repeat", "3": "retake", "4": "refer", "answer": "recur", "question": "The chief administrative officer disliked lack of attention to detail and insisted that such mistakes should never___"}, "2309": {"1": "reducing", "2": "reduction", "3": "reduce", "4": "reduces", "answer": "reduction", "question": "Once again the company has had to make a ___ in the number of office staff to try and recoup their losses."}, "2310": {"1": "share", "2": "state", "3": "stock", "4": "selection", "answer": "stock", "question": "The ___ of zip discs in the office is running dangerously low."}, "2311": {"1": "summit", "2": "top", "3": "head", "4": "line", "answer": "top", "question": "If the managers want to stay employed, they will have to learn how to stay on ___ of their jobs."}, "2312": {"1": "needed", "2": "noted", "3": "called", "4": "told", "answer": "needed", "question": "It's not worth paying for an annual service when you can simply call the supplier on an as-___ basis."}, "2313": {"1": "use", "2": "mind", "3": "case", "4": "charge", "answer": "charge", "question": "The new office manager will be in ___ of all the IT requirements that the company uses."}, "2314": {"1": "capability", "2": "capacity", "3": "control", "4": "capable", "answer": "capacity", "question": "Currently there is a shortage of clerical staff but it is hoped that by the end of the year they will be up to full___"}, "2315": {"1": "initiative", "2": "interest", "3": "involvement", "4": "initial", "answer": "initiative", "question": "Staff are always encouraged to work by themselves and whenever they meet a problem, they should use theirown ___"}, "2316": {"1": "reinforce", "2": "respond", "3": "react", "4": "resource", "answer": "reinforce", "question": "Having attended the office procedures course all employees were expected to ___ what they had learned andintroduce it into their daily routine."}, "2317": {"1": "manner", "2": "method", "3": "feature", "4": "code", "answer": "code", "question": "Visiting clients had commented on the casual dress ___ of most of the clerical staff."}, "2318": {"1": "practical", "2": "practicality", "3": "practice", "4": "practically", "answer": "practice", "question": "The ___ of staff doing physical exercises before the start of the day is well established in Japanesecompanies."}, "2319": {"1": "wordy", "2": "verbal", "3": "worded", "4": "verbose", "answer": "verbal", "question": "There is a lengthy procedure used in this office for staff who have produced shoddy work and it begins with a___ warning."}, "2320": {"1": "possible", "2": "probable", "3": "unplanned", "4": "casual", "answer": "casual", "question": "There was no fixed agenda for that particular day as it was to be regarded simply as a ___ meeting."}, "2321": {"1": "look", "2": "view", "3": "glimpse", "4": "picture", "answer": "glimpse", "question": "At the interview all the candidates were shown round the building but could only really catch a ___ of the sortof work being carried out."}, "2322": {"1": "in to", "2": "up for", "3": "out of", "4": "up to", "answer": "out of", "question": "They really need to keep a check on the stationery supplies as they've run ___ A4 paper once again."}, "2323": {"1": "devoted", "2": "exposed", "3": "opened", "4": "experienced", "answer": "exposed", "question": "Managers prefer to select people who have been ___ to many different types of office environments."}, "2324": {"1": "outdated", "2": "completed", "3": "finished", "4": "ended", "answer": "outdated", "question": "A troubleshooter was brought into the office from another firm to get rid of some very ___ procedures."}, "2325": {"1": "objects", "2": "products", "3": "bargains", "4": "offerings", "answer": "bargains", "question": "At the ShopsWe got there early so that we could get the best ___ in the sale before anyone else."}, "2326": {"1": "hold", "2": "stay", "3": "bear", "4": "wait", "answer": "bear", "question": "If you ___ with me, I'll go and see whether we have that in your size."}, "2327": {"1": "barriers", "2": "sales points", "3": "exits", "4": "checkouts", "answer": "checkouts", "question": "The trouble with these huge superstores is that they don't have enough ___ to deal with customers at busytimes."}, "2328": {"1": "expanded", "2": "extended", "3": "explored", "4": "enlarged", "answer": "expanded", "question": "It started off as a small street corner shop over 30 years ago but it has now ___ into a massive departmentstore."}, "2329": {"1": "proceeds", "2": "items", "3": "products", "4": "produce", "answer": "items", "question": "Take a good look at the receipt when you leave so that you can see that all the ___ have been listed."}, "2330": {"1": "examine", "2": "search", "3": "check", "4": "explore", "answer": "explore", "question": "Whenever I go to the old part of a city, I like to ___ all the shops selling antiques."}, "2331": {"1": "tendency", "2": "trend", "3": "custom", "4": "habit", "answer": "trend", "question": "Are you aware of the latest ___ in children's clothing?"}, "2332": {"1": "severe", "2": "strong", "3": "strict", "4": "hard", "answer": "strict", "question": "They're quite ___ in their policy of not giving refunds without a receipt in this store."}, "2333": {"1": "legal", "2": "reasonable", "3": "required", "4": "mandatory", "answer": "mandatory", "question": "They have a ___ restriction in the shop with regard to the number of items of clothing that you can try on atone time."}, "2334": {"1": "merchandise", "2": "objects", "3": "produce", "4": "articles", "answer": "merchandise", "question": "The extent of the ___ available in this one store is more than you can possibly imagine."}, "2335": {"1": "notification", "2": "certification", "3": "clarification", "4": "signification", "answer": "clarification", "question": "BusinessI was pleased to receive your response to my proposal but there are one or two points that need ___"}, "2336": {"1": "published", "2": "directed", "3": "opened", "4": "held", "answer": "published", "question": "A report has just been ___ that gives details of the causes of this trend towards informality in the businesssector."}, "2337": {"1": "seeking", "2": "searching", "3": "findings", "4": "probing", "answer": "findings", "question": "According to the ___ in the report it is clear that employees under the age of 35 prefer to dress casually atwork."}, "2338": {"1": "withheld", "2": "endured", "3": "suffered", "4": "tolerated", "answer": "tolerated", "question": "Thirty years ago this kind of informality would not have been ___"}, "2339": {"1": "stop", "2": "restrain", "3": "refrain", "4": "restrict", "answer": "refrain", "question": "All employees are kindly requested to ___ from smoking in the presence of customers."}, "2340": {"1": "list", "2": "index", "3": "contents", "4": "agenda", "answer": "agenda", "question": "The meeting went on for three hours and as a result there was no time left to discuss all the topics on the___"}, "2341": {"1": "business", "2": "work", "3": "activity", "4": "tasks", "answer": "business", "question": "There's really no point in hoping to add important topics right at the end of the meeting under the heading ofany other ___"}, "2342": {"1": "cessation", "2": "standstill", "3": "stopping", "4": "halt", "answer": "halt", "question": "The chairman was obliged to bring the meeting to a ___ because a fire broke out in the adjoining room."}, "2343": {"1": "time", "2": "minute", "3": "detail", "4": "measure", "answer": "minute", "question": "It is absolutely essential that the clerk takes care to ___ any decisions that have been reached during themeeting."}, "2344": {"1": "delay", "2": "wait", "3": "postpone", "4": "hold", "answer": "postpone", "question": "As so few members had turned up at the meeting, it was decided to ___ it until further notice."}, "2345": {"1": "put", "2": "set", "3": "place", "4": "hold", "answer": "set", "question": "Shortly after he was dismissed from the firm he decided to___ himself up in his own business."}, "2346": {"1": "out", "2": "in", "3": "into", "4": "on", "answer": "into", "question": "They went ___business shortly after their children had left home and got married."}, "2347": {"1": "made", "2": "tried", "3": "managed", "4": "called", "answer": "made", "question": "As soon as they heard what had happened, they ___it their business to find out the truth."}, "2348": {"1": "no", "2": "nothing", "3": "none", "4": "nor", "answer": "none", "question": "I would ask you kindly not to interfere with what I'm doing as in all honesty it's___ of your business."}, "2349": {"1": "common", "2": "practical", "3": "frequent", "4": "usual", "answer": "usual", "question": "Despite all the alterations that are taking place in the department store, the management wanted to explain itwas business as ___"}, "2350": {"1": "weird", "2": "unusual", "3": "funny", "4": "stupid", "answer": "funny", "question": "She knew that there was some kind of ___business going on because strange things were happening."}, "2351": {"1": "set", "2": "get", "3": "cut", "4": "find", "answer": "get", "question": "We really can't delay any more with our plans and must ___down to business as soon as possible."}, "2352": {"1": "about", "2": "along", "3": "across", "4": "through", "answer": "about", "question": "When the bomb went off, most of the injured were just ordinary people going ___their business."}, "2353": {"1": "turned", "2": "came", "3": "went", "4": "fell", "answer": "went", "question": "Although they had high hopes that they would be successful, they ___out of business within six months."}, "2354": {"1": "in", "2": "out", "3": "of", "4": "by", "answer": "in", "question": "That's really not my concern at all and I'm certainly not ___the business of telling others what to do."}, "2355": {"1": "as", "2": "with", "3": "similar", "4": "like", "answer": "like", "question": "She was very enthusiastic about her new job and was making rapid progress___ nobody's business."}, "2356": {"1": "signify", "2": "mean", "3": "require", "4": "need", "answer": "mean", "question": "I really wouldn't joke about it because these people are deadly serious and ___business."}, "2357": {"1": "concern", "2": "look after", "3": "tend to", "4": "mind", "answer": "mind", "question": "He didn't hesitate to tell me that I wasn't wanted and just told me to ___my own business."}, "2358": {"1": "off", "2": "on", "3": "for", "4": "to", "answer": "on", "question": "I'm afraid it won't be possible to talk to the boss today because he's away___ business till Tuesday."}, "2359": {"1": "ticket", "2": "paper", "3": "card", "4": "notice", "answer": "card", "question": "He was very keen that we kept in touch and for that reason he handed me his business ___"}, "2360": {"1": "centre", "2": "end", "3": "area", "4": "point", "answer": "end", "question": "This is the really important part of the machine and that's why we call it the business ___"}, "2361": {"1": "place", "2": "situation", "3": "field", "4": "park", "answer": "park", "question": "The whole site has nothing but offices and administration centres and that's why we call it a business ___"}, "2362": {"1": "play", "2": "drama", "3": "show", "4": "performance", "answer": "show", "question": "All the famous film stars, actors, directors and writers were at the festival representing the world of ___business."}, "2363": {"1": "behaviour", "2": "practice", "3": "dealing", "4": "attitude", "answer": "practice", "question": "Code of PracticeThe company had its own code of ___in these matters."}, "2364": {"1": "critical", "2": "pure", "3": "simple", "4": "prime", "answer": "prime", "question": "This is a ___example of what not to do."}, "2365": {"1": "over", "2": "through", "3": "up", "4": "into", "answer": "up", "question": "Plans have already been drawn ___to deal with such situations."}, "2366": {"1": "individuals", "2": "subscribers", "3": "applicants", "4": "interviewees", "answer": "subscribers", "question": "Thousands of___are already signing up for this new telephone service."}, "2367": {"1": "blue-collar", "2": "red-collar", "3": "stiff-collar", "4": "high-collar", "answer": "blue-collar", "question": "Job losses are mainly in the___ sectors of the industry."}, "2368": {"1": "key", "2": "obvious", "3": "intelligent", "4": "noted", "answer": "key", "question": "The circular will contain ___financial information to help investors."}, "2369": {"1": "necessary", "2": "possibly", "3": "clearly", "4": "likely", "answer": "likely", "question": "The report is ___to show better than expected results."}, "2370": {"1": "dangerous", "2": "endangered", "3": "unwanted", "4": "limited", "answer": "endangered", "question": "So many of these animals have been shot over the years that they are now classed as ___species."}, "2371": {"1": "unaccustomed", "2": "shy", "3": "reluctant", "4": "inhibited", "answer": "reluctant", "question": "Some people are ___to learn a foreign language."}, "2372": {"1": "trial", "2": "sacrifice", "3": "endeavour", "4": "test", "answer": "sacrifice", "question": "It was a big ___for her to give up her acting career to look after her family."}, "2373": {"1": "space", "2": "compact", "3": "disc", "4": "place", "answer": "disc", "question": "ComputersMy computer is not capable of saving material on a separate ___ because it has no floppy drive."}, "2374": {"1": "joining", "2": "connecting", "3": "linking", "4": "networking", "answer": "networking", "question": "I understand that I can make it possible for both my computers to share the same programs by means of___"}, "2375": {"1": "replaced", "2": "restored", "3": "retaken", "4": "revived", "answer": "replaced", "question": "I had only had my computer for three weeks when I had to have the hard drive ___"}, "2376": {"1": "famous", "2": "popular", "3": "sought", "4": "wished", "answer": "popular", "question": "Laptop computers are becoming more and more ___ in the business world."}, "2377": {"1": "acute", "2": "cut", "3": "razor", "4": "sharp", "answer": "sharp", "question": "You have to have a really ___ mind in order to get your head round some of today's computing technology."}, "2378": {"1": "hoarding", "2": "keeping", "3": "holding", "4": "storage", "answer": "storage", "question": "The great advantage of having an external zip drive is that you can use it as an extra means of ___"}, "2379": {"1": "technical", "2": "technique", "3": "technician", "4": "technically", "answer": "technical", "question": "They tried very hard to install the new components on the computer but the language in the manual was too___ for them to understand."}, "2380": {"1": "revolt", "2": "revolution", "3": "revolting", "4": "revolving", "answer": "revolution", "question": "When you look at the modern office today you could compare the changes with those that took place in theindustrial ___ in the 19th century."}, "2381": {"1": "facile", "2": "facility", "3": "factual", "4": "facilitate", "answer": "facilitate", "question": "In order to ___ the method by which staff pay is calculated the company has bought a new software package."}, "2382": {"1": "proceeding", "2": "procedure", "3": "processing", "4": "processes", "answer": "processing", "question": "Obviously a computer can take all the hard work out of ___ a large mass of data."}, "2383": {"1": "lows", "2": "bottoms", "3": "depths", "4": "ends", "answer": "lows", "question": "Credit Card HoldersThe stock market has hit new ___this year."}, "2384": {"1": "examination", "2": "enquiry", "3": "evaluation", "4": "interpretation", "answer": "enquiry", "question": "The government has decided to hold an___ into the latest financial scandal."}, "2385": {"1": "launched", "2": "pursued", "3": "offered", "4": "ejected", "answer": "launched", "question": "The animal rights organisation has___a new campaign to make people aware of cruelty to animals."}, "2386": {"1": "unknowing", "2": "unclear", "3": "incredulous", "4": "unaware", "answer": "unaware", "question": "I was totally ___of the increased taxes."}, "2387": {"1": "raised", "2": "risen", "3": "escalated", "4": "ascended", "answer": "risen", "question": "The price of petrol has ___again."}, "2388": {"1": "stump up", "2": "throw up", "3": "cheer up", "4": "bring up", "answer": "stump up", "question": "The ordinary person is again being asked to ___to pay for dental treatment."}, "2389": {"1": "internal", "2": "external", "3": "export", "4": "outside", "answer": "export", "question": "This car is intended for the ___market only."}, "2390": {"1": "reduce", "2": "deduct", "3": "curtail", "4": "shorten", "answer": "reduce", "question": "Credit card holders struggle very hard to ___the amount they owe."}, "2391": {"1": "collect", "2": "gather", "3": "assemble", "4": "convene", "answer": "collect", "question": "This charity was set up to ___money for the poor."}, "2392": {"1": "happened", "2": "occurred", "3": "turned up", "4": "turned out", "answer": "turned out", "question": "Everything ___all right in the end."}, "2393": {"1": "generalizing", "2": "generating", "3": "germinating", "4": "gesticulating", "answer": "generating", "question": "Employment and TrainingWe're paying for a stand at the new industrial exhibition with a view to ___ interest among potentialemployees in our company."}, "2394": {"1": "minor", "2": "monitor", "3": "mender", "4": "mentor", "answer": "mentor", "question": "For the first three months of your employment with the firm you will be under the care of a ___"}, "2395": {"1": "return", "2": "reject", "3": "refuse", "4": "repeat", "answer": "reject", "question": "Although she was very tempted to accept the job she was offered, she had to ___ the offer because thesalary would have been insufficient."}, "2396": {"1": "preparation", "2": "concentration", "3": "training", "4": "learning", "answer": "training", "question": "A university education is of course important but it is essential that all employees undergo a period of intensive___"}, "2397": {"1": "update", "2": "dating", "3": "dates", "4": "dated", "answer": "update", "question": "A newsletter is sent out every ten days to all the staff so that they receive a regular ___ on recentappointments."}, "2398": {"1": "placed by", "2": "put on", "3": "set up", "4": "set off", "answer": "set up", "question": "Part of the ongoing training is to ensure that a regular time and place are ___ for department heads to meettheir staff."}, "2399": {"1": "success", "2": "progress", "3": "business", "4": "future", "answer": "success", "question": "The head of department acknowledged that the ___ of the section was largely due to high quality supportstaff."}, "2400": {"1": "hold on to", "2": "keep on to", "3": "hold up with", "4": "keep up with", "answer": "keep up with", "question": "The pace of change in that industry is so fast that staff find it hard to ___ the latest developments."}, "2401": {"1": "control", "2": "conduct", "3": "convene", "4": "confirm", "answer": "conduct", "question": "It is the policy of the company to ___ all interviews for new recruits with a member of the trade union present."}, "2402": {"1": "on line", "2": "on road", "3": "on track", "4": "on path", "answer": "on track", "question": "In view of the excessive workload you have at the moment I won't expect you to keep ___ during the next fewdays."}, "2403": {"1": "wanted", "2": "wished", "3": "desired", "4": "needed", "answer": "desired", "question": "FinanceIt's a gamble at the moment whether the company will make profit in its second year but that nevertheless isthe ___ aim."}, "2404": {"1": "forecast", "2": "foretell", "3": "foresee", "4": "forego", "answer": "forecast", "question": "Each year the Chancellor of the Exchequer stands up in the House of Commons and gives a ___ of what isseen as the economic outlook for the country."}, "2405": {"1": "really", "2": "realize", "3": "reality", "4": "realistic", "answer": "realistic", "question": "I think that your financial optimism is not really justified and you should adopt a more ___ attitude."}, "2406": {"1": "aiming", "2": "directing", "3": "targeting", "4": "guiding", "answer": "targeting", "question": "If you want to increase sales of a particular product, you must be sure that you are ___ the right customers."}, "2407": {"1": "confirmed", "2": "yielded", "3": "harvested", "4": "maintained", "answer": "yielded", "question": "The idea caught on very quickly and people were queuing up to buy the goods so that year the company'sinvestment ___ substantial profits."}, "2408": {"1": "Overall", "2": "Largely", "3": "Mainly", "4": "Quite", "answer": "Overall", "question": "___ it has not been a bad year as our costs are well down on last year's."}, "2409": {"1": "signs", "2": "indications", "3": "types", "4": "levels", "answer": "levels", "question": "Managers complained bitterly at the Annual General Meeting that ___ of production had dropped to an alltime low."}, "2410": {"1": "general", "2": "typical", "3": "formal", "4": "correct", "answer": "typical", "question": "You have to accept that this kind of expenditure is quite ___ in an enterprise of this kind."}, "2411": {"1": "prospective", "2": "perception", "3": "perusal", "4": "perspective", "answer": "perspective", "question": "The figures that have just been published by the company's accountants will give management some kind of___ on how sales are going."}, "2412": {"1": "detailed", "2": "dedicated", "3": "descriptive", "4": "described", "answer": "detailed", "question": "Whenever a member of staff makes a claim for travel expenses, they have to provide a ___ account of theirjourneys."}, "2413": {"1": "inputting", "2": "interesting", "3": "infusing", "4": "investing", "answer": "investing", "question": "You are never too young to start ___some money in a savings account."}, "2414": {"1": "extract", "2": "exit", "3": "withhold", "4": "withdraw", "answer": "withdraw", "question": "If ever you find you have an unexpected expense, you can always ___some money from your savings."}, "2415": {"1": "yield", "2": "take up", "3": "increase", "4": "throw up", "answer": "yield", "question": "At certain times of the year your shares will ___a good profit but you must also be prepared for them to godown in value."}, "2416": {"1": "refine", "2": "drop", "3": "cut", "4": "slice", "answer": "cut", "question": "You can ___the cost of insuring your car if you keep it in a garage."}, "2417": {"1": "deal", "2": "dealing", "3": "dealer", "4": "dealt", "answer": "deal", "question": "We got a very good ___when we bought that three piece suite for half its usual price."}, "2418": {"1": "take on", "2": "take up", "3": "take off", "4": "take to", "answer": "take off", "question": "Now that the summer has started, big department stores are hoping that sales of holiday items will ___"}, "2419": {"1": "merge", "2": "double", "3": "mix", "4": "blend", "answer": "merge", "question": "The two companies have decided to ___because they believe that their combined resources will producegreater profits."}, "2420": {"1": "profits", "2": "wealth", "3": "assets", "4": "products", "answer": "assets", "question": "When someone dies and their ___reach a certain figure, their family has to pay an additional tax."}, "2421": {"1": "steady", "2": "fixed", "3": "long", "4": "exact", "answer": "fixed", "question": "The loan you have taken out is for a ___term, which in your case is 5 years."}, "2422": {"1": "turn over", "2": "turn up", "3": "overtaker", "4": "takeover", "answer": "takeover", "question": "The larger company did not really want to join with the smaller one because it was more interested in a___"}, "2423": {"1": "Working", "2": "Trading", "3": "Pricing", "4": "Adding", "answer": "Trading", "question": "___ on the stockmarket just before Christmas is usually very slow."}, "2424": {"1": "founded", "2": "found", "3": "fined", "4": "funded", "answer": "funded", "question": "This sport centre has largely been ___by money that has come from the national lottery."}, "2425": {"1": "slowness", "2": "slowly", "3": "slowdown", "4": "slow", "answer": "slowdown", "question": "The reason for the ___in the economy is because there is a great deal of uncertainty at the moment."}, "2426": {"1": "upturn", "2": "upstart", "3": "uptake", "4": "upward", "answer": "upturn", "question": "The ___in the market was seen as a positive sign that the recession was over."}, "2427": {"1": "exercise", "2": "order", "3": "place", "4": "trade", "answer": "order", "question": "The ___books for manufacturers of small cars are now full following the rise in petrol."}, "2428": {"1": "steak", "2": "state", "3": "stake", "4": "stress", "answer": "stake", "question": "The future of his job was at___ when he made the decision to invest in new machinery."}, "2429": {"1": "valued", "2": "priced", "3": "cost", "4": "prized", "answer": "valued", "question": "After their house had been___, they decided to sell it and buy a bigger one."}, "2430": {"1": "useless", "2": "unwanted", "3": "unneeded", "4": "redundant", "answer": "redundant", "question": "Fifty people were made___when the company suffered a severe financial shock."}, "2431": {"1": "squabble", "2": "argument", "3": "quibble", "4": "quarrel", "answer": "quibble", "question": "The great thing about this guarantee is that there is never any doubt and there is no___ about getting yourmoney back."}, "2432": {"1": "shortdrop", "2": "shortfall", "3": "shortdown", "4": "shortslide", "answer": "shortfall", "question": "There is a substantial___ between the money you have available and the amount you need to spend."}, "2433": {"1": "lump", "2": "block", "3": "pile", "4": "heap", "answer": "lump", "question": "When you retire, you should get a pension and a ___sum from your employers."}, "2434": {"1": "Spenders", "2": "Borrowers", "3": "Lenders", "4": "Investors", "answer": "Investors", "question": "___ are people who put money into a business in the hope of making a profit."}, "2435": {"1": "main", "2": "chief", "3": "capital", "4": "bulk", "answer": "capital", "question": "When you take out a large loan over many years, you don't start paying off the ___for some time."}, "2436": {"1": "cost", "2": "debt", "3": "charge", "4": "payment", "answer": "charge", "question": "We will make no ___for the catalogue, which you can take with our compliments."}, "2437": {"1": "produce", "2": "benefit", "3": "products", "4": "price", "answer": "benefit", "question": "It may seem a long way into the future but in the end you will get some ___from your investment."}, "2438": {"1": "balance", "2": "scale", "3": "difference", "4": "cost", "answer": "balance", "question": "There is still an outstanding___ on that account, which must be paid in 30 days."}, "2439": {"1": "figures", "2": "rates", "3": "numbers", "4": "standards", "answer": "rates", "question": "Interest ___are at their lowest level since the 's."}, "2440": {"1": "consequence", "2": "conduct", "3": "convenience", "4": "consideration", "answer": "consequence", "question": "Guarantees and WarrantiesIf you go to an unauthorized garage to have your car serviced, the ___ is that your warranty will be invalid."}, "2441": {"1": "inferred", "2": "implied", "3": "imputed", "4": "involved", "answer": "implied", "question": "The guarantee, as I understood it, ___ that everything was covered."}, "2442": {"1": "died", "2": "deceased", "3": "expired", "4": "extinguished", "answer": "expired", "question": "I regret to inform you that as your guarantee ___ last week, we can't help you."}, "2443": {"1": "privilege", "2": "practice", "3": "printout", "4": "promise", "answer": "promise", "question": "A warranty is to be looked on as a sort of ___ between the manufacturer and you."}, "2444": {"1": "repute", "2": "reputed", "3": "reputedly", "4": "reputation", "answer": "reputation", "question": "Sometimes people don't bother about guarantees because the ___ of the manufacturer is enough for them."}, "2445": {"1": "remand", "2": "repeat", "3": "require", "4": "retain", "answer": "require", "question": "Certain warranties ___ the purchaser to have the item serviced at regular intervals."}, "2446": {"1": "famously", "2": "frequently", "3": "fervently", "4": "freely", "answer": "frequently", "question": "You will find that such warranties are not worth buying because the cover provided is ___ not worth the extraexpense."}, "2447": {"1": "provide", "2": "protect", "3": "please", "4": "pacify", "answer": "protect", "question": "This kind of legislation is in existence to ___ the customer from worthless warranties."}, "2448": {"1": "consider", "2": "contend", "3": "contain", "4": "convince", "answer": "consider", "question": "You sometimes have to ___ very seriously whether to buy a second hand car which has no guarantee."}, "2449": {"1": "various", "2": "variable", "3": "variety", "4": "vary", "answer": "vary", "question": "Sometimes you get a one year warranty, a two year one or even a six month one  they all ___"}, "2450": {"1": "road", "2": "corner", "3": "route", "4": "side", "answer": "side", "question": "How to agreeYou can be absolutely sure I'm on your ___"}, "2451": {"1": "show", "2": "rely", "3": "try", "4": "test", "answer": "rely", "question": "You can ___on me for your support."}, "2452": {"1": "convert", "2": "concert", "3": "conduct", "4": "coincide", "answer": "coincide", "question": "Our views clearly___ at this point I'm pleased to say."}, "2453": {"1": "hymn", "2": "prayer", "3": "lyric", "4": "sermon", "answer": "hymn", "question": "Fortunately the leader and all her members were singing from the same ___sheet."}, "2454": {"1": "seeing", "2": "peeping", "3": "looking", "4": "viewing", "answer": "looking", "question": "It's good that we both have the same way of ___at things."}, "2455": {"1": "sound", "2": "tone", "3": "harmony", "4": "voice", "answer": "voice", "question": "I'm pleased to say that we speak on this matter with one ___"}, "2456": {"1": "rise", "2": "raise", "3": "lift", "4": "arise", "answer": "raise", "question": "I certainly won't___ any objection when you make your proposal."}, "2457": {"1": "with", "2": "by", "3": "at", "4": "across", "answer": "with", "question": "I'm ___you all the way as far as that's concerned."}, "2458": {"1": "encompass", "2": "enthuse", "3": "endorse", "4": "endure", "answer": "endorse", "question": "I'm happy to ___those sentiments and wish you every success."}, "2459": {"1": "head", "2": "chin", "3": "arm", "4": "hand", "answer": "hand", "question": "When it comes to the vote I'm willing to put my ___up and support you."}, "2460": {"1": "forget", "2": "forfeit", "3": "forbid", "4": "forgive", "answer": "forgive", "question": "How to apologizePlease ___me for interrupting you, I didn't realize you were busy with someone else."}, "2461": {"1": "sore", "2": "sorry", "3": "sorrow", "4": "sorrowful", "answer": "sorry", "question": "I'm very ___that I'm late but there is a train strike on at the moment."}, "2462": {"1": "apologies", "2": "apologize", "3": "apologized", "4": "apologizing", "answer": "apologies", "question": "Please send my ___to the meeting as I shan't be able to attend."}, "2463": {"1": "exception", "2": "escape", "3": "excuse", "4": "exclusion", "answer": "excuse", "question": "There's really no ___for my behaviour last night. I can only think that I'd had too much to drink."}, "2464": {"1": "review", "2": "regret", "3": "respect", "4": "restore", "answer": "regret", "question": "I know I shouldn't have made those remarks about your work and I hope you now know how deeply I ___what I said."}, "2465": {"1": "bid", "2": "bide", "3": "beggar", "4": "beg", "answer": "beg", "question": "I must ___your pardon, I mistook you for somebody else."}, "2466": {"1": "again", "2": "back", "3": "in", "4": "across", "answer": "back", "question": "If it helps to put things right, please let me take ___everything I said earlier."}, "2467": {"1": "attempts", "2": "attention", "3": "amends", "4": "arrears", "answer": "amends", "question": "Please accept this small present as my way of making___ for all the trouble I've caused."}, "2468": {"1": "interest", "2": "interpretation", "3": "inclination", "4": "indulgence", "answer": "indulgence", "question": "All I can do now is simply beg your ___and hope that in time we can get back to where we used to be."}, "2469": {"1": "repent", "2": "restore", "3": "repeat", "4": "request", "answer": "repent", "question": "In their religion as long as they ___, they will be forgiven their sins."}, "2470": {"1": "route", "2": "way", "3": "sign", "4": "direction", "answer": "direction", "question": "How to ask the wayAm I going in the right___ for the post office?"}, "2471": {"1": "come", "2": "get", "3": "take", "4": "fetch", "answer": "get", "question": "Can you tell me please how I ___to the cinema from here?"}, "2472": {"1": "show", "2": "indicate", "3": "point", "4": "deliver", "answer": "point", "question": "Could you please___me in the direction of the motorway?"}, "2473": {"1": "straight", "2": "clear", "3": "obvious", "4": "direct", "answer": "direct", "question": "I'm making for the M25 motorway  is this road the most ___route?"}, "2474": {"1": "near", "2": "far", "3": "close", "4": "away", "answer": "far", "question": "Could you tell me please how ___I am from the town centre?"}, "2475": {"1": "need", "2": "require", "3": "request", "4": "must", "answer": "need", "question": "Can you help please because I've lost my way and ___to get to the shops before closing time?"}, "2476": {"1": "seeking", "2": "making", "3": "seeing", "4": "trying", "answer": "making", "question": "I'm ___for the town hall  am I anywhere near?"}, "2477": {"1": "turn", "2": "turner", "3": "turned", "4": "turning", "answer": "turning", "question": "I took the wrong ___at the last road junction, can you tell me how I get back on the motorway?"}, "2478": {"1": "Following", "2": "After", "3": "According", "4": "considering", "answer": "According", "question": "___ to this map I should be near the church. Is it near?"}, "2479": {"1": "correct", "2": "clear", "3": "fine", "4": "right", "answer": "right", "question": "Is this ___for the railway station?"}, "2480": {"1": "dealt", "2": "handled", "3": "done", "4": "fingered", "answer": "handled", "question": "How to complainI'm really not satisfied with the way you have___the situation."}, "2481": {"1": "action", "2": "acting", "3": "acted", "4": "active", "answer": "action", "question": "I've really had enough of all your excuses, what I want is some ___"}, "2482": {"1": "on", "2": "longer", "3": "far", "4": "further", "answer": "further", "question": "You've refused to help me now for six months and so I shall now have to take the matter___"}, "2483": {"1": "persist", "2": "desist", "3": "insist", "4": "consist", "answer": "insist", "question": "I must ___you do something immediately as I've been patient long enough."}, "2484": {"1": "lack", "2": "fail", "3": "failing", "4": "missing", "answer": "lack", "question": "I now want some kind of compensation for the total___ of service I've experienced."}, "2485": {"1": "older", "2": "above", "3": "over", "4": "senior", "answer": "senior", "question": "I'm obviously not getting anywhere with my complaint please let me talk to someone ___to you."}, "2486": {"1": "considered", "2": "treated", "3": "placed", "4": "pushed", "answer": "treated", "question": "I'm very unhappy with the way I've been ___. No one seems at all interested in my case."}, "2487": {"1": "lands", "2": "terrains", "3": "grounds", "4": "areas", "answer": "grounds", "question": "I believe I have very good___ for suing your company for negligence."}, "2488": {"1": "held", "2": "ordered", "3": "commanded", "4": "forced", "answer": "forced", "question": "If you don't do something today, I shall be ___to take legal action."}, "2489": {"1": "mood", "2": "temper", "3": "state", "4": "feeling", "answer": "temper", "question": "You're the tenth person I've been put through to and I'm on the point of losing my ___"}, "2490": {"1": "lot", "2": "few", "3": "little", "4": "much", "answer": "much", "question": "How to criticizeQuite honestly I didn't think___ of the standard of acting in the play."}, "2491": {"1": "honoured", "2": "honourable", "3": "honest", "4": "honour", "answer": "honest", "question": "If you want my ___opinion, I thought the food tasted revolting."}, "2492": {"1": "summit", "2": "top", "3": "topic", "4": "point", "answer": "point", "question": "To come straight to the ___I think the management team needs replacing."}, "2493": {"1": "outcome", "2": "outlook", "3": "issue", "4": "outing", "answer": "issue", "question": "There are several matters on which I should like to take___ concerning your report."}, "2494": {"1": "treading", "2": "footing", "3": "walking", "4": "tripping", "answer": "footing", "question": "There's really no virtue in me pussy___around because I might as well tell you it's awful."}, "2495": {"1": "story", "2": "description", "3": "file", "4": "list", "answer": "list", "question": "I have a long ___of things I think are wrong, where shall I start?"}, "2496": {"1": "considerable", "2": "believable", "3": "acceptable", "4": "available", "answer": "acceptable", "question": "I'm afraid to tell you that your standard of work has fallen well below what we think is ___"}, "2497": {"1": "lying", "2": "laying", "3": "loading", "4": "letting", "answer": "lying", "question": "In all honesty if I said that everything was all right, I'd simply be ___"}, "2498": {"1": "anywhere", "2": "elsewhere", "3": "nowhere", "4": "somewhere", "answer": "elsewhere", "question": "If you can't improve your level of work, I'm afraid you'll have to look ___for another job."}, "2499": {"1": "weary", "2": "exhausted", "3": "fatigued", "4": "tired", "answer": "tired", "question": "I'm sick and ___of always having to put right your mistakes."}, "2500": {"1": "take", "2": "share", "3": "give", "4": "find", "answer": "share", "question": "How to disagreeI'm sorry but I can't ___your opinion on that."}, "2501": {"1": "divide", "2": "devise", "3": "part", "4": "leave", "answer": "part", "question": "I very much regret that we must ___company on that issue."}, "2502": {"1": "apposed", "2": "imposed", "3": "supposed", "4": "opposed", "answer": "opposed", "question": "Let's be honest about it we'll never agree on that because our views are diametrically ___"}, "2503": {"1": "ask", "2": "bid", "3": "beg", "4": "try", "answer": "beg", "question": "We'll never agree, that's clear so let's ___to differ."}, "2504": {"1": "away", "2": "along", "3": "back", "4": "home", "answer": "home", "question": "You can argue with me till the cows come ___but I can't accept that."}, "2505": {"1": "basic", "2": "own", "3": "common", "4": "similar", "answer": "common", "question": "I really see no point in continuing this argument because we have no ___ground."}, "2506": {"1": "meet", "2": "hold", "3": "take", "4": "find", "answer": "meet", "question": "There's absolutely no way I can ___you on that matter."}, "2507": {"1": "thought", "2": "mind", "3": "idea", "4": "heart", "answer": "mind", "question": "Nothing in the world will ever make me change my ___on that subject."}, "2508": {"1": "principal", "2": "principles", "3": "principally", "4": "principle", "answer": "principle", "question": "I would love to meet you half way but I'm afraid I can't because with me it's a matter of ___"}, "2509": {"1": "look", "2": "take", "3": "face", "4": "see", "answer": "face", "question": "Let's ___it, you and I will never see eye to eye on this."}, "2510": {"1": "made", "2": "done", "3": "finished", "4": "taken", "answer": "done", "question": "How to encourageWell ___! This is a very good piece of work."}, "2511": {"1": "Continue", "2": "Take", "3": "Keep", "4": "Hold", "answer": "Keep", "question": "I must congratulate you on your efforts. ___it up!"}, "2512": {"1": "acquire", "2": "get", "3": "put", "4": "make", "answer": "make", "question": "Don't give up whatever you do. I'm sure you'll ___it in the end."}, "2513": {"1": "stand", "2": "keep", "3": "lean", "4": "support", "answer": "stand", "question": "I'll ___by you no matter what happens."}, "2514": {"1": "pursue", "2": "proceed", "3": "propel", "4": "persevere", "answer": "persevere", "question": "I'm sure if you ___, you'll succeed."}, "2515": {"1": "control", "2": "power", "3": "talent", "4": "strength", "answer": "talent", "question": "You've clearly got ___and it's obvious that you'll get to the top."}, "2516": {"1": "think", "2": "trust", "3": "hold", "4": "believe", "answer": "believe", "question": "I've watched a lot of young people try to make a success of it, but you're the only one I really ___in."}, "2517": {"1": "cause", "2": "sense", "3": "reason", "4": "doubt", "answer": "reason", "question": "I see no ___why you shouldn't be accepted as an employee."}, "2518": {"1": "give", "2": "do", "3": "take", "4": "try", "answer": "give", "question": "Never ___up. That's a good philosophy."}, "2519": {"1": "taken", "2": "held", "3": "put", "4": "pushed", "answer": "put", "question": "You mustn't ever be___ off by a few setbacks."}, "2520": {"1": "off", "2": "by", "3": "on", "4": "in", "answer": "on", "question": "How to make exclamationsWhat a wonderful day to see the mountains ___!"}, "2521": {"1": "forgot", "2": "deserted", "3": "traced", "4": "left", "answer": "left", "question": "How stupid can I get! I ___my keys in the door overnight."}, "2522": {"1": "criticizing", "2": "telling", "3": "complaining", "4": "calling", "answer": "complaining", "question": "For goodness sake stop ___about the weather! It'll stop raining soon."}, "2523": {"1": "tail", "2": "end", "3": "finish", "4": "part", "answer": "tail", "question": "What on earth are you talking about? I can't make head or ___of it."}, "2524": {"1": "path", "2": "journey", "3": "route", "4": "way", "answer": "way", "question": "How nice of you to come all this ___just to wish me a happy birthday."}, "2525": {"1": "off", "2": "wrong", "3": "incorrect", "4": "false", "answer": "wrong", "question": "What a disaster! I don't believe anything else could go___ now."}, "2526": {"1": "job", "2": "work", "3": "task", "4": "duty", "answer": "job", "question": "Wow! You've certainly made a good___ of decorating this room."}, "2527": {"1": "succeeded", "2": "passed", "3": "caught", "4": "tackled", "answer": "passed", "question": "Well blow me down! I just can't believe I've actually ___my exam."}, "2528": {"1": "certainly", "2": "surely", "3": "naturally", "4": "actually", "answer": "actually", "question": "You could have knocked me down with a feather! You mean to say he's ___cleaned my car."}, "2529": {"1": "last", "2": "length", "3": "least", "4": "end", "answer": "least", "question": "I'll go to the foot of my stairs! It must be at ___years since we last met."}, "2530": {"1": "contract", "2": "policy", "3": "agreement", "4": "deal", "answer": "policy", "question": "Insurance Policy VocabularyI took out a life insurance___with State Ranch Insurance Company last week."}, "2531": {"1": "receipts", "2": "fees", "3": "premiums", "4": "payings", "answer": "premiums", "question": "My insurance ___are only $70 per month."}, "2532": {"1": "recipient", "2": "widow", "3": "donor", "4": "beneficiary", "answer": "beneficiary", "question": "In the event of my death, the ___will be my widow."}, "2533": {"1": "collect", "2": "cover", "3": "console", "4": "contribute", "answer": "cover", "question": "My insurance does not ___me if I commit suicide."}, "2534": {"1": "manager", "2": "archivist", "3": "actuary", "4": "agent", "answer": "actuary", "question": "The amount of money that my wife will get has already been calculated by State Ranch's ___"}, "2535": {"1": "rebate", "2": "surrender", "3": "discount", "4": "return", "answer": "return", "question": "If I decide that I no longer need my insurance, I can cash it in for the amount of its___ value."}, "2536": {"1": "investigation", "2": "injection", "3": "therapy", "4": "examination", "answer": "examination", "question": "Before I got the insurance, I had to receive a complete physical ___."}, "2537": {"1": "length", "2": "line", "3": "expectancy", "4": "experience", "answer": "expectancy", "question": "I am feeling great, because the doctor told me that I have a life ___of 82 years!"}, "2538": {"1": "grace", "2": "satisfaction", "3": "long", "4": "latent", "answer": "grace", "question": "Even if I am late in paying, the insurance remains in effect for a ___period of 30 days."}, "2539": {"1": "troubles", "2": "involvements", "3": "hazards", "4": "duties", "answer": "hazards", "question": "The insurance is pretty expensive though: I am a policeman, so there are a lot of occupational ___"}, "2540": {"1": "affective", "2": "addictive", "3": "effective", "4": "reductive", "answer": "effective", "question": "It's no good spending a small fortune on new IT equipment as it's more cost ___ to hire it."}, "2541": {"1": "down", "2": "cut", "3": "out", "4": "through", "answer": "down", "question": "One of the fashionable ways of saying you've been sacked is to say that your company is ___sizing butyou've still lost your job."}, "2542": {"1": "in", "2": "inter", "3": "out", "4": "across", "answer": "inter", "question": "The important thing to realise is that your service is not a little island on its own because all the services in thiscompany are ___connected."}, "2543": {"1": "worldly", "2": "mondial", "3": "globular", "4": "global", "answer": "global", "question": "Whereas ten years ago we only dealt with customers in this country nowadays we are truly ___ with branchesall over the world."}, "2544": {"1": "communication", "2": "concentration", "3": "contemplation", "4": "consideration", "answer": "communication", "question": "One of the most successful tools in your organisation is that of good ___ because everybody knows what'sgoing on."}, "2545": {"1": "restore", "2": "retake", "3": "recap", "4": "redo", "answer": "recap", "question": "Let me just ___ what we have agreed in the agenda so far if nobody minds me going over it all again."}, "2546": {"1": "address", "2": "access", "3": "acceptance", "4": "approach", "answer": "access", "question": "You have to realise that not all your clients can reach you online because they don't have ___ to a computer."}, "2547": {"1": "movement", "2": "mastery", "3": "manifestation", "4": "motivation", "answer": "motivation", "question": "There are times when you have to force yourself to improve your performance and that's simply called self-___"}, "2548": {"1": "term", "2": "period", "3": "length", "4": "time", "answer": "term", "question": "You must think big in this business and not just think short ___ but what you hope to do in ten years' time."}, "2549": {"1": "draining", "2": "filtering", "3": "cleaning", "4": "dredging", "answer": "filtering", "question": "Her job in the company was to sort out the relevant information thereby ___ it so that only appropriatematerial was sent to her directors."}, "2550": {"1": "circle", "2": "round", "3": "curve", "4": "wheel", "answer": "wheel", "question": "She told him to stop wasting time by coming up with tried and tested ideas and in this way simply re-inventingthe ___"}, "2551": {"1": "enhancement", "2": "enthusiasm", "3": "endeavour", "4": "enticement", "answer": "enhancement", "question": "The product had been on the market for some years and was selling well but somehow the image was in needof a face lift or ___"}, "2552": {"1": "gangways", "2": "portals", "3": "doorways", "4": "passages", "answer": "portals", "question": "In the hope of finding fresh ideas he used the internet to help him by using as many search ___ as he coulddiscover."}, "2553": {"1": "dripping", "2": "floating", "3": "tapping", "4": "sailing", "answer": "tapping", "question": "You must increase the sale of this commodity by trying to interest a different age range and by ___ into theirsociety."}, "2554": {"1": "generate", "2": "generalize", "3": "germinate", "4": "engender", "answer": "generate", "question": "You'll never make any more money or ___ new income if you keep using that unimaginative marketing logo."}, "2555": {"1": "measurement", "2": "distance", "3": "width", "4": "dimension", "answer": "dimension", "question": "Now that you've explained the scope and ___ of the market, we are very keen to inject some money into yourproject."}, "2556": {"1": "venture", "2": "journey", "3": "adventure", "4": "voyage", "answer": "venture", "question": "There is always a risk in any business ___ when your scheme is based on an entirely new concept."}, "2557": {"1": "place", "2": "lead", "3": "leading", "4": "leader", "answer": "lead", "question": "Get in there first and don't hesitate to act as the boss and take the ___"}, "2558": {"1": "ease", "2": "case", "3": "power", "4": "ability", "answer": "ability", "question": "Interviews and JobsOne of the most important qualities which the panel is looking for in a candidate is the ___to work withothers."}, "2559": {"1": "across", "2": "in", "3": "up", "4": "along", "answer": "up", "question": "Once the applications have been looked at the usual procedure for the panel is to follow ___the references ofthose candidates who have been shortlisted."}, "2560": {"1": "delay", "2": "hesitate", "3": "waiver", "4": "dither", "answer": "hesitate", "question": "They were so impressed with the way she reacted to their questions that they didn't ___to offer her the job."}, "2561": {"1": "expert", "2": "exponent", "3": "exhibitor", "4": "expedient", "answer": "expert", "question": "As this job was of a very specialist nature an ___was invited to join the interview panel."}, "2562": {"1": "always", "2": "ever", "3": "constantly", "4": "competently", "answer": "constantly", "question": "After the interview one of the candidates ___phoned the office to see whether he had been successful."}, "2563": {"1": "called on", "2": "called in", "3": "called over", "4": "called off", "answer": "called in", "question": "She was in such a state of extreme nervousness when she was ___for the interview that she burst into tears."}, "2564": {"1": "reference", "2": "history", "3": "family", "4": "background", "answer": "background", "question": "From the point of view of relevant___ she was the ideal candidate at least on paper."}, "2565": {"1": "concern", "2": "continuity", "3": "confidence", "4": "confirmation", "answer": "confidence", "question": "It is absolutely essential in an interview to give the impression at least that you are full of ___"}, "2566": {"1": "weaknesses", "2": "varieties", "3": "virtues", "4": "variables", "answer": "weaknesses", "question": "One of the most popular questions asked of interviewees is to explain their strengths and ___"}, "2567": {"1": "display", "2": "present", "3": "show", "4": "demonstrate", "answer": "present", "question": "Each candidate was asked to ___a short account of how they saw the future of the company."}, "2568": {"1": "figure", "2": "charge", "3": "number", "4": "charging", "answer": "charge", "question": "InvoicesThere is an additional ___ added to the price of the product if you want to have it delivered to your house."}, "2569": {"1": "reasons", "2": "types", "3": "lists", "4": "terms", "answer": "terms", "question": "You should have read the ___ of payment as soon as you received the invoice for the goods."}, "2570": {"1": "officious", "2": "effecting", "3": "efficient", "4": "affected", "answer": "efficient", "question": "In order to cut down the expenses of compiling and sending out the invoices, you need to employ an ___administrator."}, "2571": {"1": "interest", "2": "estimate", "3": "esteem", "4": "actual", "answer": "estimate", "question": "It's always a good idea to get an ___ of what the cost of the work will be before the invoice lands on yourdoormat."}, "2572": {"1": "prompt", "2": "private", "3": "promoted", "4": "prominent", "answer": "prompt", "question": "I do like to get a ___ reply to my letters especially when they are referring to the amount of money I'msupposed to be paying."}, "2573": {"1": "error", "2": "trip", "3": "mistake", "4": "damage", "answer": "mistake", "question": "Just as we were about to leave the restaurant, the waiter came running up to apologize there had been a ___in the bill."}, "2574": {"1": "correct", "2": "rectified", "3": "stamped", "4": "righted", "answer": "rectified", "question": "The company were very quick to point out it was their fault we had been sent the wrong invoice and they ___it immediately."}, "2575": {"1": "discord", "2": "dispute", "3": "dislike", "4": "discount", "answer": "discount", "question": "In view of our previous orders over the last year we were offered a 10% ___ on any future dealings."}, "2576": {"1": "customer", "2": "courier", "3": "courtier", "4": "custom", "answer": "customer", "question": "He appreciated the additional welcome and help he received from the department store staff as he had afterall been a longstanding ___"}, "2577": {"1": "insisted", "2": "imposed", "3": "inserted", "4": "indented", "answer": "imposed", "question": "She got quite angry about the size of the invoice until it was pointed out that it was the government who ___the value added tax."}, "2578": {"1": "foreground", "2": "background", "3": "knowledge", "4": "history", "answer": "background", "question": "Job InterviewTell us something about your ___in the engineering industry?"}, "2579": {"1": "apply", "2": "applying", "3": "applied", "4": "application", "answer": "application", "question": "I see from your___ form that you have had three different jobs in the last 5 years."}, "2580": {"1": "span", "2": "duration", "3": "period", "4": "long", "answer": "period", "question": "What sort of ___of time would you stay with us if we offered you the job?"}, "2581": {"1": "you", "2": "your", "3": "yours", "4": "yourself", "answer": "yourself", "question": "Describe how you would describe ___in five years' time."}, "2582": {"1": "strength", "2": "strengths", "3": "force", "4": "forces", "answer": "strengths", "question": "Give us some idea of what you believe are your ___and weaknesses."}, "2583": {"1": "house", "2": "space", "3": "time", "4": "record", "answer": "time", "question": "As this is a managerial post, we must ask you how you deal with bad ___keeping or unpunctuality in anemployee."}, "2584": {"1": "take", "2": "do", "3": "handle", "4": "deal", "answer": "deal", "question": "Imagine one of your staff loses her temper and shouts at you in front of others, how would you ___with this?"}, "2585": {"1": "delivered", "2": "handed", "3": "produced", "4": "completed", "answer": "handed", "question": "What would you say to a member of your staff who always ___his work in late?"}, "2586": {"1": "believe", "2": "show", "3": "decide", "4": "honour", "answer": "honour", "question": "I should explain that we would naturally___ any previous holiday arrangements you have made."}, "2587": {"1": "place", "2": "put", "3": "offer", "4": "consider", "answer": "put", "question": "Finally now that we've asked you several questions, do you want to ___any to us?"}, "2588": {"1": "turning", "2": "snapping", "3": "holding", "4": "breaking", "answer": "breaking", "question": "Legal ExpressionsIf you drive faster than the stated speed limit, you are simply ___ the law."}, "2589": {"1": "fingers", "2": "hands", "3": "mind", "4": "control", "answer": "hands", "question": "However angry you may get at what someone has done to you, the police always advise you not to take thelaw into your own ___"}, "2590": {"1": "by", "2": "for", "3": "through", "4": "against", "answer": "against", "question": "In London in any underground station it is ___ the law to smoke."}, "2591": {"1": "arm", "2": "feel", "3": "stretch", "4": "reach", "answer": "arm", "question": "Even if you think you may have got away with a crime, in most cases the long ___ of the law will catch you."}, "2592": {"1": "animals", "2": "zoo", "3": "jungle", "4": "forest", "answer": "jungle", "question": "In that particular industry everyone has to look after themselves because the law of the ___ rules."}, "2593": {"1": "unto", "2": "into", "3": "outside", "4": "across", "answer": "unto", "question": "They have no respect for modern conventions and do exactly what they want  they are a law ___themselves."}, "2594": {"1": "lie", "2": "lies", "3": "lay", "4": "lays", "answer": "lay", "question": "Her parents are very strict and frequently ___ down the law about the way she behaves."}, "2595": {"1": "print", "2": "number", "3": "point", "4": "letter", "answer": "letter", "question": "Although technically his judgement was not according to the ___ of the law, most people thought the judgewas right to let the man go free."}, "2596": {"1": "above", "2": "over", "3": "superior", "4": "higher", "answer": "above", "question": "I get the impression sometimes that she thinks she can never do anything wrong almost as if she is ___ thelaw."}, "2597": {"1": "ease", "2": "order", "3": "correct", "4": "structure", "answer": "order", "question": "All governments want people to live in peace and comfort and so they try to promote a sense of law and___"}, "2598": {"1": "appoint", "2": "appointee", "3": "appointment", "4": "appointing", "answer": "appointment", "question": "and to try and make an ___to meet you and discuss my problem with you have been unsuccessful."}, "2599": {"1": "simple", "2": "same", "3": "extreme", "4": "very", "answer": "very", "question": "I would like to tell you the story from the ___beginning."}, "2600": {"1": "cash", "2": "money", "3": "cheque", "4": "pounds", "answer": "cash", "question": "In January this year I bought a washing machine from you for which I paid ___"}, "2601": {"1": "instigations", "2": "arrangements", "3": "alterations", "4": "confirmations", "answer": "arrangements", "question": "and made ___for it to be delivered to my home in Southcote on the following Tuesday."}, "2602": {"1": "intention", "2": "regard", "3": "purpose", "4": "plan", "answer": "purpose", "question": "I stayed in all day on ___as you had informed me that you could not be sure at what time of day the washingmachine would arrive."}, "2603": {"1": "will", "2": "shall", "3": "ought", "4": "would", "answer": "would", "question": "In the end nobody came that day. When I phoned, I was told it ___come the following Tuesday."}, "2604": {"1": "vain", "2": "fault", "3": "vanity", "4": "error", "answer": "vain", "question": "Again I stayed in all day in___and there was no delivery."}, "2605": {"1": "eventfully", "2": "event", "3": "eventually", "4": "events", "answer": "eventually", "question": "After six more phone calls I ___succeeded in settling on a date"}, "2606": {"1": "promising", "2": "promised", "3": "promises", "4": "promise", "answer": "promised", "question": "and the machine came on Tuesday February 20th  almost 5 weeks after the ___delivery date."}, "2607": {"1": "Appearing", "2": "Appearance", "3": "Apparition", "4": "Apparently", "answer": "Apparently", "question": "___ one of the components was faulty and he recommended that I got back to you so that a replacementcould be fitted."}, "2608": {"1": "criterion", "2": "situation", "3": "place", "4": "happening", "answer": "situation", "question": "When I telephoned your store and explained the ___to your receptionist,"}, "2609": {"1": "told", "2": "remarked", "3": "said", "4": "greeted", "answer": "greeted", "question": "I was ___with the comment, 'Oh not you again'"}, "2610": {"1": "offended", "2": "offending", "3": "offensive", "4": "offends", "answer": "offensive", "question": "which I found most___especially since throughout the protracted period of waiting for the machine"}, "2611": {"1": "hitting", "2": "kicking", "3": "knocking", "4": "striking", "answer": "kicking", "question": "I remained calm although I believe I have every reason for ___up a fuss."}, "2612": {"1": "through", "2": "over", "3": "in", "4": "across", "answer": "through", "question": "I eventually got put___to the technical department"}, "2613": {"1": "to", "2": "in", "3": "by", "4": "off", "answer": "off", "question": "who were most ___hand"}, "2614": {"1": "less", "2": "little", "3": "least", "4": "few", "answer": "little", "question": "and told me there was ___that could be done immediately"}, "2615": {"1": "through", "2": "for", "3": "off", "4": "under", "answer": "off", "question": "since there were a number of people ___sick."}, "2616": {"1": "defective", "2": "deficient", "3": "defining", "4": "defeating", "answer": "defective", "question": "and one of your technical staff came out to see me with the intention of replacing the ___part."}, "2617": {"1": "delivered", "2": "fetched", "3": "brought", "4": "picked", "answer": "brought", "question": "Unfortunately he had___ the wrong part with him"}, "2618": {"1": "unable", "2": "unsure", "3": "unskilled", "4": "untrained", "answer": "unsure", "question": "and was very ___as to when he would be able to find the right part and get it back to me."}, "2619": {"1": "position", "2": "spot", "3": "time", "4": "place", "answer": "place", "question": "Another visit took ___in late April but the engineer, although he had got the right part with him, was unable tomake the washing machine work."}, "2620": {"1": "rid", "2": "riddance", "3": "hold", "4": "loose", "answer": "rid", "question": "It was at this stage that I was seriously considering getting ___of the machine"}, "2621": {"1": "repeat", "2": "refund", "3": "replace", "4": "return", "answer": "refund", "question": "and asking for a ___"}, "2622": {"1": "rose", "2": "risen", "3": "arose", "4": "raised", "answer": "raised", "question": "When I ___this matter with one of your staff"}, "2623": {"1": "problem", "2": "concern", "3": "question", "4": "hand", "answer": "question", "question": "I was informed that this was out of the ___"}, "2624": {"1": "near", "2": "next", "3": "soon", "4": "coming", "answer": "near", "question": "and they would send someone in the '___future'."}, "2625": {"1": "everything", "2": "now", "3": "then", "4": "all", "answer": "all", "question": "and meet you face to face so that the matter could be settled once and for ___"}, "2626": {"1": "Admittedly", "2": "Admitting", "3": "Confessing", "4": "Allowing", "answer": "Admittedly", "question": "___ I should have checked first since when I reached the shop I was led to believe that you were out for theday."}, "2627": {"1": "faculty", "2": "facility", "3": "ability", "4": "control", "answer": "facility", "question": "Throughout this time of course I have been without the___ of a washing machine"}, "2628": {"1": "launder", "2": "laundering", "3": "launderette", "4": "launderer", "answer": "launderette", "question": "and have had to use the local ___"}, "2629": {"1": "while", "2": "attending", "3": "from", "4": "during", "answer": "during", "question": "From the end of May until August I have been away on business and was surprised that ___that period"}, "2630": {"1": "on", "2": "up", "3": "in", "4": "over", "answer": "up", "question": "no effort has been made to write to me and keep me ___to date."}, "2631": {"1": "tether", "2": "line", "3": "rope", "4": "cord", "answer": "tether", "question": "Since returning in September I have made at least a dozen phone calls and quite frankly I have reached theend of my ___."}, "2632": {"1": "persist", "2": "resist", "3": "insist", "4": "desist", "answer": "insist", "question": "and must ___that you do something immediately to put the matter right."}, "2633": {"1": "search", "2": "find", "3": "look", "4": "seek", "answer": "seek", "question": "If I do not hear from you by the end of this week I shall be forced to ___legal advice."}, "2634": {"1": "pocket", "2": "purse", "3": "case", "4": "hand", "answer": "hand", "question": "MoneyIt's useful when you go to an auction if you're ready with cash in ___"}, "2635": {"1": "solid", "2": "hard", "3": "real", "4": "actual", "answer": "hard", "question": "I prefer to deal in ___cash rather than cheques."}, "2636": {"1": "small", "2": "little", "3": "tiny", "4": "petty", "answer": "petty", "question": "Every office has a certain amount of ___cash to pay for things like tea, coffee or stamps."}, "2637": {"1": "fly", "2": "stream", "3": "flow", "4": "run", "answer": "flow", "question": "At the moment we are experiencing some cash ___problems because little money is coming in."}, "2638": {"1": "off", "2": "out", "3": "up", "4": "in", "answer": "in", "question": "At the casino you can cash___ your chips at the desk."}, "2639": {"1": "doing", "2": "making", "3": "massing", "4": "creating", "answer": "making", "question": "Whatever she does, she just can't help ___money."}, "2640": {"1": "facile", "2": "simple", "3": "easy", "4": "quick", "answer": "easy", "question": "There doesn't seem to be anyone working really hard for the business and yet they all seem to earn ___money."}, "2641": {"1": "order", "2": "command", "3": "instruction", "4": "directive", "answer": "order", "question": "If you don't want to use a cheque or postal order, you can always use a money___"}, "2642": {"1": "driver", "2": "worker", "3": "spinner", "4": "turner", "answer": "spinner", "question": "That new invention has been very successful and has proved to be a money ___for its creator."}, "2643": {"1": "back", "2": "again", "3": "return", "4": "up", "answer": "back", "question": "This machine is obviously useless and if I were you I'd get your money ___"}, "2644": {"1": "take off", "2": "take out", "3": "take over", "4": "take in", "answer": "take out", "question": "As the builder wanted cash for the work he had done, she had to go to the bank personally to ___ the moneyherself."}, "2645": {"1": "pledge", "2": "promise", "3": "mortgage", "4": "borrowing", "answer": "mortgage", "question": "It was considered a very good time to apply for a ___ to buy the house because interest rates were very low."}, "2646": {"1": "down", "2": "through", "3": "low", "4": "base", "answer": "down", "question": "Before they could borrow a large sum of money to buy the house, they had to make sure they had enoughmoney to be able to make a ___ payment."}, "2647": {"1": "movements", "2": "deals", "3": "activities", "4": "transactions", "answer": "transactions", "question": "All the ___ you make on your internet account are recorded so that you can check the details at any time."}, "2648": {"1": "signature", "2": "signs", "3": "signing", "4": "signed", "answer": "signature", "question": "I'm afraid this cheque will be of no value until you have put your ___ on it."}, "2649": {"1": "receive", "2": "take", "3": "accept", "4": "enter", "answer": "accept", "question": "The bank refused to ___ the money order because the customer had no proof of identity."}, "2650": {"1": "limiting", "2": "restriction", "3": "restricting", "4": "limitation", "answer": "restriction", "question": "Under the rules laid down by the bank there is a ___ on the amount of money you can get out from a cashmachine in any one day."}, "2651": {"1": "concerned", "2": "careful", "3": "conscious", "4": "cautious", "answer": "cautious", "question": "The bank clerk at the counter did not know the customer and in view of the large amount of money involvedwas naturally ___ about paying out the sum on the cheque."}, "2652": {"1": "lend", "2": "loan", "3": "borrow", "4": "remove", "answer": "borrow", "question": "The bank will simply not let you ___ any money unless you can prove that you have been in regularemployment for at least three years."}, "2653": {"1": "debt", "2": "debts", "3": "owing", "4": "owes", "answer": "debt", "question": "The company fell heavily into ___ when it took on too many customers and offered them all cheap warranties."}, "2654": {"1": "people", "2": "contributors", "3": "clients", "4": "members", "answer": "clients", "question": "Once you have built up your company, you must remember to keep in touch with your original ___"}, "2655": {"1": "sum", "2": "money", "3": "dividend", "4": "budget", "answer": "budget", "question": "Each department within the organisation is given a ___ within which it has to remain for the whole year."}, "2656": {"1": "earnings", "2": "assets", "3": "accumulation", "4": "asset", "answer": "assets", "question": "When the time came to close the business down, its entire ___ had to be calculated so that the creditorscould be paid off."}, "2657": {"1": "acquaint", "2": "resolve", "3": "reconcile", "4": "recognize", "answer": "reconcile", "question": "The manager called in her chief clerk because she could not ___ the figures on the monthly spreadsheet."}, "2658": {"1": "order", "2": "regulate", "3": "control", "4": "audit", "answer": "audit", "question": "Every year the college finance officer did not look forward to the visit from the government official who came to___ the accounts."}, "2659": {"1": "extraordinary", "2": "upstanding", "3": "outstanding", "4": "standing", "answer": "outstanding", "question": "It was a great relief to Charlie when he realized that he had come to the end of his agreement with the bankand there was only one ___ payment left."}, "2660": {"1": "lenders", "2": "borrowers", "3": "loans", "4": "takers", "answer": "borrowers", "question": "The building society sent a letter to all its savers and ___ that there would be a reduction in the interest rate."}, "2661": {"1": "accentuate", "2": "aggravate", "3": "accumulate", "4": "access", "answer": "accumulate", "question": "Shortly after the couple had bought their first house, they saw the number of bills ___ rapidly."}, "2662": {"1": "foundations", "2": "funds", "3": "findings", "4": "finds", "answer": "funds", "question": "There is no need to worry about the money side of the project because ___ are available from the charitysponsoring us."}, "2663": {"1": "concerned", "2": "considering", "3": "concerning", "4": "conservative", "answer": "conservative", "question": "The present finance minister has adopted a very ___ approach towards change and always follows a verycautious policy."}, "2664": {"1": "elongated", "2": "lengthy", "3": "long-term", "4": "longing", "answer": "long-term", "question": "As all advisers always do, she stressed that investing in this particular market had to be considered as a ___commitment over at least 10 years."}, "2665": {"1": "suitcase", "2": "portfolio", "3": "folder", "4": "briefcase", "answer": "portfolio", "question": "The best way to develop an income for the future is to invest in a series of companies and in that way to buildup a ___"}, "2666": {"1": "reward", "2": "reprise", "3": "return", "4": "response", "answer": "return", "question": "I strongly recommend investing in these shares because you will get a very good ___ after only a few years."}, "2667": {"1": "wisdom", "2": "wise", "3": "wisely", "4": "wisest", "answer": "wise", "question": "The question is whether it is ___ to sell up all your shares at this stage rather than wait to see how the marketis next year."}, "2668": {"1": "resort", "2": "resorted", "3": "resource", "4": "resorting", "answer": "resource", "question": "There is no question that the most important ___ in that company is its youthful enthusiasm."}, "2669": {"1": "attacking", "2": "aggression", "3": "fighting", "4": "invasion", "answer": "aggression", "question": "If you want to make a good job of selling shares to the public, you must have an element of ___ in yourapproach."}, "2670": {"1": "advance", "2": "approach", "3": "attitude", "4": "angle", "answer": "attitude", "question": "It's a personal matter whether you choose stock from this company or from that because in the end it's an ___of mind."}, "2671": {"1": "fill up", "2": "fill through", "3": "fill out", "4": "fill on", "answer": "fill out", "question": "If you are self-employed, you must make sure that you ___the form indicating how much you have earned."}, "2672": {"1": "return", "2": "reply", "3": "response", "4": "refund", "answer": "refund", "question": "If the department agrees that you have paid too much tax in the year, you will receive a ___in due course."}, "2673": {"1": "withholds", "2": "withstands", "3": "withdraws", "4": "without", "answer": "withholds", "question": "Each month when you receive your pay, the employer ___a certain amount to pay towards your pension."}, "2674": {"1": "own", "2": "lend", "3": "owe", "4": "take", "answer": "owe", "question": "When you take out a loan, you have to pay interest on the amount you ___"}, "2675": {"1": "file", "2": "box", "3": "book", "4": "container", "answer": "file", "question": "In the tax office there will be a ___that holds all the documents and papers connected with you."}, "2676": {"1": "punishment", "2": "pain", "3": "restriction", "4": "penalty", "answer": "penalty", "question": "There is quite a heavy financial ___ attached to any action that involves late payment of taxes."}, "2677": {"1": "figure", "2": "calculate", "3": "add", "4": "amount", "answer": "calculate", "question": "Under the new regulations you can agree yourself to ___the tax you have to pay on the income over theprevious year."}, "2678": {"1": "joint", "2": "united", "3": "unified", "4": "joined", "answer": "joint", "question": "As the couple had a ___account, the money to pay the mortage was taken from there."}, "2679": {"1": "give in", "2": "give up", "3": "give out", "4": "give off", "answer": "give up", "question": "You can decide, if you so wish, to ___your right to take your pension at an earlier date."}, "2680": {"1": "many", "2": "piles", "3": "loads", "4": "buckets", "answer": "loads", "question": "Money Slang ExpressionsMary: Did you know there are ___ of slang words for money, like bread for example?"}, "2681": {"1": "go", "2": "follow", "3": "take", "4": "come", "answer": "come", "question": "John: I suppose there are when you ___ to think about it  like dough, which is similar to your word bread."}, "2682": {"1": "favourites", "2": "collections", "3": "favourable", "4": "specials", "answer": "favourites", "question": "Mary: One of my ___ is dosh. I like the sound of it."}, "2683": {"1": "attending", "2": "referring", "3": "resorting", "4": "trying", "answer": "referring", "question": "John: Well if you're ___ to sound. What about spondulicks?"}, "2684": {"1": "attracts", "2": "adheres", "3": "appeals", "4": "attains", "answer": "appeals", "question": "Mary: Yes, that's excellent. Another short sound that ___ to me is brass."}, "2685": {"1": "sounds", "2": "strikes", "3": "hits", "4": "rhymes", "answer": "rhymes", "question": "John: Another one that ___ with jolly is the word lolly."}, "2686": {"1": "decadent", "2": "down", "3": "deep", "4": "divisive", "answer": "decadent", "question": "Mary: An expression which sounds very ___ of course is filthy lucre."}, "2687": {"1": "intention", "2": "signification", "3": "meaning", "4": "sense", "answer": "meaning", "question": "John: That's true and then there's that word that also has the same ___ as something that's been stolen loot."}, "2688": {"1": "protects", "2": "hides", "3": "places", "4": "holds", "answer": "hides", "question": "Mary: The one that sounds very grand because it in a way ___ the fact that it means money and that's thewherewithal."}, "2689": {"1": "awkward", "2": "backward", "3": "unused", "4": "embarrassed", "answer": "embarrassed", "question": "John: Actually, I'm a little ___ about this but I haven't any money to pay for the bus home. Do you think youcould lend me some readies?"}, "2690": {"1": "but", "2": "yet", "3": "neither", "4": "either", "answer": "either", "question": "Online Marketing CampaignShe was going to discuss the matter ___ with her colleagues or her family."}, "2691": {"1": "of", "2": "at", "3": "by", "4": "as", "answer": "of", "question": "Our project team tried hard to think ___ all the possible alternatives before making a decision."}, "2692": {"1": "strongly", "2": "greatly", "3": "extremely", "4": "already", "answer": "extremely", "question": "Timing can be ___ crucial when you're considering launching a new online marketing campaign."}, "2693": {"1": "except", "2": "expect", "3": "accept", "4": "access", "answer": "accept", "question": "Are you able to ___ our conditions of delivery in line with our recent invoice?"}, "2694": {"1": "prophet", "2": "profit", "3": "profitably", "4": "profits", "answer": "profit", "question": "Fortunately for us we're finding our new internet division is showing an increased ___"}, "2695": {"1": "fined", "2": "finding", "3": "found", "4": "finds", "answer": "found", "question": "Following some recent research our engineers ___ that our index system has scope for fast improvement."}, "2696": {"1": "except", "2": "but", "3": "besides", "4": "instead", "answer": "instead", "question": "In our line of business it is vital to host our website on our own server ___ of getting someone else to do it."}, "2697": {"1": "careful", "2": "caring", "3": "carefulness", "4": "carefully", "answer": "careful", "question": "Before you employ new staff you should carry out a ___ examination of their personal qualities andprofessional experience."}, "2698": {"1": "repute", "2": "reputable", "3": "reputation", "4": "reputedly", "answer": "reputation", "question": "Thanks to the high standards of service we offer our customers, we have been able to establish an excellent___"}, "2699": {"1": "signify", "2": "significant", "3": "significance", "4": "signification", "answer": "significant", "question": "An interactive website can save your organisation ___ amounts of time and money that would otherwise bespent on correspondence."}, "2700": {"1": "base", "2": "basis", "3": "ground", "4": "foundation", "answer": "basis", "question": "Pay and AllowancesOn the ___ of her ten years' service she immediately qualified for the extended annual leave of six weeks."}, "2701": {"1": "sincere", "2": "fragile", "3": "breakable", "4": "delicate", "answer": "delicate", "question": "Although he knew it was a sensitive subject, his boss had to ask him the ___ question about his drinkproblem."}, "2702": {"1": "negotiate", "2": "demonstrate", "3": "apply", "4": "dispute", "answer": "negotiate", "question": "At the interview each applicant was able to ___ the level of remuneration they would be expecting to receive."}, "2703": {"1": "malleable", "2": "shaped", "3": "flexible", "4": "bending", "answer": "flexible", "question": "Under the new ___ arrangements coming into force soon all employees can decide what time to start andwhen to finish."}, "2704": {"1": "allowed", "2": "illegible", "3": "selectable", "4": "eligible", "answer": "eligible", "question": "According to the contract you are not ___ for the new allowance until you have been with the company oneyear."}, "2705": {"1": "rise", "2": "raise", "3": "arise", "4": "raze", "answer": "raise", "question": "The only way you can hope to ___ the level of your pay is to take on greater responsibility."}, "2706": {"1": "cooperation", "2": "confirmation", "3": "compensation", "4": "consideration", "answer": "compensation", "question": "She is trying to get some form of ___ to make up for the poor working conditions she had to put up with for allthose years."}, "2707": {"1": "increase", "2": "benefit", "3": "grow", "4": "develop", "answer": "benefit", "question": "Of course there is a little extra added to your salary because you will ___ from the inner city allowance."}, "2708": {"1": "wage", "2": "validity", "3": "recompense", "4": "value", "answer": "wage", "question": "The hourly ___ for all part time clerical assistants has gone up by 40% since ."}, "2709": {"1": "return", "2": "retreat", "3": "respite", "4": "retire", "answer": "retire", "question": "Remember when you stop work and ___, you will be able to receive the company pension."}, "2710": {"1": "escape", "2": "endure", "3": "avoid", "4": "enter", "answer": "avoid", "question": "Planning a BusinessIt is essential before starting a business to work on a plan to ___ problems later on."}, "2711": {"1": "scene", "2": "risk", "3": "encounter", "4": "harm", "answer": "risk", "question": "The biggest ___ in business can be eliminated if you have sufficient capital to start with."}, "2712": {"1": "mighty", "2": "huge", "3": "hefty", "4": "strong", "answer": "strong", "question": "Even when the economic situation is ___, there is always present the need for planning in a new business."}, "2713": {"1": "consideration", "2": "criterion", "3": "substitute", "4": "contemplation", "answer": "substitute", "question": "Whatever happens in the future there is absolutely no ___ for good market research before you launch a newproduct."}, "2714": {"1": "firstly", "2": "primary", "3": "primarily", "4": "initially", "answer": "primary", "question": "Your ___ concern is naturally the plan but don't forget your capital or your premises."}, "2715": {"1": "encompass", "2": "evolve", "3": "evaluate", "4": "enquire", "answer": "evaluate", "question": "When people are considering whether to loan your new business a substantial sum, they are going to ___your potential."}, "2716": {"1": "including", "2": "snatching", "3": "grabbing", "4": "gathering", "answer": "gathering", "question": "It is worthwhile ___ as much market research information as possible before you work out your plan."}, "2717": {"1": "declare", "2": "demonstrate", "3": "state", "4": "announce", "answer": "demonstrate", "question": "Her next task was to have a meeting with the bank manager to ___ that she had a secure enough plan towarrant a loan."}, "2718": {"1": "affixed", "2": "acquired", "3": "addressed", "4": "attended", "answer": "addressed", "question": "There are certain weaknesses in your plan that need to be ___ urgently if you are to succeed."}, "2719": {"1": "developed", "2": "shown", "3": "gained", "4": "built", "answer": "developed", "question": "Since the start of the business many new ideas have ___ out of the original plan."}, "2720": {"1": "ask", "2": "calculate", "3": "ascertain", "4": "argue", "answer": "ascertain", "question": "Product ImprovementBefore the product is put on the market, the company must ___ whether it complies with safety standards."}, "2721": {"1": "revision", "2": "research", "3": "repeat", "4": "return", "answer": "research", "question": "It is absolutely essential to do some thorough ___ before you even think of putting a new product on themarket."}, "2722": {"1": "responsibility", "2": "concern", "3": "attitude", "4": "behaviour", "answer": "responsibility", "question": "You have a ___ to the public to ensure your toy products are suitable for children to play with."}, "2723": {"1": "answer", "2": "solve", "3": "discover", "4": "dissolve", "answer": "solve", "question": "The company is busy trying to ___ the problems arising from the sudden drop in sales of their cosmeticproducts."}, "2724": {"1": "controller", "2": "organizer", "3": "supervisor", "4": "governor", "answer": "organizer", "question": "The job of the ___ of this particular section is to train the members to deal politely with any complaints fromthe public."}, "2725": {"1": "systematic", "2": "thematic", "3": "automatic", "4": "emblematic", "answer": "systematic", "question": "Inspiration has its place in any form of product development but at the same time you also need to adoptsome kind of ___ approach."}, "2726": {"1": "physical", "2": "fundamental", "3": "judgmental", "4": "logical", "answer": "logical", "question": "A ___ approach to new ideas is to be welcomed but you do need a strong element of imagination as well."}, "2727": {"1": "period", "2": "decade", "3": "scale", "4": "time", "answer": "decade", "question": "Since  or if you like within the last ___, there have been many products that have failed because of poormarketing."}, "2728": {"1": "discover", "2": "uncover", "3": "examine", "4": "reflect", "answer": "examine", "question": "We would definitely like to ___ the proposal you have presented to us with a view to including it in our currentrange of products."}, "2729": {"1": "enterprise", "2": "experiment", "3": "undertaking", "4": "exception", "answer": "experiment", "question": "As we have enough money in our present budget, we are happy to launch this new product in the nature of an___"}, "2730": {"1": "types", "2": "species", "3": "brands", "4": "standards", "answer": "brands", "question": "Quality ControlThe reason why I always buy my clothes at this store is because all the___ they sell are of very high quality."}, "2731": {"1": "seen", "2": "looked at", "3": "appraised", "4": "inspected", "answer": "inspected", "question": "Before these articles leave the factory to be forwarded to the retailer, each one is thoroughly ___"}, "2732": {"1": "believe", "2": "think", "3": "perceive", "4": "hold", "answer": "perceive", "question": "The advantages of working for this company is that all employees ___themselves as a member of the team."}, "2733": {"1": "hold it back", "2": "take it back", "3": "keep it back", "4": "give it back", "answer": "take it back", "question": "If for any reason customers do not like the item they have bought, they always ___and get a refund."}, "2734": {"1": "wrinkles", "2": "twists", "3": "turns", "4": "folds", "answer": "wrinkles", "question": "The great thing about this particular material is that however much you screw it up, it never ___"}, "2735": {"1": "actual", "2": "identity", "3": "typical", "4": "uniform", "answer": "uniform", "question": "The company insists that all their products are ___in respect of their quality, specification and look."}, "2736": {"1": "cloth", "2": "garment", "3": "clothing", "4": "clothe", "answer": "garment", "question": "This is the department for children's clothes and each___ is marked with the recommended age range."}, "2737": {"1": "reject", "2": "repulse", "3": "repel", "4": "return", "answer": "repel", "question": "The sole purpose of this jacket is to ___water and if you wear it in the rain and still get wet, it's useless."}, "2738": {"1": "engrossed", "2": "enlarged", "3": "enveloped", "4": "enhanced", "answer": "enhanced", "question": "The whole look of the shop front is ___by the introduction of bright colours."}, "2739": {"1": "defect", "2": "mistake", "3": "error", "4": "faulting", "answer": "defect", "question": "These pots are being sold as seconds because each one has a slight ___in the glaze."}, "2740": {"1": "standing", "2": "stand", "3": "stance", "4": "status", "answer": "stance", "question": "Super SupermarketsIf you ask someone for their ___ on supermarkets as opposed to the small corner shop, you will get varyingreplies."}, "2741": {"1": "target", "2": "hit", "3": "aim", "4": "deliver", "answer": "target", "question": "The first question you have to ask is who are the customers that they are each trying to ___"}, "2742": {"1": "dispute", "2": "disdain", "3": "dislike", "4": "dismay", "answer": "dismay", "question": "When you tell the inhabitants of a small village that the little local store is going to close, many will express___"}, "2743": {"1": "cuts", "2": "splits", "3": "slices", "4": "pieces", "answer": "splits", "question": "There will naturally be ___ in the various sections of the community as to the benefits or disadvantages oflosing the little store."}, "2744": {"1": "plagued", "2": "attacked", "3": "stormed", "4": "bothered", "answer": "plagued", "question": "Of course we all get ___ with endless leaflets through the door telling us of bargains at the local supermarket."}, "2745": {"1": "nerve killing", "2": "nerve hurting", "3": "nerve racking", "4": "nerve splitting", "answer": "nerve racking", "question": "Big discussions take place in the area as to whether a supermarket will come to the area and waiting for theoutcome can be quite ___ for the small shop owner."}, "2746": {"1": "speeded through", "2": "speeded along", "3": "speeded up", "4": "speeded in", "answer": "speeded up", "question": "Inquiries are held which seem to go on forever and you only wish that the procedure could be ___"}, "2747": {"1": "disgrace", "2": "shambles", "3": "chaos", "4": "fall", "answer": "shambles", "question": "Protest meetings are held but invariably they end in a ___ because they are not organized properly."}, "2748": {"1": "joiner", "2": "combine", "3": "link", "4": "merger", "answer": "merger", "question": "Then the final result is announced that there is to be a ___ between EASISHOP and GOSHOP, which willthen become a super supermarket."}, "2749": {"1": "distress", "2": "disturb", "3": "dilemma", "4": "disturbance", "answer": "dilemma", "question": "The confused customer is now in a terrible ___ because in the old days there was just one brand of butter tobuy and now there is a choice of 24."}, "2750": {"1": "consider", "2": "complete", "3": "correct", "4": "calculate", "answer": "calculate", "question": "TaxesIf you are self-employed, it is your responsibility to ___ how much tax you should legally pay."}, "2751": {"1": "due", "2": "indebted", "3": "owed", "4": "owned", "answer": "owed", "question": "I had a letter from the office of the Collector of Taxes telling me that I had to pay back all the money I ___over the last 3 years."}, "2752": {"1": "joined", "2": "conjoined", "3": "joined up", "4": "joint", "answer": "joint", "question": "The arrangement they have is that all the money that has to be paid in tax out of their earnings comes fromtheir ___ account."}, "2753": {"1": "penalty", "2": "punishment", "3": "pain", "4": "penalize", "answer": "penalty", "question": "Under the current legislation if you are late in paying your taxes, then you have to face a financial ___"}, "2754": {"1": "dead end", "2": "deadline", "3": "dead date", "4": "dead stop", "answer": "deadline", "question": "He is in a terrible rush to complete his tax returns by Tuesday otherwise he won't be able to reach the ___"}, "2755": {"1": "remake", "2": "repeat", "3": "refund", "4": "respite", "answer": "refund", "question": "It doesn't happen very often but I actually got some money from the tax office and with the ___ I'm going totreat myself."}, "2756": {"1": "fill for", "2": "fill out", "3": "fill through", "4": "fill with", "answer": "fill out", "question": "Before you can claim any money back on overpayment of tax, you have to ___ an application form."}, "2757": {"1": "spouse", "2": "sponsor", "3": "spook", "4": "spokesperson", "answer": "spouse", "question": "You can elect, if you want, to transfer your tax free allowance to your ___"}, "2758": {"1": "withstand", "2": "without", "3": "withhold", "4": "withal", "answer": "withhold", "question": "Until it's clearly established which tax group you are in, your employer will be asked to ___ a certain amountof your pay."}, "2759": {"1": "full", "2": "filled", "3": "filling", "4": "file", "answer": "file", "question": "There have been so many queries about his tax situation that there is now a huge ___ containing the detailsin the office."}, "2760": {"1": "before", "2": "since", "3": "prior", "4": "previous", "answer": "prior", "question": "Verbal Communication SkillsRemember that this happened first and was ___ to the episode that happened afterwards."}, "2761": {"1": "need", "2": "requirement", "3": "indictment", "4": "necessity", "answer": "necessity", "question": "As the police saw the accident themselves, the driver avoided the ___ of having to give a detailed report."}, "2762": {"1": "arguing", "2": "discussing", "3": "repeating", "4": "considering", "answer": "arguing", "question": "It's a complete waste of time ___ over who was to blame, the main thing we have to do is decide what to donext."}, "2763": {"1": "complement", "2": "concern", "3": "consequence", "4": "conviction", "answer": "consequence", "question": "It was easy to realise why the machine had stopped working since it was a direct ___ of his failure to maintainit."}, "2764": {"1": "definite", "2": "difficult", "3": "debatable", "4": "decided", "answer": "difficult", "question": "I am completely confused as to why she did it and so it's not ___ to imagine why other people are mystified,too."}, "2765": {"1": "entrance", "2": "beginning", "3": "side", "4": "inside", "answer": "inside", "question": "If you want to try and influence that political party it's best to become a member yourself and then you canargue from the ___"}, "2766": {"1": "sincerity", "2": "sympathy", "3": "sorrow", "4": "sadness", "answer": "sympathy", "question": "I have great ___ for them at this time because I have had a similar experience."}, "2767": {"1": "retake", "2": "undertake", "3": "partake", "4": "intake", "answer": "partake", "question": "Feel free to visit anything of interest to you in the exhibition and also you can ___ of any of the refreshmentsavailable."}, "2768": {"1": "resented", "2": "regretted", "3": "rejoined", "4": "sympathized", "answer": "sympathized", "question": "Many of the people in the crowd were visibly crying because they all ___ with those who had lost relatives inthe disaster."}, "2769": {"1": "as", "2": "than", "3": "and", "4": "it", "answer": "as", "question": "I assure you that you will have no problem with the task because it's as easy ___ can be."}, "2770": {"1": "litter", "2": "dust", "3": "waste", "4": "rubbish", "answer": "rubbish", "question": "Ways of commentingIf you want my honest opinion, I thought the play was___"}, "2771": {"1": "paper", "2": "cardboard", "3": "plastic", "4": "material", "answer": "cardboard", "question": "It was quite a good film but I thought the characters were a bit like ___"}, "2772": {"1": "area", "2": "limit", "3": "room", "4": "fullness", "answer": "room", "question": "It's quite a nice car but there was not very much ___in the back."}, "2773": {"1": "plain", "2": "straight", "3": "simple", "4": "casual", "answer": "plain", "question": "She's pleasant enough but not very pretty. In fact I'd say she was rather ___"}, "2774": {"1": "out", "2": "over", "3": "under", "4": "away", "answer": "away", "question": "The first time you see the view you can't believe it. It almost takes your breath ___"}, "2775": {"1": "gaping", "2": "yawning", "3": "stretching", "4": "crying", "answer": "yawning", "question": "I sat through the concert feeling really bored and sleepy and had to stop myself from ___several times."}, "2776": {"1": "ease", "2": "throe", "3": "open", "4": "crack", "answer": "open", "question": "It was one of the most embarrassing moments of my life and I just wanted the ground to ___up and swallowme."}, "2777": {"1": "as", "2": "same", "3": "more", "4": "like", "answer": "like", "question": "In my opinion no one in their right mind would ever go and pay to see a play ___that."}, "2778": {"1": "required", "2": "desired", "3": "demanded", "4": "included", "answer": "desired", "question": "The room was good, the bed was comfortable and the service was excellent but the hotel food left a lot to be___"}, "2779": {"1": "life", "2": "days", "3": "duration", "4": "stay", "answer": "life", "question": "To be perfectly honest with you I think that this is the best test I've ever taken in my entire ___"}, "2780": {"1": "separate", "2": "divide", "3": "part", "4": "leave", "answer": "part", "question": "Ways of disagreeingI'll have to ___company with you there, I'm afraid."}, "2781": {"1": "incline", "2": "consume", "3": "indicate", "4": "accept", "answer": "accept", "question": "There's no way I can ___that."}, "2782": {"1": "differ", "2": "differentiate", "3": "deny", "4": "decide", "answer": "differ", "question": "We'll have to agree to ___over that."}, "2783": {"1": "deck", "2": "place", "3": "board", "4": "position", "answer": "board", "question": "Don't even think about it! I can't possibly take that on ___"}, "2784": {"1": "perceptive", "2": "perverse", "3": "pernicious", "4": "persuasive", "answer": "persuasive", "question": "No matter how ___you are, I won't change my mind."}, "2785": {"1": "dogs", "2": "cows", "3": "cats", "4": "hens", "answer": "cows", "question": "You can't talk until the ___come home. I won't accept that scheme."}, "2786": {"1": "closed", "2": "locked", "3": "done", "4": "completed", "answer": "closed", "question": "Sorry the subject is now ___"}, "2787": {"1": "power", "2": "court", "3": "hand", "4": "grip", "answer": "hand", "question": "I regret I have no choice but to reject the plan out of ___"}, "2788": {"1": "convicted", "2": "convinced", "3": "conduced", "4": "concerned", "answer": "convinced", "question": "No matter how much you object, I am ___I am right and you're wrong."}, "2789": {"1": "foot", "2": "arm", "3": "hand", "4": "leg", "answer": "leg", "question": "You might as well admit it! You haven't a___to stand on."}, "2790": {"1": "submitting", "2": "renouncing", "3": "leaving", "4": "departing", "answer": "leaving", "question": "Ways of disapprovingThere is no way that I can agree to you ___ early today."}, "2791": {"1": "up", "2": "without", "3": "against", "4": "off", "answer": "against", "question": "I must object and make it clear that I am totally ___ any measures that suggest changes to the originalscheme."}, "2792": {"1": "habit", "2": "custom", "3": "task", "4": "job", "answer": "habit", "question": "He has the ___ of always rejecting any idea that will change the current arrangements."}, "2793": {"1": "routine", "2": "manners", "3": "going", "4": "behaviour", "answer": "behaviour", "question": "I cannot condone that sort of ___ in my establishment and would ask you to remember that in future."}, "2794": {"1": "off", "2": "over", "3": "down", "4": "across", "answer": "down", "question": "I have no choice really but to turn ___ your recent proposal because it is completely unworkable."}, "2795": {"1": "over", "2": "along", "3": "in", "4": "above", "answer": "along", "question": "They can't possibly go ___ with your suggestions because it will involve too much expenditure."}, "2796": {"1": "sense", "2": "balance", "3": "thought", "4": "mind", "answer": "mind", "question": "Quite honestly I'd have to be out of my ___ to sanction what is a crazy proposition."}, "2797": {"1": "obstacle", "2": "burden", "3": "impediment", "4": "problem", "answer": "obstacle", "question": "When her father discovered that his daughter wanted to marry a pop singer, he decided to put every ___ intheir way to prevent the marriage."}, "2798": {"1": "occasion", "2": "chance", "3": "opportunity", "4": "time", "answer": "chance", "question": "He told me there was definitely no ___ that I would pass my examination until I did some work."}, "2799": {"1": "method", "2": "plan", "3": "way", "4": "path", "answer": "way", "question": "You could tell by the ___ he refused to smile that he didn't like the story."}, "2800": {"1": "by", "2": "from", "3": "of", "4": "for", "answer": "for", "question": "Ways of greetingGreat to see you again. I haven't seen you ___ages."}, "2801": {"1": "comfortable", "2": "easy", "3": "relaxing", "4": "comforting", "answer": "comfortable", "question": "Welcome to our house. Come in and make yourself ___"}, "2802": {"1": "after", "2": "since", "3": "then", "4": "before", "answer": "before", "question": "How do you do? I don't think we've met ___"}, "2803": {"1": "discovering", "2": "hiding", "3": "finding", "4": "looking", "answer": "hiding", "question": "Hi Mary. Where have you been ___yourself all this time?"}, "2804": {"1": "stay", "2": "halt", "3": "stop", "4": "sojourn", "answer": "stay", "question": "Good morning, sir. I hope you will have an enjoyable ___in our hotel."}, "2805": {"1": "corner", "2": "angle", "3": "table", "4": "part", "answer": "table", "question": "Good evening to you all. Let me find you a ___near the window."}, "2806": {"1": "declare", "2": "recite", "3": "state", "4": "admit", "answer": "admit", "question": "How are you, David.? I must ___you're looking very well."}, "2807": {"1": "bit", "2": "piece", "3": "little", "4": "section", "answer": "bit", "question": "Hello there. I just don't believe it. You haven't changed a ___since we last met."}, "2808": {"1": "see", "2": "look", "3": "find", "4": "meet", "answer": "meet", "question": "Ah, you must be Mary's husband. Do come in and ___everyone."}, "2809": {"1": "travel", "2": "journey", "3": "trip", "4": "voyage", "answer": "journey", "question": "Here you are at last! I hope your ___here wasn't too horrible."}, "2810": {"1": "find", "2": "lean", "3": "stomach", "4": "point", "answer": "stomach", "question": "Ways of showing angerI've had just as much as I can ___from you."}, "2811": {"1": "consume", "2": "devour", "3": "munch", "4": "bite", "answer": "bite", "question": "You do that again and I'll___ your head off."}, "2812": {"1": "screaming", "2": "crying", "3": "howling", "4": "shouting", "answer": "screaming", "question": "I'm sorry but I can't take any more. I'm afraid I've reached ___point."}, "2813": {"1": "attempt", "2": "dare", "3": "try", "4": "endeavour", "answer": "dare", "question": "You just ___touch that piece of paper and I'll kill you."}, "2814": {"1": "restrain", "2": "render", "3": "repeat", "4": "resign", "answer": "repeat", "question": "How many more times do I have to ___it to you, stupid?"}, "2815": {"1": "chortling", "2": "chuckling", "3": "grinning", "4": "laughing", "answer": "laughing", "question": "I know you find this highly amusing but to me it's no___ matter."}, "2816": {"1": "any", "2": "no", "3": "some", "4": "enough", "answer": "no", "question": "I'm warning you. I can take just that much and ___more."}, "2817": {"1": "out", "2": "off", "3": "with", "4": "over", "answer": "out", "question": "Everybody just get ___of my way and leave me alone."}, "2818": {"1": "conclusive", "2": "final", "3": "ending", "4": "concluded", "answer": "final", "question": "Not another word from either of you. That's ___"}, "2819": {"1": "more", "2": "lesser", "3": "least", "4": "less", "answer": "less", "question": "Right. I'm leaving. You can do whatever you like. I couldn't care ___"}, "2820": {"1": "perfect", "2": "finished", "3": "completed", "4": "ended", "answer": "perfect", "question": "Ways of showing pleasureNow that's what I call absolutely ___"}, "2821": {"1": "tested", "2": "trailed", "3": "required", "4": "tried", "answer": "tried", "question": "You couldn't have made that drink better if you'd ___."}, "2822": {"1": "bloom", "2": "colour", "3": "scent", "4": "smell", "answer": "scent", "question": "What a delightful___ those flowers give off when you touch them."}, "2823": {"1": "fail", "2": "miss", "3": "pass", "4": "fool", "answer": "fail", "question": "Words just ___me when I try to say how happy I am."}, "2824": {"1": "surely", "2": "safely", "3": "clearly", "4": "notably", "answer": "safely", "question": "I can ___say that I don't think I've ever enjoyed myself so much before."}, "2825": {"1": "found", "2": "seen", "3": "acquired", "4": "got", "answer": "got", "question": "There's really nothing like it, is there when you find you've ___all the answers to the test right?"}, "2826": {"1": "any", "2": "all", "3": "some", "4": "no", "answer": "some", "question": "The only problem with your cooking is that the more I eat, the more I want ___more."}, "2827": {"1": "thinking", "2": "dreaming", "3": "sleeping", "4": "dozing", "answer": "dreaming", "question": "I must be ___because it's all too good to be true."}, "2828": {"1": "promise", "2": "assure", "3": "confirm", "4": "affirm", "answer": "promise", "question": "Just let me try one more of your delicious chocolates and then I'll ___not to take any more."}, "2829": {"1": "clarity", "2": "certainty", "3": "bliss", "4": "fortune", "answer": "bliss", "question": "It's absolute ___here. I think I'll stay at this hotel one more week."}, "2830": {"1": "detail", "2": "delineate", "3": "underline", "4": "express", "answer": "express", "question": "Ways of thankingWords can't possibly___ how grateful I am for what you have done."}, "2831": {"1": "accept", "2": "agree", "3": "appreciate", "4": "deserve", "answer": "appreciate", "question": "Thank you so much for helping me. I really ___it."}, "2832": {"1": "forego", "2": "forget", "3": "foretell", "4": "forbid", "answer": "forget", "question": "A thousand thanks for all your hard work. I shall never ___it."}, "2833": {"1": "sum", "2": "packet", "3": "box", "4": "bundle", "answer": "sum", "question": "They showed their great gratitude by sending us a large___ of money."}, "2834": {"1": "base", "2": "foundation", "3": "end", "4": "bottom", "answer": "bottom", "question": "Thank you for all you've done from the ___of my heart."}, "2835": {"1": "piece", "2": "token", "3": "counter", "4": "emblem", "answer": "token", "question": "I'm sending this bunch of flowers as a small___of my thanks and appreciation."}, "2836": {"1": "entirely", "2": "probably", "3": "possibly", "4": "exactly", "answer": "possibly", "question": "How can I ___thank you enough for all you've done?"}, "2837": {"1": "at", "2": "of", "3": "by", "4": "in", "answer": "in", "question": "On the watch they gave him were the words: ___gratitude for 40 years loyal service."}, "2838": {"1": "show", "2": "initiate", "3": "enclose", "4": "refer", "answer": "enclose", "question": "It's very difficult for children to ___their gratitude for what their parents have done for them."}, "2839": {"1": "type", "2": "sort", "3": "sign", "4": "species", "answer": "sort", "question": "Look upon this as a ___of thank you present for all your endeavours on our behalf."}, "2840": {"1": "spoken", "2": "said", "3": "told", "4": "mentioned", "answer": "told", "question": "Ways of threateningIf I've ___you once, I've done it a hundred times. Don't do it!"}, "2841": {"1": "go", "2": "occasion", "3": "time", "4": "chance", "answer": "chance", "question": "I'll give you just one more___ and after that, you'll be in real trouble."}, "2842": {"1": "bright", "2": "clear", "3": "simple", "4": "obvious", "answer": "clear", "question": "I'm telling you loud and ___that you really must get it right this time."}, "2843": {"1": "approve", "2": "disprove", "3": "disapprove", "4": "improve", "answer": "improve", "question": "She told him that if his manners didn't ___, he would be sent home."}, "2844": {"1": "nose", "2": "eye", "3": "head", "4": "foot", "answer": "head", "question": "He agreed because he said it was like having a gun held to his ___"}, "2845": {"1": "own", "2": "self", "3": "side", "4": "back", "answer": "own", "question": "I'll lend you money for the very last time because after that you're on your___"}, "2846": {"1": "attend", "2": "wait", "3": "expect", "4": "delay", "answer": "wait", "question": "I can't tell you how lucky you've been this time but just ___till next time."}, "2847": {"1": "oversee", "2": "overtake", "3": "overhear", "4": "overlook", "answer": "overlook", "question": "I'm prepared to ___your mistake on this occasion but I can't ever do it again."}, "2848": {"1": "need", "2": "require", "3": "demand", "4": "order", "answer": "need", "question": "If you leave me now, you don't ___to come back."}, "2849": {"1": "eye", "2": "nose", "3": "ear", "4": "head", "answer": "ear", "question": "Let me put it simply one more incident like that and you're out on your ___!"}, "2850": {"1": "find", "2": "seek", "3": "achieve", "4": "manage", "answer": "achieve", "question": "Working WellThe boss was appointed in the hope that she would be able to ___results."}, "2851": {"1": "productive", "2": "producing", "3": "produced", "4": "production", "answer": "productive", "question": "In the very beginning she had a meeting with all the staff, which turned out to be extremely ___"}, "2852": {"1": "trusting", "2": "believing", "3": "attached", "4": "loyal", "answer": "loyal", "question": "Although many people wanted to remain ___to her predecessor, they soon started to respect her style ofmanagment."}, "2853": {"1": "project", "2": "promote", "3": "proffer", "4": "protect", "answer": "promote", "question": "At the first series of interviews the question was whether to appoint a newcomer or___ a current employee."}, "2854": {"1": "marvel", "2": "mandate", "3": "merit", "4": "mastery", "answer": "merit", "question": "The decision was finally taken that appointments should be based purely and simply on ___"}, "2855": {"1": "valued", "2": "valuable", "3": "valuing", "4": "valid", "answer": "valued", "question": "There was a new spirit in the company and for the first time in ages staff at last felt they were being ___"}, "2856": {"1": "respect", "2": "referral", "3": "recognized", "4": "recognition", "answer": "recognition", "question": "Employees were beginning to receive___for the hard work that they had been doing."}, "2857": {"1": "donate", "2": "deliver", "3": "contribute", "4": "convert", "answer": "contribute", "question": "It soon became apparent that under the new management people were also starting to ___some of their freetime to the company."}, "2858": {"1": "on", "2": "about", "3": "through", "4": "forward", "answer": "forward", "question": "Some of the longest serving staff actually looked ___to coming into work."}, "2859": {"1": "obvious", "2": "granted", "3": "taken", "4": "thought", "answer": "obvious", "question": "At the end of her first year it was ___to everyone that as the new boss she had been totally accepted."}, "2860": {"1": "flood", "2": "fluid", "3": "flush", "4": "full", "answer": "flush", "question": "A good real estate rental marketRay Alcorn of Park Real Estate Inc remarks that real estate is a capital-intensive industry, and its health risesand falls with capital availability; currently the capital markets are so ___ with cash, they can't find a place forit all."}, "2861": {"1": "ameliorated", "2": "mollified", "3": "tempered", "4": "transformed", "answer": "tempered", "question": "Boom times typically engender oversupply of product, but construction prices have skyrocketed due to naturaldisasters and rising commodity prices, which has ___ new building in all property types."}, "2862": {"1": "dealing", "2": "ending", "3": "landing", "4": "spending", "answer": "landing", "question": "Rising consumer interest rates will further slow consumer purchasing and the housing market, and mayproduce the desired soft ___"}, "2863": {"1": "groundings", "2": "grumblings", "3": "ramblings", "4": "rumblings", "answer": "rumblings", "question": "Historically, contractions in capital have a negative effect on valuations, and current ___ from governmentregulators aiming to trim commercial banks' real estate loan exposure are worrisome."}, "2864": {"1": "cache", "2": "niche", "3": "surfeit", "4": "surplus", "answer": "surfeit", "question": "Global markets are literally awash in capital, all of it seeking yield and stability; fortunately, commercial realestate offers both, and even if banks are constrained there is a ___ of capital to fill the void."}, "2865": {"1": "budget", "2": "gauntlet", "3": "roof", "4": "stock", "answer": "roof", "question": "Construction costs have gone through the ___ in the past year due to natural disasters and increasedcommodity prices."}, "2866": {"1": "brush off", "2": "cat's meow", "3": "door prize", "4": "last laugh", "answer": "last laugh", "question": "High construction costs and condo conversions have reduced new supply and a slowing housing marketincreases rental demand, so owners can now flex their muscles with rent increases, and those who bought athigh valuations may yet get the ___"}, "2867": {"1": "off chance", "2": "offer", "3": "offering", "4": "offing", "answer": "offing", "question": "Areas with declining employment and population will experience an acceleration of those trends, and investorswill not acquire properties in such markets without good reason to believe a comeback is in the ___"}, "2868": {"1": "keep up with", "2": "ride out", "3": "sail into", "4": "wriggle out of", "answer": "ride out", "question": "Retail properties will suffer as owners rediscover risk as a component of value, but most of these assets areowned by well-capitalized private equity groups that can easily ___ the storm."}, "2869": {"1": "receipt", "2": "recipe", "3": "recipient", "4": "reward", "answer": "recipe", "question": "Acquisition of stabilized properties at low cap rates with little potential for rent growth is a sure ___ for belowmarket returns."}, "2870": {"1": "anthropologists", "2": "archaeologists", "3": "paleontologists", "4": "prehistorians", "answer": "archaeologists", "question": "A Quick History of AdvertisingEncarta's History of Advertising notes that ___ have found evidence of advertising dating back to the sBC, among the Babylonians."}, "2871": {"1": "eye-arresting", "2": "eye-catching", "3": "eye-stopping", "4": "eye-taking", "answer": "eye-catching", "question": "One of the first known methods of advertising was the outdoor display, usually an ___ sign painted on thewall of a building."}, "2872": {"1": "excavated", "2": "exhumed", "3": "extracted", "4": "extricated", "answer": "excavated", "question": "An outdoor advertisement ___ in Rome offers property for rent, and one found painted on a wall in Pompeiicalls the attention of travelers to a tavern."}, "2873": {"1": "announcers", "2": "criers", "3": "heralds", "4": "plaintiffs", "answer": "criers", "question": "In medieval times word-of-mouth praise of products gave rise to a simple but effective form of advertising, theuse of so-called town ___"}, "2874": {"1": "places", "2": "portions", "3": "praises", "4": "prices", "answer": "praises", "question": "These were citizens who read public notices aloud and were also employed by merchants to shout the ___ oftheir wares."}, "2875": {"1": "coverage", "2": "headway", "3": "impression", "4": "profit", "answer": "headway", "question": "Although graphic forms of advertising appeared early in history, printed advertising made little ___ until theinvention of the movable-type printing press by German printer Johannes Gutenberg about ."}, "2876": {"1": "opened", "2": "set", "3": "started", "4": "took", "answer": "set", "question": "In the United States, the advertising profession began in Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, in , when Volney B.Palmer ___ up shop as an advertising agent, the forerunner of the advertising agency."}, "2877": {"1": "lack", "2": "without", "3": "do not", "4": "no", "answer": "lack", "question": "Rocky shores that ___ beaches are eventually destroyed by the sea."}, "2878": {"1": "twice a", "2": "two and a", "3": "two and", "4": "twice and", "answer": "two and a", "question": "A person's blood flows through a pipeline of vessels that, end to end, would stretch more than ___ half times around the Earth at the equator."}, "2879": {"1": "which cellulose fibers", "2": "cellulose fibers", "3": "fibers are cellulose", "4": "which fibers are cellulose", "answer": "cellulose fibers", "question": "All paper is formed into sheets from ___"}, "2880": {"1": "as it", "2": "when", "3": "that", "4": "it", "answer": "when", "question": "A silkworm has glands that secrete a liquid that hardens into silk ___ comes into contact with air."}, "2881": {"1": "because", "2": "so", "3": "and since", "4": "except", "answer": "so", "question": "Recently doctors warned that too much animal fat in the diet can lead to heart disease, ___ special types of margarine made with vegetable oils are becoming popular."}, "2882": {"1": "when mixed", "2": "when is mixed", "3": "it mixed", "4": "mixed is", "answer": "when mixed", "question": "A reagent is any chemical that reacts in a predictable way ___ with other chemicals."}, "2883": {"1": "what has saved", "2": "which saved", "3": "which has saved", "4": "who saves", "answer": "which has saved", "question": "Penicillin is perhaps the drug ___ more lives than any other in the history of medicine."}, "2884": {"1": "the heatless light given off by certain plants and animals.", "2": "certain plants and animals give off the heatless light", "3": "which certain plants and animals give off the heatless light", "4": "is the heatless light given off by certain plants and animals", "answer": "the heatless light given off by certain plants and animals.", "question": "Biochemists use fireflies to study bioluminescence, ___."}, "2885": {"1": "introduces its principal theme", "2": "its principal theme introduced", "3": "being introduced its principal theme", "4": "its principal theme introducing", "answer": "introduces its principal theme", "question": "The opening section of a sonata is the longest and ___."}, "2886": {"1": "being originated", "2": "have originated", "3": "originates", "4": "originating", "answer": "originates", "question": "Igneous rock ___ from the cooling and solidification of molten matter from the Earth's interior."}, "2887": {"1": "which", "2": "that which", "3": "of which", "4": "of what", "answer": "of what", "question": "Although the audience was well informed, no one knew ___ he spoke."}, "2888": {"1": "web-like", "2": "like a web", "3": "webbed like", "4": "the webs like", "answer": "webbed like", "question": "With its antlers ___ the feet of a duck, the North American moose is easy to identify."}, "2889": {"1": "The", "2": "One of the", "3": "As the", "4": "Of the", "answer": "The", "question": "___ most brilliant Greek inventor was Archmedes , who lived about  years ago."}, "2890": {"1": "twenty- four years", "2": "at the age of twenty-four", "3": "age twenty-four", "4": "of twenty-four years", "answer": "at the age of twenty-four", "question": "In , ___ , Alice Freeman Parmer became head of the history department at wellesley."}, "2891": {"1": "It was", "2": "There was", "3": "It", "4": "There were", "answer": "There was", "question": "___ not a single hard-surfaced road during the entire colonial period aside from city streets."}, "2892": {"1": "It was", "2": "There was", "3": "There", "4": "It", "answer": "It was", "question": "___ in  that the declaration of independence was signed."}, "2893": {"1": "There were", "2": "It was", "3": "Were", "4": "Were there", "answer": "There were", "question": "In the eighteen century, ___ not many women who had access to formal education in the colonies."}, "2894": {"1": "they were", "2": "it", "3": "it was", "4": "there was", "answer": "it was", "question": "After the Revolution, although some advances were made in education ___ a slow process."}, "2895": {"1": "Mountaineering it as we know", "2": "Mountaineering as we know", "3": "We know mountaineering is", "4": "We know there is mountaineering", "answer": "Mountaineering as we know", "question": "___ today was developed by the Swiss scientist Horace de Sassure around ."}, "2896": {"1": "was commemorated", "2": "commemorated", "3": "commemorates", "4": "commemorating", "answer": "commemorated", "question": "The marathon, first staged in , ___ the legendary feat of a Greek soldier who carried news of victory from the battlefield at Marathon to Athens."}, "2897": {"1": "burning", "2": "is burned", "3": "burned", "4": "burns", "answer": "burns", "question": "The Olympic torch ___ throughout the Games and is then extinguished at the closing ceremony."}, "2898": {"1": "sense", "2": "sense are", "3": "sensing", "4": "senses", "answer": "sense", "question": "Some fish ___ distortions of electrical field through special receptors."}, "2899": {"1": "had", "2": "are", "3": "do", "4": "that", "answer": "do", "question": "Only rarely ___ neuroses leave a person unable to function in everyday situations."}, "2900": {"1": "yet", "2": "which", "3": "there", "4": "despite", "answer": "yet", "question": "Great salt is fed by fresh-water stems, ___ is about four to five times as salty as the ocean."}, "2901": {"1": "had", "2": "has", "3": "would have", "4": "has not", "answer": "has", "question": "I would wear my red dress save it ___ a stain in the front."}, "2902": {"1": "have", "2": "had", "3": "have had", "4": "would have", "answer": "had", "question": "M : \" Would you like to visit Los Angeles on your vacation? \" W : \" If I ___ a week off. \""}, "2903": {"1": "have thought", "2": "were thinking", "3": "have been thinking", "4": "were thought", "answer": "were thought", "question": "Gold was originally valued for the magical powers that ___ to come from it."}, "2904": {"1": "where apricots can", "2": "apricot can", "3": "where can apricots can", "4": "which apricots can", "answer": "where apricots can", "question": "There are very few areas in the world ___ be brown successfully."}, "2905": {"1": "require", "2": "requires", "3": "requiring", "4": "to require", "answer": "require", "question": "A majority off people in the United States can get all the calcium their bodies ___ from the food they eat."}, "2906": {"1": "the least studied", "2": "studied the least", "3": "study less and less", "4": "to study the less", "answer": "the least studied", "question": "Of all the economically important plants, palms, have been ___ ."}, "2907": {"1": "That", "2": "Why", "3": "About", "4": "What", "answer": "About", "question": "___ two thirds of the grants made by the Ford Foundation have been for the support of education."}, "2908": {"1": "to be conveniently measured", "2": "which conveniently measured", "3": "to measure conveniently", "4": "conveniently measured", "answer": "to be conveniently measured", "question": "Except for the sun, all stars are too far from the Earth for their distances ___ in miles or kilometers."}, "2909": {"1": "to be full general", "2": "he made full general", "3": "made full general", "4": "was being made full general", "answer": "made full general", "question": "John Joseph pershing ___ in , the highest rank held by any American citizen since George Washington."}, "2910": {"1": "my watch was missing", "2": "I found my watch disappeared", "3": "I found my watch missing", "4": "the watch was missed", "answer": "I found my watch missing", "question": "Returning to my room, ___."}, "2911": {"1": "the light is not on", "2": "and not on light", "3": "but is not on the light", "4": "is not on light", "answer": "but is not on the light", "question": "The photo periodic response of algae actually depends on the duration of darkness, ___.."}, "2912": {"1": "require", "2": "requires", "3": "requiring", "4": "to require", "answer": "require", "question": "A majority of people in the United States can get all the calcium their bodies ___ from the food they eat."}, "2913": {"1": "Despite", "2": "To be", "3": "While", "4": "However", "answer": "While", "question": "___ usually thought to end in Northern New Mexico, the Rocky Mountains really extend southward to the frontier of Mexico."}, "2914": {"1": "however we fight off it many times", "2": "no matter how many times we fight it off", "3": "no matter what many times", "4": "we fight it off how many times", "answer": "no matter how many times we fight it off", "question": "The influenza virus infects us again and again, ___ ."}, "2915": {"1": "Oddly heard it may sound", "2": "Maybe it was as odd as", "3": "Odd as it may sound", "4": "It may sound as odd", "answer": "Odd as it may sound", "question": "___, Cameron had thought of both \"The Abyss\" and \"True Lies\" as love stories, but he know he'd failed to convey that."}, "2916": {"1": "have won him a considerable critical acclaim", "2": "have won considerate critical acclaim", "3": "has won considerably critical acclaim to him", "4": "has won him considerable critical acclaim", "answer": "has won him considerable critical acclaim", "question": "His cynical and often savage vision of life and love ___."}, "2917": {"1": "operates", "2": "was operating", "3": "operated", "4": "operating", "answer": "operating", "question": "During the flood of , the Red Cross, ___ out of emergency headquarters in Mississippi, set up temporary for the homeless."}, "2918": {"1": "that she drew", "2": "by drawing her", "3": "from which she drew", "4": "dream from which", "answer": "from which she drew", "question": "Emily Dickinson's garden was a place ___ great inspiration of her poems."}, "2919": {"1": "of an international reputation", "2": "international reputation", "3": "reputation of internation", "4": "an international reputation", "answer": "an international reputation", "question": "By the ', Mahalia Jackson's powerful, joyous gospel music style had gained her ___."}, "2920": {"1": "independent to be the first plants", "2": "the first independent plants to be", "3": "the first plants to be independent", "4": "to be the first independent plants", "answer": "the first plants to be independent", "question": "The gymnosperms were ___ of water for reproductive purposes."}, "2921": {"1": "too", "2": "so", "3": "than", "4": "enough", "answer": "too", "question": "simple pressure gauges such as liquid-level manometers are ___ insensitive for use in vacuum works."}, "2922": {"1": "are several recently settled lnuit communities are there", "2": "several recently settled lnuit communities are there", "3": "near several recently settled lnuit communities", "4": "is where several recently settled lnuit communities", "answer": "are several recently settled lnuit communities are there", "question": "Nestled along the shoreline of Hudso Bay ___"}, "2923": {"1": "that book", "2": "yours", "3": "that one", "4": "that", "answer": "that", "question": "\"What is the difference?\" \"This furniture is different from ___\""}, "2924": {"1": "that of the United States", "2": "which the United States", "3": "those of the United States", "4": "the United States", "answer": "that of the United States", "question": "Unlike the budgets of some countries, ___ focuses chiefly on expenditure."}, "2925": {"1": "to link", "2": "linked", "3": "links", "4": "to be linked", "answer": "to link", "question": "The Canadian National Railway was built ___"}, "2926": {"1": "their social equalities", "2": "them social equality", "3": "social equalities of theirs", "4": "that they have social equalities", "answer": "them social equality", "question": "The government exploited their labor while denying ___"}, "2927": {"1": "a developmental disorder, so does an autism", "2": "so did an autism, a developmental disorder", "3": "than does autism, a developmental disorder", "4": "so does autism, a developmental disorder", "answer": "so does autism, a developmental disorder", "question": "Just as mental illness have less severe \"shadow\" versions, ___"}, "2928": {"1": "to be run", "2": "run", "3": "it may be run", "4": "is run", "answer": "is run", "question": "The Kentucky Derby ___ every may at Churchill Downs in Louisville, Kentucky."}, "2929": {"1": "in length", "2": "it is long", "3": "its length", "4": "length", "answer": "in length", "question": "The javelin used in competition must be between  and  centimeters ___"}, "2930": {"1": "any do", "2": "than do any", "3": "than any do", "4": "do than", "answer": "than any do", "question": "Scientists stress that the overall warming trend of the last decade holds much more significance ___ single year's temperatures."}, "2931": {"1": "the simultaneous bursts", "2": "simultaneously burst", "3": "there are simultaneous bursts of", "4": "simultaneously bursting", "answer": "simultaneously bursting", "question": "When ___ impulses from many of the neurons in one part of the brain, an epileptic seizure occurs."}, "2932": {"1": "there are two on", "2": "it has two on", "3": "two are on", "4": "two on", "answer": "it has two on", "question": "The human body has four jugular veins, ___ each side of the neck."}, "2933": {"1": "the counteraction", "2": "to counteract", "3": "counteract", "4": "counteracting", "answer": "counteracting", "question": "Aspiria is used ___ a construction of the bleed vessels."}, "2934": {"1": "the ways are useful", "2": "useful ways", "3": "the most useful ways", "4": "most are useful ways", "answer": "the ways are useful", "question": "Drying of meats and vegetables is no longer considered one of ___ of preserving food."}, "2935": {"1": "looks rather like", "2": "looks like rather", "3": "likes looking rather", "4": "rather likes looking", "answer": "looks rather like", "question": "The sea mammal meduoa is popularly called a jellyfish because it ___ jelly."}, "2936": {"1": "helpful", "2": "for help", "3": "helpfully", "4": "with the help", "answer": "helpfully", "question": "Therapists are currently using mental imagery in the hope that it might prove ___ in the treatment of cancer."}, "2937": {"1": "from", "2": "between", "3": "into", "4": "among", "answer": "between", "question": "The employee lounge on the second floor is closed tor daily cleaning ___ 3:00 and 4:00 p.m."}, "2938": {"1": "journal", "2": "journalist", "3": "journalism", "4": "journalistic", "answer": "journalist", "question": "Julia Angwin is an award-winning ___ at The Wall Street Journal, where she writes about the convergence of technology and media."}, "2939": {"1": "except", "2": "until", "3": "soon", "4": "earlier", "answer": "until", "question": "You may continue to receive this error message ___ all the computers on your network have been repaired."}, "2940": {"1": "carefully", "2": "harmlessly", "3": "extremely", "4": "hardly", "answer": "carefully", "question": "Please, read the instruction manual ___ when using the washing machine tor the first time."}, "2941": {"1": "such", "2": "it", "3": "but", "4": "and", "answer": "and", "question": "It is almost impossible both to find ___ to buy the first edition of the Benny comic book."}, "2942": {"1": "dividends", "2": "components", "3": "representatives", "4": "institutions", "answer": "components", "question": "Wolf Robotics can replace worn-out ___ to keep your existing equipment functioning at its peak performance."}, "2943": {"1": "highest", "2": "high", "3": "higher", "4": "highly", "answer": "highest", "question": "Weyburn Inland Terminal, the farmerowned and managed grain company, recently paid out its ___ ever dividends to the shareholders."}, "2944": {"1": "sent", "2": "send", "3": "sends", "4": "sending", "answer": "send", "question": "WOCO will ___ employees to Ireland to help design the plant and assist in establishing the production line."}, "2945": {"1": "either", "2": "or", "3": "then", "4": "but", "answer": "but", "question": "Breakfasts and evening dinners are included in your tour package, ___ lunches are not."}, "2946": {"1": "theirs", "2": "themselves", "3": "them", "4": "their own", "answer": "themselves", "question": "It is too heavy for Mr. Lim and Ms. Hwang to move the new office furniture by ___ ."}, "2947": {"1": "probable", "2": "eligible", "3": "considerable", "4": "available", "answer": "available", "question": "Our technical support will be ___ online throughout the day to aid our customers in using the T-Learning software."}, "2948": {"1": "receives", "2": "has received", "3": "is receiving", "4": "would receive", "answer": "has received", "question": "Sky News has introduced many innovations in the broadcasting sector, for which it ___ multiple awards over the past fifteen years."}, "2949": {"1": "classify", "2": "modify", "3": "substitute", "4": "support", "answer": "substitute", "question": "For your health, if available, ___ olive oil for butter when baking, as up to 25% less fat is used when baking with olive oil."}, "2950": {"1": "expressing", "2": "expresses", "3": "expressly", "4": "expressive", "answer": "expressly", "question": "All papers for this course must be written ___ for this course; students are not permitted to turn in work completed for any other class."}, "2951": {"1": "next", "2": "nearby", "3": "closest", "4": "brief", "answer": "nearby", "question": "Even though most conference attendees reserved the rooms in the hotel where the conference is held, some others planned to stay at a ___ hotel instead."}, "2952": {"1": "invest", "2": "investors", "3": "investments", "4": "investing", "answer": "investors", "question": "Nintendo Limited has announced to ___ that it has completed the full acquisition of Retro Studios Inc. for the sum of one million dollars."}, "2953": {"1": "too", "2": "much", "3": "highly", "4": "mostly", "answer": "too", "question": "If you usually have ___ many appointments, many web-based calendars can remind you when a scheduled event is about to happen."}, "2954": {"1": "renovate", "2": "renovated", "3": "renovating", "4": "renovation", "answer": "renovated", "question": "The annual NCA Conference will be held at the newly ___ Hilton Wilmington Hotel located in the heart of Wilmington."}, "2955": {"1": "implementing", "2": "constructing", "3": "instructing", "4": "supplementing", "answer": "implementing", "question": "By ___ the methods outlined below you will increase your sales while lowering your overall marketing costs."}, "2956": {"1": "equal", "2": "equally", "3": "equality", "4": "equaled", "answer": "equally", "question": "Since , the funds have been distributed ___ between MJF and the Hen County Bar Foundation."}, "2957": {"1": "excursion", "2": "itinerary", "3": "reservation", "4": "proposal", "answer": "excursion", "question": "If you are interested in tomorrow's ___ to Knott's Berry Farm, sign up at the reception desk by 1 o'clock this afternoon."}, "2958": {"1": "discount", "2": "discounts", "3": "discounter", "4": "discounting", "answer": "discounts", "question": "Malaysia Airlines is offering ___ of up to 60% on online bookings for one million domestic tickets from next month until July 31 next year."}, "2959": {"1": "that", "2": "unless", "3": "even", "4": "after", "answer": "that", "question": "Most of the applicants for the marketing director position were so highly qualified ___ it has been hard to choose from them."}, "2960": {"1": "request", "2": "question", "3": "knowledge", "4": "curiosity", "answer": "request", "question": "The colour, material and design of our jewelry products can be changed or tailor-made for clients upon ___ ."}, "2961": {"1": "innovate", "2": "innovative", "3": "innovates", "4": "innovatively", "answer": "innovative", "question": "Mr. Colin Johnston is a principal research scientist working on ___ techniques for the remediation of contaminated groundwater environments."}, "2962": {"1": "wraps", "2": "covers", "3": "guards", "4": "spreads", "answer": "covers", "question": "The cost of the convention ___ all the materials provided and accommodations at the Palace Hotel."}, "2963": {"1": "techniques", "2": "developments", "3": "consequences", "4": "appointments", "answer": "appointments", "question": "We are unable to arrange ___ by email, so this can only be done via the telephone."}, "2964": {"1": "who", "2": "whose", "3": "they", "4": "what", "answer": "who", "question": "Nearly half of the customers ___ responded to the survey said that Austraclear delivered services that were above their expectations."}, "2965": {"1": "confirms", "2": "confirmed", "3": "confirming", "4": "confirmation", "answer": "confirmation", "question": "An order will be deemed accepted by SonicSpider when written ___ of the order is sent to the customer."}, "2966": {"1": "pretend", "2": "repair", "3": "remind", "4": "increase", "answer": "increase", "question": "University of Calgary recently had to ___ fees for the first time in seven years because of deep state budget cuts, but financial aid has mitigated the impact of the increase for many students."}, "2967": {"1": "to", "2": "up", "3": "of", "4": "out", "answer": "to", "question": "The TVA upgrades are part of the extension of a 69,volt transmission line to provide additional electric power ___ all the cities in Alberta."}, "2968": {"1": "on the contrary", "2": "consequently", "3": "in spite of", "4": "even though", "answer": "in spite of", "question": "The Sun Group achieved net earnings of $20 million tor the year ___ high startup costs tor the new plant in Belgium."}, "2969": {"1": "locates", "2": "located", "3": "locating", "4": "was locating", "answer": "located", "question": "The loading dock entrance is accessible from the South Town Exposition Center's parking lot and is ___ on the east side of the building."}, "2970": {"1": "affordable", "2": "potential", "3": "directed", "4": "approximate", "answer": "affordable", "question": "Due to an increase in rents in Dubai, many people facing problems of high cost of living are moving to Ajman where rents are comparatively ___ ."}, "2971": {"1": "mark", "2": "proposal", "3": "potential", "4": "indication", "answer": "potential", "question": "Medical imaging technology has enormous ___ to contribute to the improvement of health care throughout the world."}, "2972": {"1": "others", "2": "another", "3": "any other", "4": "one another", "answer": "any other", "question": "In case of bad weather conditions or ___ unexpected circumstances, the concert hall will post cancellations on the website."}, "2973": {"1": "train", "2": "trains", "3": "trained", "4": "training", "answer": "training", "question": "Whether you're interested in the MCSE, CIW, or the CCNA, LaSalle Computer Learning Center otters the computer ___ that can help you reach your career goals."}, "2974": {"1": "elects", "2": "remains", "3": "receives", "4": "appears", "answer": "remains", "question": "According to Top Tour Magazine's survey, Jasper ___ the top vacation destination tor Canadian families with nearly 50 million visitors each year."}, "2975": {"1": "It so", "2": "Rather than", "3": "Owing to", "4": "Given that", "answer": "Given that", "question": "___ the city council has approved the urban renewal project, we need to recruit several new workers."}, "2976": {"1": "recently", "2": "approximately", "3": "exactly", "4": "comparatively", "answer": "recently", "question": "For ___ hired engineers, the training course provides a chance to get a better understanding of their work as well as meet experienced engineers."}, "2977": {"1": "having reduced", "2": "reduce", "3": "reduced", "4": "reducing", "answer": "reduced", "question": "The new technology ___ the consumption of natural resources by a tremendous amount."}, "2978": {"1": "she", "2": "her", "3": "hers", "4": "herself", "answer": "her", "question": "Inspired by ___ father's presidential nomination acceptance speech when she was a child, Irene decided to become a politician."}, "2979": {"1": "between", "2": "among", "3": "near", "4": "onto", "answer": "near", "question": "OBI store will be the first local store to move in ___ the much larger Target Shopping Center."}, "2980": {"1": "orders", "2": "permits", "3": "shifts", "4": "entries", "answer": "shifts", "question": "It is difficult to find a worker who can work evening and weekend ___ ."}, "2981": {"1": "led to", "2": "developed", "3": "practiced", "4": "reserved", "answer": "developed", "question": "James Martin ___ his theory based on his thorough 15-year research."}, "2982": {"1": "describe", "2": "descriptions", "3": "descriptive", "4": "describable", "answer": "descriptions", "question": "Although the ___ sounded very complicated, the engineer had no problem using the equipment for the first time."}, "2983": {"1": "efficiently", "2": "dramatically", "3": "openly", "4": "hastily", "answer": "dramatically", "question": "The company was able to recover ___ from the past three months' losses because its new product dominated the market."}, "2984": {"1": "concerned", "2": "repaired", "3": "established", "4": "determined", "answer": "repaired", "question": "If your vehicle has to be ___ , please call our service department and we will provide the service you need immediately."}, "2985": {"1": "already", "2": "a great deal", "3": "soon", "4": "by far", "answer": "already", "question": "Because its rival company has ___ developed its new technology successfully, it's nearly impossible for Geller Inc. to gain a larger market share."}, "2986": {"1": "as", "2": "so", "3": "if", "4": "or", "answer": "or", "question": "Because the board members all agreed to fire the CEO, Mr. Chen had to either resign himself ___ wait until he gets fired."}, "2987": {"1": "managing", "2": "manage", "3": "manageable", "4": "manageability", "answer": "manageable", "question": "The insurance losses were deemed ___ because the company had done so well otherwise throughout the rest of the year."}, "2988": {"1": "they", "2": "their", "3": "theirs", "4": "them", "answer": "them", "question": "Since the company had so many unsold products from last year, they had to sell ___ at a hugely discounted rate."}, "2989": {"1": "demand", "2": "payment", "3": "convenience", "4": "design", "answer": "demand", "question": "In a free market economy, the price of goods is determined by supply and ___ , which can sometimes get out of control and become the cause of an economic recession."}, "2990": {"1": "short", "2": "poor", "3": "virtual", "4": "steady", "answer": "steady", "question": "The ___ pace of sales didn't last for a long time because the stock market suddenly crashed."}, "2991": {"1": "assuming", "2": "to assume", "3": "assume", "4": "would assume", "answer": "would assume", "question": "I figured that Jaina, my boss, ___ that I was the one who messed up the project because Jim blames all his mistakes on me."}, "2992": {"1": "across", "2": "opposite", "3": "throughout", "4": "upon", "answer": "across", "question": "It was a huge mistake for Carter to open a DVD store right ___ from the city's largest movie theater."}, "2993": {"1": "was enclosing", "2": "will be enclosed", "3": "enclosed", "4": "will enclose", "answer": "will enclose", "question": "The envelope that we are going to send you ___ all the necessary documents that you'll need to fill out."}, "2994": {"1": "larger", "2": "large", "3": "largely", "4": "largeness", "answer": "largely", "question": "The Korean economy has been ___ affected by the number of exported goods because Korea is an export-driven country."}, "2995": {"1": "mediated", "2": "deliberated", "3": "regarded", "4": "supposed", "answer": "deliberated", "question": "The analyst ___ on the feasibility of the new government funding policy with passion."}, "2996": {"1": "restrict", "2": "restrictedly", "3": "restricted", "4": "restriction", "answer": "restricted", "question": "The ___ area is protected by high fences and military personnel 24 hours a day."}, "2997": {"1": "produces", "2": "producers", "3": "products", "4": "productive", "answer": "producers", "question": "The two largest manufacturing corporations in this country have now become the largest ___ in their industry worldwide."}, "2998": {"1": "customarily", "2": "externally", "3": "observantly", "4": "formally", "answer": "formally", "question": "When Paul ___ announced that the company is going to become a corporation, the entire family got mad at him for making such an important decision alone."}, "2999": {"1": "Although", "2": "Despite", "3": "When", "4": "For", "answer": "Although", "question": "___ our company has tried hard to recover from last month's loss, we were not able to reach the same number of sales as last month's."}, "3000": {"1": "other", "2": "the other", "3": "another's", "4": "the one", "answer": "the other", "question": "When the two software companies gave a presentation, the partner company had to choose one or ___ ."}, "3001": {"1": "considerable", "2": "considering", "3": "considerably", "4": "consider", "answer": "considerably", "question": "Although the company made a ___ large profit, it was still not enough to even pay off their debts."}, "3002": {"1": "around", "2": "forward", "3": "altogether", "4": "never", "answer": "forward", "question": "Howard was looking ___ to working with his new colleague, who has been considered a hard worker at the company."}, "3003": {"1": "suspicious", "2": "uncertain", "3": "reluctant", "4": "worrisome", "answer": "reluctant", "question": "David was ___ to express his real feelings about the company because he didn't want to say anything negative about his superiors."}, "3004": {"1": "exclusion", "2": "proximity", "3": "efficiency", "4": "availability", "answer": "proximity", "question": "Because of its ___ to both the capital city and the coast, lncheon was selected as the location for the international airport."}, "3005": {"1": "cooperating", "2": "conducting", "3": "negotiating", "4": "remarking", "answer": "negotiating", "question": "It is crucial for contractors to have good ___ skills because they represent their clients' business."}, "3006": {"1": "aside", "2": "even", "3": "additionally", "4": "except", "answer": "except", "question": "Matt managed to understand the presentation ___ for the part about how nanotechnology will affect the company in the long run. II [!) ."}, "3007": {"1": "attendance", "2": "abundance", "3": "persistence", "4": "frequency", "answer": "persistence", "question": "The position of general manager requires ___ when faced with difficulties because they are considered leaders of the company."}, "3008": {"1": "secure", "2": "secureness", "3": "secures", "4": "securing", "answer": "secure", "question": "There is a high demand for programmers who can come up with software that can ___ more customers."}, "3009": {"1": "adequately", "2": "objectionably", "3": "approximately", "4": "mutually", "answer": "adequately", "question": "Because the president didn't address the United States' position ___ , some Middle Eastern countries criticized the U.S for its unclear statement."}, "3010": {"1": "to increase", "2": "increase", "3": "increased", "4": "increasingly", "answer": "increase", "question": "The CEO didn't expect that his actions would result in an ___ in the company's stock value."}, "3011": {"1": "adversary", "2": "adverse", "3": "adversely", "4": "adversity", "answer": "adversely", "question": "Ken always acted ___ towards anything I did because both of us were trying to get promoted to the position of manager."}, "3012": {"1": "substantial", "2": "contented", "3": "generating", "4": "acquired", "answer": "substantial", "question": "By donating ___ amounts of money to several orphanages, the chairman of BIH Inc. was able to give a positive impression of the company to the public."}, "3013": {"1": "During", "2": "In spite of", "3": "Even though", "4": "As if", "answer": "Even though", "question": "___ the company paid extra wages for workers' overtime, the employees were still not content with the company's treatment."}, "3014": {"1": "withstanding", "2": "to withstand", "3": "is withstood", "4": "has withstood", "answer": "has withstood", "question": "Because of its regular customers, the Bason Shop ___ the harsh economic recession."}, "3015": {"1": "diligent", "2": "prepared", "3": "displayed", "4": "integral", "answer": "integral", "question": "Most CEOs of large corporations agree that strong human resources are ___ to the success of a company."}, "3016": {"1": "in favor of", "2": "prior to", "3": "owing to", "4": "in case of", "answer": "prior to", "question": "I had to notify our partner company in China three days ___ my departure because they had to find me somewhere to stay while there."}, "3017": {"1": "dine", "2": "dined", "3": "dining", "4": "diner", "answer": "dining", "question": "Rather than the usual hosted dinner and drinks, we will be ___ tonight at the Mandarin Garden at  Shattuck Ave, near the corner of Elm Street."}, "3018": {"1": "in", "2": "on", "3": "at", "4": "after", "answer": "at", "question": "McAllister Orchards promises its customers nutritious and wholesome grains, fruits, and vegetables ___ a low cost."}, "3019": {"1": "ideal", "2": "ideally", "3": "idealized", "4": "ideality", "answer": "ideally", "question": "Shareholders voted that Deborah LaSalle is ___ suited for the position of chief operating officer given her experience."}, "3020": {"1": "my", "2": "me", "3": "I", "4": "mine", "answer": "I", "question": "This plan outlines the topics ___ plan to discuss at this afternoon's staff meeting."}, "3021": {"1": "that", "2": "who", "3": "which", "4": "whom", "answer": "who", "question": "When looking into the projected draft for construction of a new shopping mall, the supervisor asked ___ was in charge of electrical engineering."}, "3022": {"1": "challenge", "2": "challenges", "3": "challenging", "4": "challenged", "answer": "challenges", "question": "As the chief administrative officer, Quincy Paxton will face exciting ___ in this new job with Laval International Shipping Company."}, "3023": {"1": "responsible", "2": "responsibly", "3": "responsibility", "4": "responsibilities", "answer": "responsible", "question": "Rei Takahashi is one of the three people ___ for overseeing the Research Department at Omi-Tech Solutions."}, "3024": {"1": "brightly", "2": "regularly", "3": "previously", "4": "accidentally", "answer": "regularly", "question": "As the chief accountant, Ms. Dasgupta must ___ review and re-evaluate the company finances."}, "3025": {"1": "formalize", "2": "formally", "3": "formal", "4": "formality", "answer": "formally", "question": "The CEO ___ appointed James Farley as vice president of Arctic Mining Ventures Co."}, "3026": {"1": "as", "2": "then", "3": "so", "4": "if", "answer": "so", "question": "Staff is reminded to treat new employees with courtesy ___ that a friendly and professional work environment can be maintained."}, "3027": {"1": "working", "2": "worker", "3": "work", "4": "worked", "answer": "work", "question": "Ms. Quong is a promising bookkeeper at our firm, as she completes ___ assigned to her with precision and quickness."}, "3028": {"1": "depends", "2": "adapts", "3": "specializes", "4": "recommends", "answer": "recommends", "question": "Lancaster Productions ___ that all workers occasionally re-read their employee guideline booklets to help refresh their memories on company policies."}, "3029": {"1": "who", "2": "whose", "3": "what", "4": "their", "answer": "who", "question": "For those ___ are determined to attend the seminar, tickets are available at the Human Resources Department."}, "3030": {"1": "themselves", "2": "them", "3": "itself", "4": "it", "answer": "it", "question": "New students at Strafford College of Computer Science are advised to take a free students' guide booklet and review ___ thoroughly."}, "3031": {"1": "Up", "2": "About", "3": "By", "4": "To", "answer": "By", "question": "___ hiring the British marketing agent Arthur Downshire, Keene Clothiers Co. has gained an edge against its competition."}, "3032": {"1": "reported", "2": "demonstrated", "3": "shown", "4": "guided", "answer": "guided", "question": "Sutter Hotel Tours provides a weekend special which includes a ___ tour around the gorgeous bay area of the resort and some scenic islands accessible only by ferry."}, "3033": {"1": "include", "2": "import", "3": "accept", "4": "enter", "answer": "accept", "question": "Many locations in the city popular with tourists only ___ credit cards."}, "3034": {"1": "next", "2": "close", "3": "adjacency", "4": "neighboring", "answer": "adjacency", "question": "The music area will be enlarged to include practice room with immediate ___ to the stage."}, "3035": {"1": "only", "2": "there", "3": "most", "4": "how", "answer": "how", "question": "Spokesmen for Newport Properties praise the company about ___ wellmade their dwellings are."}, "3036": {"1": "standard", "2": "category", "3": "rate", "4": "qualification", "answer": "standard", "question": "The restaurants along upscale Fulton Avenue maintain a strict ___ ."}, "3037": {"1": "nearly", "2": "largely", "3": "efficiently", "4": "particularly", "answer": "efficiently", "question": "Clayton Books hired some extra staff since setting up the store's website, so online orders can be handled ___ ."}, "3038": {"1": "during", "2": "whereas", "3": "while", "4": "through", "answer": "while", "question": "The lights turn on every day at 6 a.m. and off again at 1Op.m. ___ employees are in the office."}, "3039": {"1": "belief", "2": "advancement", "3": "site", "4": "travel", "answer": "site", "question": "The ___ for the public park will be between Meriwether Avenue and Winchester Drive, just north of Keenan Street."}, "3040": {"1": "Now that", "2": "In fact", "3": "In case of", "4": "Because of", "answer": "Because of", "question": "___ the unseasonably warm weather, Sweet Indulgences ice cream shops opened two weeks ahead of schedule."}, "3041": {"1": "positive", "2": "positively", "3": "positivity", "4": "positiveness", "answer": "positively", "question": "Amateur theatrical performances by locals and some appearances by renowned poets were ___ reviewed by journalists in the Eberlein County Daily."}, "3042": {"1": "attend", "2": "apply", "3": "enroll", "4": "expect", "answer": "enroll", "question": "Employees who wish to ___ in the marketing seminar are urged to do so by this Friday."}, "3043": {"1": "operate", "2": "operation", "3": "operated", "4": "operational", "answer": "operation", "question": "After ten years in ___ , Ravensdale Fiduciary Firm is expanding its factories to Shanghai, Hong Kong, Tokyo, Seoul, and Singapore."}, "3044": {"1": "of", "2": "from", "3": "with", "4": "for", "answer": "of", "question": "This summer's lack ___ interesting events in the community caused a decline in tourism from other townships."}, "3045": {"1": "favor", "2": "favors", "3": "favorable", "4": "favorably", "answer": "favorable", "question": "Construction of the new shopping center should be complete by the end of the year as long as economic conditions are ___ ."}, "3046": {"1": "But", "2": "Even so", "3": "Except", "4": "Although", "answer": "Although", "question": "___ top entertainment venues enjoy using notable celebrities, local talents are also welcome to participate and gain experience."}, "3047": {"1": "careful", "2": "relevant", "3": "convenient", "4": "regardless", "answer": "relevant", "question": "The purchase of high-risk products should be accompanied by retaining ___ receipts while exiting the store."}, "3048": {"1": "permissive", "2": "outgoing", "3": "reversed", "4": "absolute", "answer": "outgoing", "question": "All ___ products must be properly registered before being shipped out the distribution center."}, "3049": {"1": "on", "2": "in", "3": "with", "4": "for", "answer": "on", "question": "The survey indicates how much the average person within various income spends ___ specific goods and services."}, "3050": {"1": "who", "2": "whom", "3": "whoever", "4": "anyone", "answer": "anyone", "question": "Remember that work-life balance issues can affect ___ in any stage of the life cycle."}, "3051": {"1": "exceedingly", "2": "accordingly", "3": "considerably", "4": "namely", "answer": "accordingly", "question": "When shipping, it is crucial to label chemical samples ___ ."}, "3052": {"1": "notable", "2": "observant", "3": "exclusive", "4": "limiting", "answer": "exclusive", "question": "Most of the information held on computers used by employees is the ___ property of Perelli Solutions Inc."}, "3053": {"1": "Every", "2": "Almost", "3": "Once", "4": "Near", "answer": "Almost", "question": "___ half of the existing employees at Alabama factory have agreed to transfer to the newly built factory in Ohio in July."}, "3054": {"1": "reproductive", "2": "overran", "3": "inadequate", "4": "underwritten", "answer": "inadequate", "question": "We are unable to meet the present demand because of ___ plant capacity."}, "3055": {"1": "was monitored", "2": "monitors", "3": "to monitor", "4": "monitoring", "answer": "monitoring", "question": "Brackwell Farms plans on implementing a natural ___ system that checks for the acidity levels in the soil."}, "3056": {"1": "to speed it up or slow it down", "2": "it speeds up or slows down", "3": "than speeding it up or slowing it down", "4": "than speeding up or slowing down", "answer": "to speed it up or slow it down", "question": "The greater an objects's mass, the more difficult it is ___ ."}, "3057": {"1": "skin", "2": "which is smooth", "3": "smooth skin", "4": "smooth-skinned", "answer": "smooth-skinned", "question": "The grape is the ___ , juicy fruit of a woody vine."}, "3058": {"1": "began to be used as rugs", "2": "rugs began to be used", "3": "as rugs began to be used", "4": "began to used them as rugs", "answer": "began to be used as rugs", "question": "In the second half of the nineteenth century, textiles from the southwestern United state, particularly fabrics woven by the Navajo people, ___ ."}, "3059": {"1": "the values", "2": "of the values", "3": "the values are", "4": "are the values", "answer": "the values", "question": "During adolescence many young people begin to question ___ held by their families."}, "3060": {"1": "as was defines by others", "2": "its definitions by others", "3": "other's definition", "4": "as others defined it", "answer": "as others defined it", "question": "In her writing, Elimor Wylie often dealt with her own personality as it was, rather than ___ ."}, "3061": {"1": "to act", "2": "acting", "3": "that has acted", "4": "having acted", "answer": "to act", "question": "Congress chartered the first Bank of the United States in  to engage in general commercial banking and ___ as a fiscal agent of the federal government."}, "3062": {"1": "what is conceived", "2": "what it is conceived", "3": "what is conceived to be", "4": "what is being conceived", "answer": "what is conceived to be", "question": "Essentially, a theory is an abstract, symbolic representation of ___ reality."}, "3063": {"1": "runs off that", "2": "runs it off", "3": "that runs it off", "4": "that runs off", "answer": "that runs off", "question": "The more arid the continent, the less the amount of annual precipitation ___ ."}, "3064": {"1": "much better from", "2": "more better than", "3": "much better as", "4": "much better than", "answer": "much better than", "question": "He really deserved the award because he performed ___ was expected of him."}, "3065": {"1": "others", "2": "thing", "3": "another", "4": "the other", "answer": "another", "question": "To take pride in what deserves boasting is one thing, and to take good care of it is quite ___ ."}, "3066": {"1": "though charming and capable is he", "2": "even with charm and so capable", "3": "charming and having capability", "4": "however charming and capable", "answer": "however charming and capable", "question": "It would be difficult for a man of his political affiliation, ___, to become a senator from the south."}, "3067": {"1": "what has saved", "2": "which saved", "3": "which has saved", "4": "who saves", "answer": "which has saved", "question": "Penicillin is perhaps the drug ___ more lives than any other in the history of medicine."}, "3068": {"1": "to understand", "2": "understandably", "3": "understandable", "4": "when understood", "answer": "understandable", "question": "A politician can make a legislative proposal more ___ by giving specific examples of what its effect will be."}, "3069": {"1": "are voted", "2": "voting", "3": "to be voted", "4": "will vote", "answer": "will vote", "question": "Before every presidential election in the United States, the statisticians try to guess the proportion of the population that ___ for each candidate."}, "3070": {"1": "useful most world's", "2": "world's most useful", "3": "useful world's most", "4": "most world's useful", "answer": "world's most useful", "question": "The decimal numeral system is one of the ___ ways of expressing numbers."}, "3071": {"1": "in others droughts", "2": "droughts are others", "3": "while other droughts", "4": "others in drought", "answer": "in others droughts", "question": "Nebraska has floods in some years, ___ ."}, "3072": {"1": "as others defined it", "2": "other's definitions", "3": "its definition by others", "4": "it was defined by others", "answer": "as others defined it", "question": "In her writing, Elinor Wylie, often dealt with her own responsibility as it was, rater than ___ ."}, "3073": {"1": "Although such a short time", "2": "It is such a short", "3": "With so short time", "4": "With such a short time", "answer": "With such a short time", "question": "___ left before the deadline, it doesn't seem likely that John will accomplish the job."}, "3074": {"1": "regularly reading", "2": "were reading regularly", "3": "regularly reading what", "4": "who reading regularly", "answer": "regularly reading", "question": "With the start for the penny papers in the 's, the number of people ___ a newspaper rose considerably."}, "3075": {"1": "known", "2": "known are", "3": "they are known", "4": "what is known", "answer": "known", "question": "At present production levels, ___ deposits of bauxite can provide the world with aluminum for hundreds of years."}, "3076": {"1": "of varying thickness", "2": "varied thickness", "3": "its thickness varies", "4": "its thickness varying", "answer": "of varying thickness", "question": "Au bones have an exterior layer, termed the cortex, that is smooth, dense, continuous, and ___ ."}, "3077": {"1": "was one of the greatest periods", "2": "one of the greatest periods", "3": "was of the greatest periods", "4": "the greatest periods", "answer": "was one of the greatest periods", "question": "Coinciding with the development of jazz in New Orleans in the 's ___ in blues music."}, "3078": {"1": "give it that", "2": "that give it", "3": "give that", "4": "that gives it to", "answer": "that give it", "question": "Despite its wide range of styles and instrumentation, country music has certain common features ___ its own special character."}, "3079": {"1": "The cool air", "2": "If the air is cool", "3": "That the air cools", "4": "The cooler the air", "answer": "If the air is cool", "question": "___ around stones that are sunwarmed, even the smallest of stones creates tiny currents of warm air."}, "3080": {"1": "starting", "2": "having started", "3": "once I start", "4": "after to start", "answer": "once I start", "question": "\"Whenever I have to write a paper, I don't know where to begin.\" \"I have the same problem, but ___ the paper seems to write itself.\""}, "3081": {"1": "was proved to be useful", "2": "has proved it useful", "3": "has been proved to be useful", "4": "has proved useful", "answer": "has proved useful", "question": "This Information ___ to a great many people."}, "3082": {"1": "is", "2": "the", "3": "has", "4": "it has", "answer": "the", "question": "The closer to one of the Earth's poles, the greater ___ gravitational force."}, "3083": {"1": "when", "2": "is", "3": "that it is", "4": "was", "answer": "when", "question": "The flamingo uses its bill ___ feeding to filter mud and water from the tiny plants and animals that it finds in shallow ponds."}, "3084": {"1": "how the thunder and lightening are far away", "2": "how far away the thunder and lightening are", "3": "how far away are the thunder and lightening", "4": "the thunder and lightening are how far away", "answer": "how far away the thunder and lightening are", "question": "The amount of lapsed time between the thunder and lightening can be used to determine ___ ."}, "3085": {"1": "it possible", "2": "possible", "3": "it is possible", "4": "possibility", "answer": "possible", "question": "The application of electronic controls made ___ by the microprocessor and computer storage have multiplied the uses of the modern typewriter."}, "3086": {"1": "days to shovel people several", "2": "people several days to shovel", "3": "several days people to shovel", "4": "people to shovel several days", "answer": "people several days to shovel", "question": "After the great blizzard of  in the northeastern United States, it took some ___ the snow away from their homes."}, "3087": {"1": "amount to", "2": "in the amount", "3": "amount to it", "4": "to the amount of", "answer": "amount to", "question": "The production of tin ore in the United States is relatively insignificant, ___ less than one hundred tons annually."}, "3088": {"1": "known what", "2": "known what it is", "3": "what is known", "4": "what it is known", "answer": "what is known", "question": "A logarithm is ___algebra as an exponent."}, "3089": {"1": "human behavior is studied", "2": "is human behavior studied", "3": "is studied human behavior", "4": "human behavior", "answer": "is human behavior studied", "question": "Not only ___ in the field of psychology but animal behavior is examined as well."}, "3090": {"1": "that they grow", "2": "that grow", "3": "they grow it", "4": "do they grow", "answer": "that they grow", "question": "Farmers grow popcorn in much the same way ___ field corn, except that the rows are planted closer together."}, "3091": {"1": "Parsely, an herb that is", "2": "For parsely, an herb to be", "3": "An herb, parsely is", "4": "Parsely, is that herb", "answer": "Parsely, an herb that is", "question": "___ often added to sauces and soups, is plentiful and relatively inexpensive."}, "3092": {"1": "most famous", "2": "the most famous", "3": "are most famous", "4": "and most famous", "answer": "most famous", "question": "The Grapes of Wrath, a novel about the Depression years of the 's, is one of John Steinbecks's ___ books."}, "3093": {"1": "so can do", "2": "do so can", "3": "can do so", "4": "so do can", "answer": "can do so", "question": "A semiconductor is a substance that seldom conducts electricity, but ___ under certain circumstances."}, "3094": {"1": "tuna", "2": "the tuna", "3": "being the tuna", "4": "is the tuna", "answer": "is the tuna", "question": "Among the giants of the sea ___, which may weigh up to 1, pounds."}, "3095": {"1": "All living things consist of", "2": "Although all living things that consist of", "3": "All living things consisting of", "4": "In all living things consisting of", "answer": "All living things consist of", "question": "___ one of more units of living substance called protoplasm."}, "3096": {"1": "serve as", "2": "serve", "3": "in serving", "4": "be served", "answer": "serve as", "question": "A newspaper's political cartoons ___ capsule versions of editorial opinion."}, "3097": {"1": "the softest one of", "2": "softest of the one", "3": "the one of the softest", "4": "one of the softest", "answer": "one of the softest", "question": "Diamond is the hardest substance known, whereas graphite, another carbon allotrope, is___ ."}, "3098": {"1": "divides", "2": "divide", "3": "be dividing", "4": "to be divided", "answer": "to be divided", "question": "Texas is the only state whose constitution permits it ___ into smaller states."}, "3099": {"1": "in spite of", "2": "contrary", "3": "contrast to", "4": "but", "answer": "but", "question": "Until the ninth century, written words were not actually separated, ___ in some literary writing, dots or points were used to indicate divisions."}, "3100": {"1": "how one atom or molecule could stimulate", "2": "one atom or molecule stimulating", "3": "stimulating one atom or molecule by", "4": "by which one atom or molecule could stimulate", "answer": "by which one atom or molecule could stimulate", "question": "Physicists sought ways ___ many others to emit light, amplifying it to much higher powers."}, "3101": {"1": "how", "2": "of", "3": "by which", "4": "for it", "answer": "by which", "question": "An ideal is a standard ___ people judge real phenomena."}, "3102": {"1": "the oldest continuously occupied", "2": "occupied continuously the oldest", "3": "the oldest occupied continuously", "4": "continuously the oldest occupied", "answer": "the oldest continuously occupied", "question": "Founded around , the Acoma pueblo is considered ___settlement in the United States."}, "3103": {"1": "as the best engineer", "2": "be the best engineer", "3": "by the president to be the best engineer", "4": "as being the best engineer", "answer": "as the best engineer", "question": "Jacobson is often referred to ___ at the factory."}, "3104": {"1": "To apply for this job", "2": "In order to get his job", "3": "Making application for this job", "4": "If you want to apply for this job", "answer": "If you want to apply for this job", "question": "___, a Form 57 must be completed."}, "3105": {"1": "with which", "2": "where", "3": "which", "4": "in which", "answer": "in which", "question": "The farmer uses wood to build a house ___ to store grains."}, "3106": {"1": "amounting to", "2": "in the amount", "3": "amounts to it", "4": "to the amount of", "answer": "amounting to", "question": "The production of tim ore in the United States is relatively insignificant, ___ less than one hundred tons annually."}, "3107": {"1": "known what", "2": "known what it is", "3": "what is known", "4": "what it is known", "answer": "what it is known", "question": "A logarithm is ___ in algebra as an exponent."}, "3108": {"1": "human behavior is studied", "2": "is human behavior studied", "3": "is studied human behavior", "4": "human behavior", "answer": "is human behavior studied", "question": "Not only ___ in the field of psychology but animal behavior is examined as well."}, "3109": {"1": "was", "2": "were", "3": "who was", "4": "who were", "answer": "who was", "question": "Every one of the boys ___ here yesterday has a bicycle."}, "3110": {"1": "the softest one of", "2": "softest of the one", "3": "the one of the softest", "4": "one of the softest", "answer": "one of the softest", "question": "Diamond is the hardest substance known, whereas graphite, another carbon allotrope, is___ ."}, "3111": {"1": "divides", "2": "divide", "3": "be dividing", "4": "to be divided", "answer": "to be divided", "question": "Texas is the only state whose constitution permits it ___ into smaller states."}, "3112": {"1": "in spite of", "2": "contrary", "3": "contrast to", "4": "but", "answer": "but", "question": "Until the ninth century, written words were not actually separated, ___ in some literary writing, dots or points were used to indicate divisions."}, "3113": {"1": "amount to", "2": "in the amount", "3": "amount to it", "4": "to the amount of", "answer": "amount to", "question": "The production of tin ore in the United States is relatively insignificant, ___ less than one hundred tons annually."}, "3114": {"1": "known what", "2": "known what it is", "3": "what is known", "4": "what it is known", "answer": "what is known", "question": "A logarithm is ___ .algebra as an exponent."}, "3115": {"1": "human behavior is studied", "2": "is human behavior studied", "3": "is studied human behavior", "4": "human behavior", "answer": "is human behavior studied", "question": "Not only ___ in the field of psychology but animal behavior is examined as well."}, "3116": {"1": "was", "2": "were", "3": "who was", "4": "who were", "answer": "who were", "question": "Every one of the boys ___ here yesterday has a bicycle."}, "3117": {"1": "that they grow", "2": "that grow", "3": "they grow it", "4": "do they grow", "answer": "that they grow", "question": "Farmers grow popcorn in much the same way ___ field corn, except that the rows are planted closer together."}, "3118": {"1": "Parsely, an herb that is", "2": "For parsely, an herb to be", "3": "An herb, parsely is", "4": "Parsely, is that herb", "answer": "Parsely, an herb that is", "question": "___ often added to sauces and soups, is plentiful and relatively inexpensive."}, "3119": {"1": "most famous", "2": "the most famous", "3": "are most famous", "4": "and most famous", "answer": "most famous", "question": "The Grapes of Wrath, a novel about the Depression years of the 's, is one of John Steinback's ___ books."}, "3120": {"1": "so can do", "2": "do so can", "3": "can do so", "4": "so do can", "answer": "can do so", "question": "A semiconductor is a substance that seldom conducts electricity, but ___ under certain circumstances."}, "3121": {"1": "tuna", "2": "the tuna", "3": "being the tuna", "4": "is the tuna", "answer": "is the tuna", "question": "Among the giants of the sea ___ which may weigh up to 1, pounds."}, "3122": {"1": "All living things consist of", "2": "Although all living things that consist of", "3": "All living things consisting of", "4": "In all living things consisting of", "answer": "All living things consist of", "question": "___ one of more units of living substance called protoplasm."}, "3123": {"1": "serve as", "2": "serve", "3": "in serving", "4": "be served", "answer": "serve as", "question": "A newspaper's political cartoons ___ capsule versions of editorial opinion."}, "3124": {"1": "Tornadoes almost occur never", "2": "Tornadoes never almost occur", "3": "Never tornadoes almost occur", "4": "Tornadoes almost never occur", "answer": "Tornadoes almost never occur", "question": "___ west of the Rocky Mountains."}, "3125": {"1": "one hundred years later", "2": "one hundred years ago", "3": "the one hundred years since", "4": "the last one hundred years", "answer": "the last one hundred years", "question": "In ___, the advent of the telephone, radio, and television has made rapid long-distance communication possible."}, "3126": {"1": "of value", "2": "is valuable", "3": "to be valued", "4": "valuable", "answer": "is valuable", "question": "Not every peal that is found ___"}, "3127": {"1": "geometrically designed", "2": "designs are geometric", "3": "geometric designs", "4": "geometry designed", "answer": "geometric designs", "question": "The clay burial vessels from the early Hopewell culture of North America are decorated with zigzag, grooved, and ___"}, "3128": {"1": "Not only does rust corrode", "2": "Not only rust corrode", "3": "Rust, which not only corrode", "4": "Rust not only corrodes", "answer": "Rust not only corrodes", "question": "___ the surface of metal, but also weakens it."}, "3129": {"1": "when, pure which", "2": "when, which pure", "3": "which, pure when", "4": "which, when pure", "answer": "which, when pure", "question": "All marble is composed of crystals of the minerals calcite or dobmite, ___, are perfectly white."}, "3130": {"1": "less the farther it gets", "2": "the farther it gets, the less", "3": "less than it gets farther", "4": "less than it, the farther it gets", "answer": "less the farther it gets", "question": "A body weighs ___ from the surface of the Earth."}, "3131": {"1": "each has", "2": "with each", "3": "has each", "4": "each with", "answer": "each with", "question": "When a bacterium becomes to large, it splits on half and forms two new bacteria, ___ its own cell wall and protoplasm."}, "3132": {"1": "clearest", "2": "the clearest", "3": "much clearer", "4": "more clearer", "answer": "much clearer", "question": "The photographs of Mars taken by satellite are ___ than those taken from the Earth."}, "3133": {"1": "which we are certain", "2": "that we are certain of", "3": "of which we are sure", "4": "for which we are sure", "answer": "which we are certain", "question": "Our friends are expected to assume the burden of their own defense, ___ they are competent to do."}, "3134": {"1": "to require", "2": "requiring", "3": "to be required", "4": "required", "answer": "required", "question": "I have written about the change in the social system ___ to promote happiness."}, "3135": {"1": "Believing", "2": "To believe", "3": "The belief", "4": "It is believed", "answer": "It is believed", "question": "___ that the formation of the sun, the planets, and other stars began with the condensation of an interstellar gas cloud."}, "3136": {"1": "which hang", "2": "which has hung", "3": "by that hung", "4": "which hung", "answer": "which hung", "question": "The art students were enthralled by the sheer beauty of the portrait ___ before them."}, "3137": {"1": "is not known", "2": "not known", "3": "has not known", "4": "are not known", "answer": "is not known", "question": "where to find him and how to find him ___ to us."}, "3138": {"1": "that the merger should go", "2": "to go on merging", "3": "to start merging", "4": "to go ahead with the merger", "answer": "to go ahead with the merger", "question": "After careful consideration and planning, he was determined ___"}, "3139": {"1": "What is known", "2": "To be known", "3": "Knowing is", "4": "Known", "answer": "What is known", "question": "___ about Emily Dickinson's psychological and emotional well-being is inferred from her poems and letters."}, "3140": {"1": "are absorbed", "2": "absorbed", "3": "which is absorbed", "4": "is absorbed", "answer": "is absorbed", "question": "Much of the precipitation that falls on the earth ___ by plants"}, "3141": {"1": "a bottom area more than", "2": "more bottom area", "3": "more bottom area than", "4": "a bottom area more", "answer": "more bottom area", "question": "The Pacific is the deepest ocean, with ___ at more profound depths than any other ocean."}, "3142": {"1": "there are", "2": "many", "3": "some of", "4": "it is", "answer": "there are", "question": "Multicolored woodcuts must be printed with as many blocks as ___ colors in the composition."}, "3143": {"1": "Children that were interested", "2": "That children interested", "3": "That children should be interested", "4": "That interested children", "answer": "That children should be interested", "question": "___ in science was important for Faraday."}, "3144": {"1": "What Robert Peary", "2": "That Robert Peary", "3": "Robert Peary, who", "4": "Robert Peary was", "answer": "That Robert Peary", "question": "Despite recent attempts to prove ___ did indeed reach the North Pole in , the evidence still remains questionable."}, "3145": {"1": "That makes the rye plant", "2": "What makes the rye plant", "3": "The rye plant", "4": "The rye plant which was", "answer": "What makes the rye plant", "question": "___so incredible B that it can grow  miles of roots in four months, or about 3 miles in a day."}, "3146": {"1": "Alexander the Great who", "2": "Whether Alexander the great", "3": "Alexander the Great", "4": "What Alexander the great", "answer": "Whether Alexander the great", "question": "___ was lowered to the sea bed in a glass container to make observation B debated."}, "3147": {"1": "Although", "2": "However", "3": "Despite", "4": "Since", "answer": "Although", "question": "___ more than  minerals are known, nearly all rocks are formed from seven mineral groups."}, "3148": {"1": "To obtain", "2": "It obtains", "3": "It is obtaining", "4": "Obtaining", "answer": "To obtain", "question": "___ energy for growth or repair, a plant must carry out photosynthesis"}, "3149": {"1": "crowd", "2": "crowds", "3": "crowding", "4": "crowded", "answer": "crowded", "question": "Some visitors to Dubrovnik feel that it is too ___ with tourists to be enjoyable during the summer."}, "3150": {"1": "both", "2": "while", "3": "not only", "4": "nor", "answer": "both", "question": "The bicycles designed by Andre Lim are ___ easy to assemble and attractive to many young people."}, "3151": {"1": "works", "2": "has worked", "3": "will work", "4": "had worked", "answer": "had worked", "question": "Before Mr. Kim joined our company as a sales analyst, he ___ in the sales sector for several years already."}, "3152": {"1": "lightly", "2": "briefly", "3": "consistently", "4": "enormously", "answer": "consistently", "question": "Our dedicated team has ___ produced high quality, innovative products since the company was established in ."}, "3153": {"1": "produce", "2": "to produce", "3": "productively", "4": "productivity", "answer": "productivity", "question": "The continuing spread of office automation has increased worker ___ , resulting in job consolidation and lower demand for accounting clerks."}, "3154": {"1": "revealed", "2": "trained", "3": "understood", "4": "taken", "answer": "trained", "question": "Teachers must be ___ in the use of the  new technology so that their students can benefit."}, "3155": {"1": "who", "2": "whom", "3": "whoever", "4": "whose", "answer": "whose", "question": "Award-winning Maida Stewart is one of the Australian artists ___ -- paintings are currently on display in the Dots exhibition at Pace Gallery."}, "3156": {"1": "facilities", "2": "attributes", "3": "supplies", "4": "members", "answer": "supplies", "question": "As an administrative assistant, you are responsible for ordering office ___ such as pens, papers, ink cartridges, and staplers."}, "3157": {"1": "direction", "2": "directing", "3": "directly", "4": "directs", "answer": "directly", "question": "You will report ___ to the project manager and you will be responsible for overseeing the work of engineers and designers."}, "3158": {"1": "publicizing", "2": "publicized", "3": "publicity", "4": "publicize", "answer": "publicized", "question": "The event was well ___ and covered by numerous media including television stations and newspapers across the country."}, "3159": {"1": "prompted", "2": "required", "3": "insisted", "4": "appealed", "answer": "required", "question": "All visitors to the main office are ___ to present their identification cards to the security guard when entering the building."}, "3160": {"1": "within", "2": "on", "3": "after", "4": "along", "answer": "after", "question": "In , Italian fashion designer Valentino Garavani announced his retirement ___ 45 years in the fashion business."}, "3161": {"1": "expand", "2": "expands", "3": "expansion", "4": "expansive", "answer": "expansion", "question": "Our monthly production capability is expected to grow significantly, owing to the ___ of our own factories in China."}, "3162": {"1": "they", "2": "them", "3": "themselves", "4": "their", "answer": "their", "question": "Coles Online Delivery is a new service enabling customers to order ___ groceries on the Internet."}, "3163": {"1": "fund", "2": "payment", "3": "copy", "4": "collection", "answer": "copy", "question": "For your reference, we have enclosed a ___ of the renewal notification which will be sent to subscribers."}, "3164": {"1": "approved", "2": "approvable", "3": "approval", "4": "approvingly", "answer": "approved", "question": "The board of directors on December 20 ___ the annual budget which won't be official until signed by President John Wei."}, "3165": {"1": "Until", "2": "Once", "3": "Unless", "4": "Although", "answer": "Although", "question": "___ Mega Foods imports only one kind of cheese now, the company will be importing a total of five varieties by next year."}, "3166": {"1": "efficient", "2": "efficiency", "3": "efficiently", "4": ".efficiencies", "answer": "efficiently", "question": "Technological progress is making it possible to produce goods more ___ with less labor input."}, "3167": {"1": "from", "2": "of", "3": "beside", "4": "with", "answer": "beside", "question": "The university's Career Services Center can assist students in finding part-time work and the jobs available are posted ___ the entrance to the office."}, "3168": {"1": "offer", "2": "hire", "3": "relocate", "4": "ask", "answer": "offer", "question": "After carefully reviewing a number of job applications, we are pleased to ___ you the marketing director position."}, "3169": {"1": "without", "2": "along", "3": "between", "4": "outside", "answer": "without", "question": "You will be required to show valid identification prior to processing a refund request ___ a receipt."}, "3170": {"1": "authorized", "2": "authorization", "3": "authority", "4": "authorize", "answer": "authorized", "question": "If you are planning to install the machine by yourself, then we recommend that you visit one of our ___ dealers that can give you additional installation assistance."}, "3171": {"1": "himself", "2": "his", "3": "he", "4": "him", "answer": "him", "question": "In preparation for the quarterly sales meeting, please print out the latest sales figures for Mr. Cho and mail it to ___ ."}, "3172": {"1": "enclosed", "2": "shaped", "3": "trained", "4": "engaged", "answer": "enclosed", "question": "With the signing of the ___ contract, we would like to welcome you as a supplier to our company."}, "3173": {"1": "quicker", "2": "quickest", "3": "quickly", "4": "quickness", "answer": "quickly", "question": "Lawmakers must ___ find a way to cut another 11 million dollars from this year's budget to fix the error."}, "3174": {"1": "quite", "2": "specially", "3": "seldom", "4": "profoundly", "answer": "specially", "question": "The Super Tip toothbrush was ___ designed to remove bacterial plaque while effectively cleaning all surfaces of the teeth."}, "3175": {"1": "economical", "2": "economy", "3": "economist", "4": "economize", "answer": "economical", "question": "In order to reduce costs, Busan Consulting's ___ use of office space and equipment has been adopted by many local businesses."}, "3176": {"1": "with", "2": "toward", "3": "between", "4": "by", "answer": "by", "question": "The manager has asked Mr. Lim to submit his final report on the sales of the new washing machine ___ April 30th."}, "3177": {"1": "sell", "2": "sells", "3": "sold", "4": "selling", "answer": "selling", "question": "The Perfect Pet Parlor is a chain of stores ___ a large selection of pet food and pet accessories at a reasonable price with excellent sales support."}, "3178": {"1": "problems", "2": "concepts", "3": "inquiries", "4": "positions", "answer": "inquiries", "question": "Since Mr. Kane is on vacation until next week, all product ___ should be made to Mr. Park in the customer service department."}, "3179": {"1": "No", "2": "Not", "3": "None", "4": "Never", "answer": "No", "question": "___ direct flights are available from Atlanta to Calgary International Airport, although major airlines offer good connections through Chicago, Denver or Houston."}, "3180": {"1": "plan", "2": "planner", "3": "planning", "4": "planned", "answer": "planning", "question": "Thanks to careful ___ , the installation of the new equipment did not disrupt or affect the plant's activities."}, "3181": {"1": "each", "2": "every", "3": "once", "4": "one", "answer": "once", "question": "The members meet ___ a week to discuss the next steps to be taken in achieving their objective."}, "3182": {"1": "Others", "2": "They", "3": "Herself", "4": "Anyone", "answer": "Anyone", "question": "___ who has questions regarding the hospital bill, pricing information or insurance coverage can contact our customer service representative."}, "3183": {"1": "invited", "2": "prepared", "3": "loaded", "4": "commended", "answer": "loaded", "question": "The display is for paper size selection, and shows the paper sizes that are currently ___ in the copier."}, "3184": {"1": "wherever", "2": "however", "3": "whomever", "4": "whatever", "answer": "whatever", "question": "Snacks and soft drinks will be served, but participants can bring ___ they like on the hiking trip."}, "3185": {"1": "always", "2": "nearly", "3": "strongly", "4": "almost", "answer": "always", "question": "Current uniforms must ___ be worn while on duty and should be kept well maintained."}, "3186": {"1": "facilities", "2": "guidelines", "3": "products", "4": "procedures", "answer": "facilities", "question": "Only full-time employees and their family members are entitled to use the company ___ such as the company gymnasium for free."}, "3187": {"1": "of", "2": "up", "3": "as", "4": "on", "answer": "on", "question": "As a local business association member, you may advertise ___ our website free of charge, for employment, or items for sale."}, "3188": {"1": "perfectly", "2": "gradually", "3": "heavily", "4": "slowly", "answer": "perfectly", "question": "The new SM-8 model is ___ suited for transporting four adults; however, like most sedans, the rear seat is a bit narrow for three adults."}, "3189": {"1": "that", "2": "there", "3": "any", "4": "how", "answer": "that", "question": "The invoice ___ was received two days ago is inaccurate and a new one must be requested."}, "3190": {"1": "therefore", "2": "consequently", "3": "otherwise", "4": "yet", "answer": "otherwise", "question": "Unless specified ___ , contractors will be responsible for obtaining all necessary safety certification and permits applicable to their scope of work."}, "3191": {"1": "on", "2": "for", "3": "from", "4": "in", "answer": "from", "question": "Any concerns regarding your natural gas appliances should be directed to the manufacturer-retailer ___ which you purchased the natural gas appliance."}, "3192": {"1": "bright", "2": "brightest", "3": "brightens", "4": "brightness", "answer": "brightest", "question": "The use of the ___ possible lighting in the laboratory has been beneficial to the research conducted by the botanists employed there."}, "3193": {"1": "Both", "2": "Each", "3": "Either", "4": "Neither", "answer": "Either", "question": "___ Mr. Fowler or Ms. Bloch will have to travel to London for the symposium on textile manufacturing."}, "3194": {"1": "highly", "2": "high", "3": "highest", "4": "higher", "answer": "highly", "question": "Andrew Hartwell is ___ regarded by his employees because of his dedication and experience."}, "3195": {"1": "sustained", "2": "held", "3": "supported", "4": "meet", "answer": "held", "question": "All future team meetings will be ___ in room  at noon on the first Wednesday of every month."}, "3196": {"1": "detail", "2": "details", "3": "detailed", "4": "detailing", "answer": "details", "question": "In a television interview, the Traxton Ltd. CEO said that ___ of the merger with Bell Corporation would be announced soon."}, "3197": {"1": "but", "2": "however", "3": "also", "4": "and", "answer": "but", "question": "Ms. Fenwick not only composed the report ___ produced the visual aids which were so useful during the meeting."}, "3198": {"1": "probably", "2": "nearly", "3": "usefully", "4": "safely", "answer": "probably", "question": "The decline in sales was ___ due to the lack of innovation in the ideas of the marketing team."}, "3199": {"1": "total", "2": "absolute", "3": "ready", "4": "actual", "answer": "ready", "question": "The webpage for each course must be ___ before the students start their classes on January 7th."}, "3200": {"1": "indicates", "2": "commands", "3": "notices", "4": "distributes", "answer": "indicates", "question": "Once you have detected a fatal virus on your computer, common sense ___ that you should have your hard drive reformatted by skilled professionals."}, "3201": {"1": "professional", "2": "profession", "3": "professionals", "4": "professionally", "answer": "professionals", "question": "Rosewater Medical Center employs healthcare ___ affiliated with Huron University."}, "3202": {"1": "proposal", "2": "proposed", "3": "propose", "4": "proposing", "answer": "proposal", "question": "Mr. Lloyd has approved a ___ for the construction of a new research facility on the other side of the city."}, "3203": {"1": "refueled", "2": "rewarded", "3": "replenished", "4": "restocked", "answer": "rewarded", "question": "All members of the staff will be ___ with a bonus and two extra vacation days."}, "3204": {"1": "Follow", "2": "Following", "3": "Followed", "4": "Follows", "answer": "Following", "question": "___ the bankruptcy of Transcontinental Airlines, other airlines have noticed an increased use of connecting flights."}, "3205": {"1": "next", "2": "afterward", "3": "past", "4": "later", "answer": "later", "question": "Ms. Crowe's replacement for the position of treasurer will be announced ___ this month."}, "3206": {"1": "adequate", "2": "adequacy", "3": "adequately", "4": "adequateness", "answer": "adequately", "question": "The chemistry lab managers are concerned that new employees have not been trained ___ in the latest emergency procedures."}, "3207": {"1": "accustomed", "2": "indefinite", "3": "originated", "4": "leading", "answer": "leading", "question": "Perry and Monroe Inc. is one of the ___ companies in the field of environmentally-friendly household appliances."}, "3208": {"1": "service", "2": "serving", "3": "server", "4": "serves", "answer": "service", "question": "After twenty-three years of ___ , Jeffrey Bartlett is retiring from his position as chief accounting officer."}, "3209": {"1": "conferences", "2": "contributions", "3": "agendas", "4": "prescriptions", "answer": "conferences", "question": "Our marketing teams attend ___ regularly to learn new methods and strategies in their field."}, "3210": {"1": "suiting", "2": "suits", "3": "suitable", "4": "suitability", "answer": "suitable", "question": "Because of their size, few of our plumbing fixtures are ___ for indoor use."}, "3211": {"1": "official", "2": "officials", "3": "officially", "4": "officialize", "answer": "officially", "question": "The journal is published every four months, and ___ available to other member societies under agreement of payment and publication."}, "3212": {"1": "spill", "2": "spills", "3": "spilled", "4": "spilling", "answer": "spills", "question": "When oil ___ do occur as a result of accidents, a single incident has the potential to affect very large areas of sea and lengths of coast."}, "3213": {"1": "is known", "2": "will know", "3": "to know", "4": "has known", "answer": "is known", "question": "Arcadia Homes ___ for its commitment to provide customers with quality furniture at competitive prices."}, "3214": {"1": "along", "2": "for", "3": "to", "4": "while", "answer": "for", "question": "Much of this year's profits will be used ___ renovation of the textile plant."}, "3215": {"1": "project", "2": "scheme", "3": "method", "4": "format", "answer": "project", "question": "Everett-Buchanan Industries' research ___ on the newest drug to combat stomach infections recently received a grant from the National Gastrointestinal Medical Research Foundation."}, "3216": {"1": "who", "2": "whose", "3": "their", "4": "they", "answer": "whose", "question": "The main artists ___ paintings are being sold at the Garrett Gallery are Elaine Crick, Jason Chambers and Sylvia Webb."}, "3217": {"1": "seems", "2": "seeming", "3": "seemingly", "4": "seemed", "answer": "seemingly", "question": "The overall satisfaction of participants with the workshop is often based on ___ unimportant details such as the ability to park close to the training facility."}, "3218": {"1": "expand", "2": "recruit", "3": "revise", "4": "converse", "answer": "recruit", "question": "Because of the increase in tourism during the winter months, the Ebony Palms Hotel and Resort plans to ___ additional staff for the next three months."}, "3219": {"1": "against", "2": "between", "3": "by", "4": "under", "answer": "by", "question": "Employees who meet their quotas ___ the last week of the month can expect bonuses."}, "3220": {"1": "interrupts", "2": "to interrupt", "3": "was interrupted", "4": "be interrupted", "answer": "was interrupted", "question": "Even though construction ___ by unexpected electrical storms, the new office building was still finished in a timely manner."}, "3221": {"1": "extend", "2": "extends", "3": "extensive", "4": "extent", "answer": "extensive", "question": "The research teams of Tyrell Telecommunications Inc. possess ___ knowledge of many of the products put forth by the competition."}, "3222": {"1": "diagnose", "2": "shift", "3": "collapse", "4": "respond", "answer": "diagnose", "question": "Innovations in the electronic equipment used in hospitals have enabled doctors to ___ illnesses and disorders more quickly and more accurately."}, "3223": {"1": "compare", "2": "comparable", "3": "comparison", "4": "comparatively", "answer": "comparable", "question": "Mr. Corbett mentioned at last week's meeting the difference in finances this year compared to the ___ quarter last year."}, "3224": {"1": "So", "2": "Since", "3": "Despite", "4": "Unless", "answer": "Since", "question": "___ research has shown shifting trends in fashion, the marketing team is looking at new approaches in advertising."}, "3225": {"1": "rely", "2": "relying", "3": "reliance", "4": "reliant", "answer": "rely", "question": "Berwick Energy Corp. seeks to ___ on specialists in the fields with which the company is most concerned."}, "3226": {"1": "continuous", "2": "settled", "3": "rival", "4": "protective", "answer": "protective", "question": "As a ___ measure, Cordell Financial Fund does not disclose information about its clients unless legally mandated to do so."}, "3227": {"1": "relevance", "2": "connection", "3": "acquaintance", "4": "mixture", "answer": "connection", "question": "Since the ___ between some new advances in technology and efficiency is tenuous, a little more research is requested."}, "3228": {"1": "both", "2": "either", "3": "yet", "4": "where", "answer": "both", "question": "When you catch a cold, be sure to eat plenty of kiwis and oranges, as they are ___ known to be abundant in vitamin C."}, "3229": {"1": "originally", "2": "original", "3": "origins", "4": "origin", "answer": "originally", "question": "The board of directors' meeting was ___ scheduled for September 4, but due to an unexpected visit from an important guest, it was postponed."}, "3230": {"1": "pays", "2": "paid", "3": "payable", "4": "payments", "answer": "payments", "question": "Our store accepts not only major credit cards and checks but also online ___ via our website."}, "3231": {"1": "since", "2": "until", "3": "between", "4": "along", "answer": "until", "question": "Dr. Longman will be on a business trip to an academic seminar ___ next Thursday."}, "3232": {"1": "qualification", "2": "qualify", "3": "qualifier", "4": "qualified", "answer": "qualified", "question": "Nelly Graham is a ___ nurse who specializes in prenatal care."}, "3233": {"1": "importantly", "2": "quite", "3": "only", "4": "nearly", "answer": "only", "question": "Fiscal matters should ___ be handled by the accounting department."}, "3234": {"1": "ourselves", "2": "our", "3": "ours", "4": "us", "answer": "our", "question": "The local labor office approved of ___ improved working safety standards."}, "3235": {"1": "past", "2": "late", "3": "once", "4": "aged", "answer": "past", "question": "For the ___ three years, the Greys have been donating regularly to charities."}, "3236": {"1": "clarity", "2": "clear", "3": "clearest", "4": "clearly", "answer": "clearly", "question": "Having accumulated many prestigious awards in numerous debate contests, Jenny is ___ a skilled debater."}, "3237": {"1": "commute", "2": "commuting", "3": "be commuting", "4": "commuted", "answer": "commuting", "question": "The province has permitted the construction of a new underground railway for people ___ to the downtown area."}, "3238": {"1": "decisions", "2": "delays", "3": "options", "4": "contracts", "answer": "delays", "question": "We are sorry to inform our customers that because of an unexpected rainstorm, there will be at least five days' ___ in our shipments."}, "3239": {"1": "his", "2": "him", "3": "himself", "4": "his own", "answer": "himself", "question": "Because Mr. Jackson's secretary was on sick leave, he had to schedule every meeting ___ ."}, "3240": {"1": "facilitating", "2": "facilitator", "3": "facilitate", "4": "facility", "answer": "facility", "question": "The Alabama factory has become old and outdated, so management decided to modernize the ___ ."}, "3241": {"1": "required", "2": "expired", "3": "respected", "4": "emphasized", "answer": "required", "question": "Employees are ___ to submit a newly issued medical examination report to renew their employment insurance."}, "3242": {"1": "early", "2": "earlier", "3": "earliest", "4": "earliness", "answer": "earlier", "question": "Katherine had to leave work ___ than usual because her plans suddenly changed."}, "3243": {"1": "contents", "2": "calculations", "3": "items", "4": "measurements", "answer": "measurements", "question": "Please remember to record the ___ accurately to ensure perfect tailoring."}, "3244": {"1": "state", "2": "review", "3": "report", "4": "follow", "answer": "report", "question": "All members should ___ to the club president upon receiving their respective registration number to be recognized as a full member."}, "3245": {"1": "interest", "2": "interesting", "3": "interests", "4": "interested", "answer": "interested", "question": "Our company is currently recruiting interns ___ in marketing pharmaceutical products."}, "3246": {"1": "aims", "2": "marks", "3": "fulfills", "4": "states", "answer": "aims", "question": "Brown Bakery ___ to achieve at least a 30% increase in its sales profit with the launch of a new product."}, "3247": {"1": "gracefully", "2": "closely", "3": "somewhat", "4": "sooner", "answer": "somewhat", "question": "Ms. Mills was ___ frustrated to hear that her stocks had fallen significantly."}, "3248": {"1": "That", "2": "Those", "3": "Their", "4": "Them", "answer": "Those", "question": "___ who have exceeded their personal sales records this quarter will be given a bonus."}, "3249": {"1": "promptly", "2": "happily", "3": "doubtfully", "4": "specifically", "answer": "specifically", "question": "Wellington Beer's promotional event will focus ___ on its award-winning brewing methods."}, "3250": {"1": "explanations", "2": "efforts", "3": "responses", "4": "answers", "answer": "efforts", "question": "Hollycrest Middle School is rewarding Josephine Avery at the graduation ceremony for her ___ in helping improve the environment."}, "3251": {"1": "By", "2": "About", "3": "Of", "4": "Out", "answer": "Of", "question": "___ all fifteen overseas branches belonging to Summerton Automobiles, the one in India is doing best in terms of production."}, "3252": {"1": "includes", "2": "were included", "3": "including", "4": "included", "answer": "were included", "question": "The results of a comprehensive medical examination on the subjects of experiment  ___ in the package sent to Dr. Dalton."}, "3253": {"1": "of", "2": "if", "3": "about", "4": "with", "answer": "if", "question": "Regular check-ups, ___ conducted by a qualified dentist, will ensure good oral hygiene."}, "3254": {"1": "necessary", "2": "necessity", "3": "necessarily", "4": "necessitate", "answer": "necessary", "question": "The Department of Treasury thinks it ___ to closely inspect the financial reports of banks to prevent further deterioration of the economy."}, "3255": {"1": "preventable", "2": "legible", "3": "defective", "4": "avoidable", "answer": "defective", "question": "The automated quality assurance system at Herrick Printers screens out ___ products in its manufacturing process to ensure  customer satisfaction."}, "3256": {"1": "which", "2": "then", "3": "there", "4": "what", "answer": "which", "question": "Antrix Cosmetics has announced that it will merge with Europe's largest cosmetic firm, Beau & Chic, ___ will change both companies' marketing strategies."}, "3257": {"1": "at", "2": "in", "3": "about", "4": "of", "answer": "in", "question": "Viva la Diva was voted the most popular perfume by teenagers ___ a recent survey conducted by Galaxy Publishers."}, "3258": {"1": "holding", "2": "hold", "3": "will hold", "4": "be held", "answer": "will hold", "question": "Aetna news agency ___ a charity ball to raise funds for its ongoing \"Save the Children\" campaign."}, "3259": {"1": "In addition", "2": "As soon as", "3": "Compared", "4": "Furthermore", "answer": "In addition", "question": "___ to providing home care service to the physically handicapped, the local public health center holds annual campaigns on raising public awareness on the rights of the disabled."}, "3260": {"1": "confidences", "2": "confidential", "3": "confidentiality", "4": "confidentially", "answer": "confidentiality", "question": "Regulations at J&P Computers stipulate that all employees put documents related to product prototypes into paper shredders to ensure the ___ of products in development."}, "3261": {"1": "implements", "2": "had implemented", "3": "to implement", "4": "will be implemented", "answer": "will be implemented", "question": "The traffic policy formulated by the city council to relieve traffic jams in the commercial district ___ as planned next month."}, "3262": {"1": "Whether", "2": "As soon as", "3": "Considering", "4": "Regarding", "answer": "Whether", "question": "___ Senator Levin will join the newly formed political party or not is a hot topic enthusiastically debated among politicians."}, "3263": {"1": "sought", "2": "forwarded", "3": "kept", "4": "located", "answer": "forwarded", "question": "Upon requesting a credit score, your results will be ___ to the institutions you have selected as recipients."}, "3264": {"1": "In case of", "2": "Resulting in", "3": "According to", "4": "Away from", "answer": "According to", "question": "___ a report published by the province, 3% of businesses are suffering from severe financial difficulties."}, "3265": {"1": "responsible", "2": "profitable", "3": "replaceable", "4": "accessible", "answer": "accessible", "question": "Personal medical records are securely protected and ___ only to individuals with matching identification."}, "3266": {"1": "when", "2": "even", "3": "therefore", "4": "seldom", "answer": "when", "question": "Employees at Karma Airlines went on an all-out strike ___ they were notified of impending layoffs."}, "3267": {"1": "affirmation", "2": "feasibility", "3": "prediction", "4": "anticipation", "answer": "feasibility", "question": "The organizing committee of this year's conference is examining the ___ of renting a large-sized sports arena."}, "3268": {"1": "our", "2": "ours", "3": "us", "4": "ourselves", "answer": "our", "question": "To fulfill our customers' needs and to increase ___ product quality we've bought a new cutting device."}, "3269": {"1": "admission", "2": "permission", "3": "commission", "4": "intermission", "answer": "permission", "question": "The CBC has new guidelines that require each employee to get a supervisor's ___ before ordering any office supplies."}, "3270": {"1": "impress", "2": "impressive", "3": "impressively", "4": "impressed", "answer": "impressive", "question": "As the largest dealer in the state, Auto Fair maintains an ___ inventory of new vehicles for immediate delivery."}, "3271": {"1": "promotion", "2": "promotes", "3": "promoted", "4": "promoting", "answer": "promotion", "question": "Ami Natashi not only remained but received a ___ just two weeks after the company reduced its staff by 10 percent."}, "3272": {"1": "either", "2": "neither", "3": "both", "4": "not only", "answer": "either", "question": "The boarding pass is available from ___ the check-in counter or the selfservice machines."}, "3273": {"1": "welcome", "2": "welcomed", "3": "will welcome", "4": "has welcomed", "answer": "welcomed", "question": "In addition, the branch offices in Washington and Atlanta ___ new interns last week."}, "3274": {"1": "greater", "2": "greatly", "3": "more greatly", "4": "as great as", "answer": "greater", "question": "Unilever Inc. has announced a new strategy that places ___ emphasis on customer satisfaction and product quality."}, "3275": {"1": "circumstances", "2": "instructions", "3": "evidence", "4": "confirmation", "answer": "instructions", "question": "Be sure to read and follow all the ___ contained in the manual and keep it in a safe place for future reference."}, "3276": {"1": "he", "2": "him", "3": "himself", "4": "his", "answer": "himself", "question": "From winning an Olympic gold medal in  to becoming an NBA champion in , Kevin Garnett has shown ___ to be one of the most talented players."}, "3277": {"1": "like", "2": "with", "3": "than", "4": "to", "answer": "to", "question": "Mr. Ken, your customer service representative was very helpful in getting the best price for shipping my packages ___ Europe."}, "3278": {"1": "soon", "2": "still", "3": "later", "4": "once", "answer": "still", "question": "After 50 years in business, Quick Star Shipping ___ tries to provide on-time delivery service, which its customers can rely on."}, "3279": {"1": "So that", "2": "As", "3": "Besides", "4": "Due to", "answer": "As", "question": "___ the holiday shopping season approaches, police ask shoppers to avoid leaving valuable items in vehicles."}, "3280": {"1": "responsibly", "2": "responsible", "3": "responsibility", "4": "responsibilities", "answer": "responsibility", "question": "DSC believes that we have a ___ to our customers, to the communities where we work and where we do business."}, "3281": {"1": "set up", "2": "taken to", "3": "given out", "4": "put down", "answer": "set up", "question": "The new turbines of GE Energy are scheduled to be ___ and commissioned between April and December next year."}, "3282": {"1": "which", "2": "where", "3": "how", "4": "what", "answer": "what", "question": "This section of the handbook explains ___ you should do if there is an emergency with your water, gas or electricity supply."}, "3283": {"1": "probable", "2": "mutual", "3": "related", "4": "frequent", "answer": "related", "question": "To be considered for the position of marketing director, applicants must be creative and dynamic with a university degree in marketing or a ___ field."}, "3284": {"1": "confirm", "2": "confirmed", "3": "confirming", "4": "confirmation", "answer": "confirming", "question": "Samsun Electronics has plans to launch 10 mobile phones in , ___ its plans to expand in the European market more aggressively."}, "3285": {"1": "sooner", "2": "often", "3": "still", "4": "greater", "answer": "sooner", "question": "The coffee mugs given as gifts for those who donated $ or more to the Winter Fundraising Drive will be shipped early next week or perhaps ___ ."}, "3286": {"1": "photographs", "2": "photography", "3": "photographic", "4": "photographers", "answer": "photographers", "question": "This booklet introduces you to a compact digital SLR camera, which is ideal for beginning ___ and amateurs."}, "3287": {"1": "book", "2": "visit", "3": "escort", "4": "reserve", "answer": "escort", "question": "The Bridge Cinema De Lux has ushers who will ___ patrons to their seats if necessary."}, "3288": {"1": "moderate", "2": "moderator", "3": "moderating", "4": "moderately", "answer": "moderately", "question": "Efforts to sell government-owned corporations have been ___ successful so far, and the privatization effort is moving ahead."}, "3289": {"1": "constructive", "2": "eager", "3": "relative", "4": "delicious", "answer": "eager", "question": "There are many small Indian companies, with potential, which are ___ to form partnerships with U.S. firms to jointly develop advanced technologies."}, "3290": {"1": "prone", "2": "vital", "3": "poised", "4": "ready", "answer": "vital", "question": "It is ___ that each department work closely with the MIS department, which coordinates all corporate data."}, "3291": {"1": "out of", "2": "because of", "3": "as to", "4": "up to", "answer": "as to", "question": "The FDA reviews the preclinical research data and then makes a decision ___ whether to allow the clinical trials to proceed."}, "3292": {"1": "reserving", "2": "reservations", "3": "reserve", "4": "reserved", "answer": "reservations", "question": "The Silo House Restaurant will also be open this weekend, but anyone wanting to eat there should make ___ to ensure a seat."}, "3293": {"1": "availability", "2": "exercise", "3": "donation", "4": "access", "answer": "access", "question": "Residents of the city have ___ to the nearby mountains, creeks and beaches, as well as a wide range of educational and cultural facilities."}, "3294": {"1": "scheduling", "2": "scheduler", "3": "scheduled", "4": "schedule", "answer": "scheduled", "question": "If, for any reason, you are not going to make your ___ travel plans, please call us at ."}, "3295": {"1": "readily", "2": "accurately", "3": "eagerly", "4": "particularly", "answer": "particularly", "question": "Wherever possible, avoid taking sleeping pills, which must only be used in ___ stressful situations or in connection with psychological or physical illnesses."}, "3296": {"1": "recommendation", "2": "recommended", "3": "recommend", "4": "recommending", "answer": "recommended", "question": "Because of his outstanding work, Mr. Tianfu Yang has been highly ___ for the position of marketing director by the board of directors."}, "3297": {"1": "was sending", "2": "would send", "3": "will be sent", "4": "was sent", "answer": "was sent", "question": "Mr. Lim, the head of the union, ___ a letter last week that stated his contract with the company was terminated."}, "3298": {"1": "directed", "2": "presented", "3": "belated", "4": "postponed", "answer": "postponed", "question": "Because of the impending storm, the second meeting of the Christopher Dawson Society will be ___ until next Tuesday."}, "3299": {"1": "relation", "2": "preparation", "3": "transformation", "4": "concentration", "answer": "concentration", "question": "The area surrounding the Lachine Canal in Montreal has the highest ___ of industrial buildings in the country."}, "3300": {"1": "In addition to", "2": "On the other hand", "3": "At the time", "4": "Despite", "answer": "At the time", "question": "___ the Pinquip Company was founded, many political changes were taking place in the Philippines."}, "3301": {"1": "upcoming", "2": "available", "3": "frequent", "4": "following", "answer": "following", "question": "We ordered the new office equipment on Tuesday, but it was not delivered until the ___ Saturday."}, "3302": {"1": "during", "2": "about", "3": "how", "4": "whom", "answer": "how", "question": "If you would like to see ___ our products are made, we are happy to show you around our factory."}, "3303": {"1": "Despite", "2": "Aside", "3": "Unlike", "4": "Except", "answer": "Unlike", "question": "___ other equipment manufacturers, Orange Line provides unparalleled service and support through our teams who provide quick response services and repairs."}, "3304": {"1": "will choose", "2": "was choosing", "3": "choose", "4": "has chosen", "answer": "will choose", "question": "After all entries have been submitted, a panel of independent judges ___ the winning slogan based on originality."}, "3305": {"1": "useful", "2": "cooperative", "3": "exact", "4": "capable", "answer": "useful", "question": "The seminar was especially ___ for newly-appointed managers since it provided a number of essential guidelines and strategies."}, "3306": {"1": "safely", "2": "safe", "3": "safeties", "4": "safety", "answer": "safety", "question": "Mr. Sasaki in the personnel department has advised employees to become more familiar with company ___ regulations."}, "3307": {"1": "as", "2": "greatly", "3": "for", "4": "when", "answer": "for", "question": "The system is currently under redevelopment and will be unavailable ___ the next few weeks."}, "3308": {"1": "constructs", "2": "constructive", "3": "constructed", "4": "construction", "answer": "construction", "question": "The train bound for Crawford will be suspended for three days to complete minor ___ on its rails."}, "3309": {"1": "announcing", "2": "announces", "3": "announced", "4": "have announced", "answer": "announced", "question": "Rosebush Stationery ___ yesterday that it is anticipating at least a twenty percent growth in revenue with the launch of a new product line related to printing."}, "3310": {"1": "on", "2": "at", "3": "below", "4": "by", "answer": "at", "question": "The data Mr. Warren requested can be found ___ the Deleon Research Institute."}, "3311": {"1": "attracts", "2": "attracting", "3": "attractive", "4": "attraction", "answer": "attractive", "question": "Denver is a famous tourist destination and renowned for its cuisine and ___ scenery."}, "3312": {"1": "participate", "2": "attend", "3": "perform", "4": "admit", "answer": "attend", "question": "All students are encouraged to ___ the Halloween dance organized by the student council."}, "3313": {"1": "regularity", "2": "regularize", "3": "regularities", "4": "regularly", "answer": "regularly", "question": "Employees at Alembic Broadcasting ___ donate to local charities by hosting fundraising parties."}, "3314": {"1": "as well as", "2": "as soon as", "3": "compared to", "4": "both", "answer": "both", "question": "You are to submit ___ your medical records and registration form to the administrative office."}, "3315": {"1": "as", "2": "in", "3": "at", "4": "among", "answer": "as", "question": "The Cahoon Daily is as widely read ___ The Cahoon Gazette in New Jersey."}, "3316": {"1": "they", "2": "them", "3": "theirs", "4": "their", "answer": "their", "question": "Blanchard's cars are popular among young people for ___ unique design."}, "3317": {"1": "demonstrated", "2": "entrusted", "3": "selected", "4": "participated", "answer": "entrusted", "question": "Boyden Investment's marketing director ___ some of his employees with the task of surveying potential clients."}, "3318": {"1": "no one", "2": "another", "3": "anyone", "4": "everyone", "answer": "everyone", "question": "When the alarm rings in the hallway during a fire drill, ___ must evacuate according to the guidelines previously instructed."}, "3319": {"1": "specific", "2": "occupied", "3": "predictable", "4": "accountable", "answer": "specific", "question": "Consumers should check the ___ instructions printed on the product before using it."}, "3320": {"1": "expects", "2": "expectation", "3": "expected", "4": "expectant", "answer": "expects", "question": "The Bank of Gough ___ that house prices will decrease with the increased supply of apartments."}, "3321": {"1": "at", "2": "by", "3": "across", "4": "during", "answer": "across", "question": "Printers & Technology collects and publishes information on the latest printing equipment from companies ___ North America."}, "3322": {"1": "effective", "2": "effect", "3": "effectiveness", "4": "effectively", "answer": "effectively", "question": "The organizing committee decided to allocate specific tasks to members to achieve its goals more ___ ."}, "3323": {"1": "record", "2": "qualification", "3": "regulation", "4": "instruction", "answer": "record", "question": "All employees must keep a/an ___ of expenses made on business trips and report them back to the administration section."}, "3324": {"1": "competitions", "2": "competitive", "3": "compete", "4": "competitively", "answer": "competitive", "question": "Because this year's prize money is larger than that of last year's, the contest has become more ___ ."}, "3325": {"1": "remind", "2": "locate", "3": "guide", "4": "advance", "answer": "locate", "question": "The tourist information center helps travelers easily ___ famous landmarks."}, "3326": {"1": "producer", "2": "producing", "3": "product", "4": "produced", "answer": "product", "question": "The new medicine developed by Crawson is the ___ of accumulated experience and hard work."}, "3327": {"1": "approximately", "2": "enthusiastically", "3": "rigidly", "4": "frequently", "answer": "frequently", "question": "Because of the decrepit facilities, Tarara's factories ___ experience blackouts."}, "3328": {"1": "optimal", "2": "optimizing", "3": "optimize", "4": "optimally", "answer": "optimal", "question": "For ___ results, please be sure to follow the instructions written on the back of the product."}, "3329": {"1": "creativity", "2": "record", "3": "exhibition", "4": "appointment", "answer": "exhibition", "question": "Mansfield Art Gallery is hosting a special ___ dedicated to the late Craig Perkins, who painted with great precision and vivid colors."}, "3330": {"1": "high", "2": "higher", "3": "highest", "4": "highly", "answer": "highly", "question": "The police performed a thorough examination, as the suspect's alibi was ___ suspect."}, "3331": {"1": "among", "2": "usually", "3": "without", "4": "already", "answer": "without", "question": "Students who submit field trip permission forms ___ a parent or guardian's signature will be excluded for the trip."}, "3332": {"1": "advancement", "2": "openings", "3": "vacancy", "4": "challenges", "answer": "advancement", "question": "The personnel department is currently considering three people from the marketing team for ___ to managerial positions."}, "3333": {"1": "ahead", "2": "optimal", "3": "forward", "4": "initial", "answer": "initial", "question": "The ___ findings from the experiment seemed to confirm the hypothesis that the drug was effective, but later results proved otherwise."}, "3334": {"1": "boldest", "2": "bolder", "3": "bold", "4": "boldly", "answer": "bolder", "question": "The new president of Wiota Computers is employing much ___ approaches to forming strategic partnerships with other companies than her predecessor."}, "3335": {"1": "which", "2": "until", "3": "despite", "4": "if", "answer": "if", "question": "All employees are encouraged to notify the personnel department ___ they feel that they have been discriminated against by anyone else."}, "3336": {"1": "allow", "2": "prevent", "3": "provide", "4": "show", "answer": "allow", "question": "Installing this software on your computer will ___ you to operate other computers by remote control."}, "3337": {"1": "exit", "2": "exited", "3": "exiting", "4": "exits", "answer": "exiting", "question": "Please be reminded that you need to save important files in your individual folder before ___ the office."}, "3338": {"1": "opportunity", "2": "contract", "3": "destination", "4": "analysis", "answer": "analysis", "question": "An accurate ___ of surveys is imperative to building a good understanding of customer needs."}, "3339": {"1": "immediately", "2": "extensively", "3": "eventually", "4": "immensely", "answer": "extensively", "question": "Weidman Real Estate has recently completed an ___ detailed report on housing trends over the last ten years."}, "3340": {"1": "to honor", "2": "in honor", "3": "honoring", "4": "honor", "answer": "in honor", "question": "The Herrick Community Library decided to open a computer lab for public use ___ of Christina Eaton, who has served as a librarian there for more than 50 years."}, "3341": {"1": "until", "2": "due to", "3": "ahead of", "4": "despite", "answer": "ahead of", "question": "Some artifacts excavated in Asia are known to have been invented several hundred years ___ similar ones in the West."}, "3342": {"1": "unfamiliar", "2": "difficult", "3": "completed", "4": "lucrative", "answer": "unfamiliar", "question": "Many people answered that they were ___ with the use of electronic books on their questionnaires."}, "3343": {"1": "enthused", "2": "enthusiasts", "3": "enthusiastic", "4": "enthusiastically", "answer": "enthusiasts", "question": "Longwood Travel Agency is offering a special tour package filled with hiking courses in the northern area of Winn National Park for ___ of hiking."}, "3344": {"1": "consideration", "2": "being considered", "3": "considering", "4": "consider", "answer": "being considered", "question": "Mr. Homes suggested that we request reference letters from applicants ___ for the new position."}, "3345": {"1": "Because", "2": "In regard to", "3": "In the order of", "4": "In order to", "answer": "In order to", "question": "___ increase the productivity of the Winnipeg factory, management decided to implement a new manufacturing process."}, "3346": {"1": "what", "2": "then", "3": "whereas", "4": "despite", "answer": "whereas", "question": "Summerton Computers exceeded their sales quota this quarter, ___ Denver Electronics' sales profit dropped by more than 15 percent."}, "3347": {"1": "revision", "2": "model", "3": "hotel", "4": "market", "answer": "market", "question": "Many economic studies predicted that a robust ___ will appear for environmentallyfriendly products within the next 10 years."}, "3348": {"1": "if", "2": "but", "3": "so", "4": "or", "answer": "or", "question": "We seek to hire employees who either have experience in the field ___ have completed an HVAC training course at an approved institution."}, "3349": {"1": "consent", "2": "increase", "3": "participate", "4": "persuade", "answer": "increase", "question": "The drive to lower costs and ___ productivity on production lines is universal throughout the automotive industry."}, "3350": {"1": "evens", "2": "evenly", "3": "evened", "4": "evenness", "answer": "evenly", "question": "Hyde Paints claims that with their new roller you will be able to spread paint more ___ , paint faster, and work more effectively."}, "3351": {"1": "their", "2": "them", "3": "theirs", "4": "they", "answer": "them", "question": "Until Mr. Mato and Mrs. Kaori moved to the newly renovated offices on the second floor, both of ___ used temporary office space."}, "3352": {"1": "about", "2": "as", "3": "like", "4": "out", "answer": "as", "question": "Ms. Linda is scheduled to replace Mr. Kay ___ factory manager at the end of the year."}, "3353": {"1": "elegance", "2": "elegantly", "3": "elegant", "4": "more elegantly", "answer": "elegant", "question": "All rooms at the hotel have been designed in a classical style that is both ___ and comfortable."}, "3354": {"1": "convenient", "2": "steady", "3": "pleased", "4": "creative", "answer": "pleased", "question": "The instructor was ___ to receive a positive response from the participants at the end of the course when they were asked their opinions of the overall quality and structure of the training."}, "3355": {"1": "responsible", "2": "responsibly", "3": "responsibility", "4": "responsibilities", "answer": "responsibilities", "question": "One of the ___ of the Parking Division of the Transportation Department is to enforce the state and municipal parking regulations."}, "3356": {"1": "longer", "2": "sooner", "3": "fewer", "4": "further", "answer": "further", "question": "After the company implemented the cleanup of the polluted river, the city government decided that no ___ penalty was necessary."}, "3357": {"1": "serving", "2": "served", "3": "server", "4": "serves", "answer": "serving", "question": "AAS Executive Transportation is a premier limousine company ___ the Houston metropolitan area."}, "3358": {"1": "they ", "2": "their", "3": "their own", "4": "themselves", "answer": "their own", "question": ". The successful candidate will be able to work effectively on ___ and as part of a team."}, "3359": {"1": "validate", "2": "validity", "3": "valid", "4": "validates", "answer": "valid", "question": "For the agreement to be ___ , it is necessary to have a written document which explicitly lays down the terms."}, "3360": {"1": "notice", "2": "noticing", "3": "noticeable", "4": "noticeably", "answer": "noticeably", "question": "Alabama's death rate from all alcoholrelated causes has increased ___ since  and is now 23 percent higher than the U.S. average rate."}, "3361": {"1": "valuably", "2": "valuable", "3": "valuing", "4": "value", "answer": "valuable", "question": "Since he joined our company in , Mr. Ogawa has proven himself to be a very ___ employee."}, "3362": {"1": "renovates", "2": "integrates", "3": "collaborates", "4": "translates", "answer": "integrates", "question": "Dr. Takahashi is also an active researcher who ___ the latest advances into his patients' treatments."}, "3363": {"1": "actual", "2": "punctual", "3": "mutual", "4": "crucial", "answer": "mutual", "question": "In , Mr. Haist and Ms. White dissolved their partnership by ___ consent and Ms. White became a sole owner."}, "3364": {"1": "is delivered", "2": "delivery", "3": "is delivering", "4": "delivered", "answer": "is delivered", "question": "Please submit the proposal according to the instructions provided and make sure it ___ before the submission deadline."}, "3365": {"1": "adjustment", "2": "provision", "3": "change", "4": "priority", "answer": "priority", "question": "As a leader in the area of computer security, IBM has made security standards the highest ___ since its inception."}, "3366": {"1": "between", "2": "whether", "3": "except", "4": "when", "answer": "between", "question": "Normally a person will regain consciousness ___ four and five days after a car accident."}, "3367": {"1": "to invite", "2": "invitation", "3": "invitingly", "4": "invited", "answer": "to invite", "question": "Healthy Workplace Club would like ___ all employees, along with their families, to participate in the event this June."}, "3368": {"1": "After", "2": "Since", "3": "Despite", "4": "Therefore", "answer": "Since", "question": "___ the copy shop is located in the office building, it attracts many office workers."}, "3369": {"1": "rotating", "2": "rotates", "3": "rotations", "4": "rotate", "answer": "rotating", "question": "In accordance with the municipal act, two members of the city council are appointed on a ___ basis for a oneyear term."}, "3370": {"1": "inwardly", "2": "promptly", "3": "highly", "4": "extremely", "answer": "promptly", "question": "Sending a letter of apology ___ after a customer complaint is a highly recommended practice."}, "3371": {"1": "known", "2": "knowing", "3": "knew", "4": "knows", "answer": "known", "question": "The Korean Association of the Auto Industry, also ___ as KAAI, publishes a quarterly technical magazine."}, "3372": {"1": "informing", "2": "telling", "3": "applying", "4": "filing", "answer": "filing", "question": "If you have any questions about the regulations for ___ taxes with the federal government, please contact your accountant first."}, "3373": {"1": "late", "2": "current", "3": "closed", "4": "direct", "answer": "current", "question": "All sales reports for the ___ year must be submitted by January 31 of the following year."}, "3374": {"1": "increasing", "2": "increases", "3": "increased", "4": "increasingly", "answer": "increasing", "question": "Mr. Zhou is our general engineer who is responsible for ___ productivity of the factory, developing new products and solving the problems occurring during production."}, "3375": {"1": "out of", "2": "except for", "3": "as to", "4": "instead of", "answer": "instead of", "question": "Most students have logged in to check their grades immediately via the website ___ waiting for written notification."}, "3376": {"1": "irritation", "2": "outbreak", "3": "controversy", "4": "disruption", "answer": "disruption", "question": "Please accept our sincere apologies for the recent ___ in telecom services in some parts of the country."}, "3377": {"1": "more", "2": "many", "3": "good", "4": "much", "answer": "more", "question": "In addition, DRS has been redesigning its website to make it ___ consumerfriendly and useful."}, "3378": {"1": "diverse", "2": "diversity", "3": "diversely", "4": "diversify", "answer": "diverse", "question": "Elizabeth Farnsworth will lead a discussion with a ___ group of voters in Denver on their views of the upcoming presidential election."}, "3379": {"1": "in order to", "2": "according to", "3": "similar", "4": "allowing", "answer": "according to", "question": "Natural Resources Canada provides a comprehensive list of vehicles ranked ___ their fuel efficiency."}, "3380": {"1": "productive", "2": "eventual", "3": "informative", "4": "absolute", "answer": "absolute", "question": "We have ___ confidence in the product's ability to provide unrivaled protection in an exposed blast environment."}, "3381": {"1": "happiness", "2": "effectiveness", "3": "prosperity", "4": "satisfaction", "answer": "effectiveness", "question": "Although a number of studies have been conducted to examine the ___ of the anti drink-driving campaign, no consistent conclusion could be drawn."}, "3382": {"1": "than", "2": "whereas", "3": "whether", "4": "such", "answer": "whether", "question": "Please let our sales representative know ___ you would prefer to receive your order by mail or courier if you need to get it earlier."}, "3383": {"1": "foundation", "2": "founder", "3": "found", "4": "founded", "answer": "founder", "question": "Under ___ and chief executive officer Chip Mason, Legg Mason has acquired many successful fund management firms and usually operates them independently."}, "3384": {"1": "quite", "2": "often", "3": "any", "4": "few", "answer": "few", "question": "Flat-panel LCD and plasma TVs have been highly reliable products that require ___ repairs during the first three years."}, "3385": {"1": "publicly", "2": "publicize", "3": "public", "4": "publicized", "answer": "public", "question": "The details of the project will be made ___ as soon as the final version has been agreed upon by the board."}, "3386": {"1": "individually", "2": "reservedly", "3": "positively", "4": "approximately", "answer": "individually", "question": "All chocolate-covered apples are ___ wrapped and the entire gift basket is wrapped in a cellophane bag to ensure freshness during shipping."}, "3387": {"1": "belongings", "2": "advances", "3": "commitments", "4": "inspections", "answer": "advances", "question": "Thanks to the widespread ___ in production techniques, it has been possible for our plant in China to produce more durable trucks."}, "3388": {"1": "next", "2": "always", "3": "soon", "4": "like", "answer": "next", "question": "Departmental restructuring will be discussed at the ___ monthly meeting."}, "3389": {"1": "our", "2": "we", "3": "US", "4": "ours", "answer": "our", "question": "To keep ___ park beautiful, please place your nonrecyclables in the available trash cans."}, "3390": {"1": "informed", "2": "asked", "3": "advised", "4": "requested", "answer": "requested", "question": "Mr. Hardin ___ additional images of the office building he is interested in leasing."}, "3391": {"1": "because", "2": "either", "3": "between", "4": "together", "answer": "together", "question": "A team of agricultural experts will be brought ___ to try to improve crop harvests."}, "3392": {"1": "named", "2": "granted", "3": "founded", "4": "proved", "answer": "named", "question": "The board of Galaxipharm ___ Mr. Kwon's successor at yesterday's meeting."}, "3393": {"1": "replacement", "2": "replacing", "3": "replace", "4": "replaces", "answer": "replacement", "question": "If your parking permit is damaged, bring it to the entrance station for a ___ ."}, "3394": {"1": "rather than", "2": "in case", "3": "such as", "4": "unless", "answer": "in case", "question": "Mr. Ahmad decided to reserve a private room for the awards dinner ___ the restaurant was noisy."}, "3395": {"1": "conserve", "2": "conserves", "3": "conservative", "4": "conservatively", "answer": "conservative", "question": "Ms. Jones has provided a ___ estimate of the costs of expanding distribution statewide."}, "3396": {"1": "compact", "2": "wealthy", "3": "faithful", "4": "realistic", "answer": "realistic", "question": "Each quarter, Acaba Exports sets ___ sales goals for its staff."}, "3397": {"1": "notify", "2": "notification", "3": "notifying", "4": "notifies", "answer": "notification", "question": "Ms. Garcia was delighted to receive ___ that her company soon will be featured in the In Town Times magazine."}, "3398": {"1": "over", "2": "down", "3": "for", "4": "out", "answer": "for", "question": "Children under five years of age are eligible ___ free vision tests."}, "3399": {"1": "caution", "2": "cautiously", "3": "cautious", "4": "cautiousness", "answer": "cautiously", "question": "Drivers on the Parian Expressway are reminded to drive ___ throughout July because of the ongoing construction work."}, "3400": {"1": "that", "2": "once", "3": "as well", "4": "then", "answer": "once", "question": "The committee will resume its weekly meetings ___ Ms. Cheon returns from Scotland on September 17."}, "3401": {"1": "proposed", "2": "proposing", "3": "proposal", "4": "propose", "answer": "proposed", "question": "The ___ initiative aims to provide public transportation for commuters living in the outer suburbs."}, "3402": {"1": "annually", "2": "anytime", "3": "whenever", "4": "temporarily", "answer": "temporarily", "question": "Yesterday's storm ___ interrupted the services of the Duddula, Inc., satellite communications system."}, "3403": {"1": "several", "2": "everybody", "3": "some", "4": "both", "answer": "both", "question": "Even though Cabrera Pictures and Marcella Images make very different films, ___ are successful movie studios."}, "3404": {"1": "Reputation", "2": "Foundation", "3": "Delegation", "4": "Permission", "answer": "Delegation", "question": "___ of tasks can make a manager's job easier and help other employees learn new skills."}, "3405": {"1": "divisions", "2": "dividing", "3": "divide", "4": "divided", "answer": "divided", "question": "Proceeds from the sale of Delcrest Corporation were equally ___ among the founder's three daughters."}, "3406": {"1": "Throughout", "2": "Except for", "3": "Despite", "4": "Prior to", "answer": "Despite", "question": "___ higher than average ticket prices, every performance of Aiden North's new play is sold out for the next six months."}, "3407": {"1": "respect", "2": "respects", "3": "respectfully", "4": "respected", "answer": "respectfully", "question": "Ricardo Sosa, the executive chef at Restaurant Ninal, responds to guests' suggestions ___ ."}, "3408": {"1": "scope", "2": "turn", "3": "grip", "4": "drive", "answer": "scope", "question": "Mr. Koster is negotiating the ___ of the new contract with Arban, Inc."}, "3409": {"1": "may find", "2": "can be found", "3": "have found", "4": "have to find", "answer": "can be found", "question": "The equipment-use guidelines ___ on our internal corporate Web site."}, "3410": {"1": "dominantly", "2": "precisely", "3": "relatively", "4": "widely", "answer": "precisely", "question": "Professor Han created spreadsheets to calculate the farm's irrigation needs ___ ."}, "3411": {"1": "reasonable", "2": "appropriate", "3": "equivalent", "4": "significant", "answer": "equivalent", "question": "For hiring purposes, five years of professional experience is ___ to having achieved certification."}, "3412": {"1": "light", "2": "lighten", "3": "lightly", "4": "lightening", "answer": "lightening", "question": "South Regent Aviation is adopting measures to reduce fuel expenses by ___ cargo loads."}, "3413": {"1": "Perhaps", "2": "Outside", "3": "Every", "4": "While", "answer": "Perhaps", "question": "___ the most challenging aspect of accepting a new position is negotiating a salary that is both fair and satisfying."}, "3414": {"1": "standards", "2": "features", "3": "risks", "4": "institutions", "answer": "standards", "question": "Complaints about its new line of kitchen appliances led Loxevo, Inc., to adopt higher ___ for assessing quality."}, "3415": {"1": "economy", "2": "economics", "3": "economically", "4": "economical", "answer": "economical", "question": "The chief engineer noted that constructing another bridge would be more ___ than repairing the existing structure."}, "3416": {"1": "in addition to", "2": "according to", "3": "inside", "4": "within", "answer": "in addition to", "question": "Jansen Bus Company drivers are expected to complete regular trainings ___ maintaining their state licenses."}, "3417": {"1": "to have urged", "2": "had urged", "3": "will have urged", "4": "was urged", "answer": "had urged", "question": "Ms. DeSoto ___ all employees to come to last week's budget meeting even though only officers were obligated to attend."}, "3418": {"1": "theirs", "2": "ours", "3": "our", "4": "they", "answer": "our", "question": "The new interns have been very mindful of ___ parking regulations."}, "3419": {"1": "informative", "2": "primary", "3": "enthusiastic", "4": "financial", "answer": "informative", "question": "To help the arts center improve its programming, please indicate which aspect of the workshop was most ___ ."}, "3420": {"1": "beneficial", "2": "benefits", "3": "benefited", "4": "benefiting", "answer": "benefits", "question": "Mr. Gupta explained the of ___ the upgraded customer database to the sales team."}, "3421": {"1": "on", "2": "out", "3": "from", "4": "until", "answer": "on", "question": "Buses leaving the city terminal were delayed due to icy conditions ___ the roads."}, "3422": {"1": "purchased", "2": "purchase", "3": "purchasing", "4": "to purchase", "answer": "purchased", "question": "If you have recently ___ a digital camera and want to learn how to use it, this course is for you."}, "3423": {"1": "performance", "2": "supplement", "3": "deadline", "4": "renovation", "answer": "renovation", "question": "The upcoming ___ of Tantino Airport will ease congestion and modernize guest accommodations."}, "3424": {"1": "frequently", "2": "frequent", "3": "more frequently", "4": "frequency", "answer": "more frequently", "question": "The study showed that customers aged 35 to 44 paid with a Sonoka credit card ___ than customers in any other age-group."}, "3425": {"1": "donate", "2": "request", "3": "confess", "4": "submit", "answer": "submit", "question": "You need to ___ a business plan before your loan application can be processed."}, "3426": {"1": "compliments", "2": "complimentary", "3": "compliment", "4": "complimenting", "answer": "complimentary", "question": "The hotel's ___ shuttle bus will take guests to Hong Kong's major landmarks."}, "3427": {"1": "Besides", "2": "After", "3": "Still", "4": "For", "answer": "After", "question": "___ months of work to sell the Apton Building, the realtor finally succeeded last week."}, "3428": {"1": "some", "2": "one", "3": "others", "4": "either", "answer": "one", "question": "We will review all four custodial-service bids and choose ___ that suits our needs."}, "3429": {"1": "standards", "2": "drawings", "3": "revisions", "4": "duplications", "answer": "revisions", "question": "The client asked for ___ to the images in the advertising text."}, "3430": {"1": "that", "2": "of", "3": "whether", "4": "between", "answer": "that", "question": "Please be advised ___ we have had to cancel your order because of a difficulty with our shipping agent."}, "3431": {"1": "obtains", "2": "competes", "3": "inquires", "4": "claims", "answer": "claims", "question": "Tin Creek Corporation ___ that its paper towels are the most absorbent on the market."}, "3432": {"1": "agreed", "2": "agreement", "3": "agreeable", "4": "agreeing", "answer": "agreement", "question": "KCLN Associates will enter into a business ___ with the contractor as soon as some of the terms are renegotiated."}, "3433": {"1": "Although", "2": "Instead", "3": "Regardless", "4": "Despite", "answer": "Although", "question": "___ registering for online banking is not required, we strongly recommend it to all of our customers."}, "3434": {"1": "related", "2": "relatable", "3": "relating", "4": "relate", "answer": "relate", "question": "Viewers can easily ___ to the main character in the popular television series Autumn Mystery."}, "3435": {"1": "center", "2": "surplus", "3": "range", "4": "type", "answer": "range", "question": "Fairlawn Medical Clinic offers a full ___ of services as part of its community wellness programs."}, "3436": {"1": "accessible", "2": "accessing", "3": "access", "4": "accesses", "answer": "accessible", "question": "The rear entrance to RC Bank will be closed for repairs and not ___ next Monday."}, "3437": {"1": "decidedly", "2": "furthermore", "3": "rather", "4": "everywhere", "answer": "everywhere", "question": "Mr. Carson wants to see Carson audio products ___ , even in remote regions of the world."}, "3438": {"1": "equip", "2": "equipping", "3": "equipment", "4": "equipped", "answer": "equipment", "question": "We can buy office ___ such as desks and printers from any of our company's approved vendors."}, "3439": {"1": "assembled", "2": "listed", "3": "addressed", "4": "earned", "answer": "listed", "question": "When taking a book order, agents must record the customer's name and the ___ price of each item."}, "3440": {"1": "with", "2": "these", "3": "once", "4": "just", "answer": "once", "question": "The building will be furnished ___ the supervisors do their inspection."}, "3441": {"1": "superficially", "2": "regularly", "3": "magnificently", "4": "unanimously", "answer": "unanimously", "question": "In a strong display of confidence, the firm's board of directors ___ approved the merger."}, "3442": {"1": "poll", "2": "polls", "3": "pollster", "4": "polled", "answer": "polled", "question": "When recently ___ , residents of Mill Creek Park said that street disrepair is the issue that concerns them most."}, "3443": {"1": "considering", "2": "so that", "3": "as if", "4": "wherever", "answer": "so that", "question": "Ms. Rivera agreed to work on the holiday ___ Mr. Grant could attend the conference."}, "3444": {"1": "throughout", "2": "all along", "3": "too much", "4": "downstairs", "answer": "downstairs", "question": "The clerk collects packages from each department twice a day and takes them to the mail room ___ ."}, "3445": {"1": "beyond", "2": "between", "3": "during", "4": "against", "answer": "beyond", "question": "Please inform Ms. Erwin of any complaints ___ those already discussed in today's meeting."}, "3446": {"1": "accomplishes", "2": "accomplishment", "3": "accomplished", "4": "accomplish", "answer": "accomplished", "question": "The Tonsin Writers League is a reputable organization with highly ___ members."}, "3447": {"1": "discussing", "2": "briefing", "3": "resuming", "4": "narrating", "answer": "briefing", "question": "As Mr. Nakata's assistant, Ms. Bain is in charge of ___ him on the latest financial news."}, "3448": {"1": "addition", "2": "additions", "3": "additional", "4": "additionally", "answer": "additional", "question": "The event planner determined that Tuesday's forum will require ___ chairs."}, "3449": {"1": "contains", "2": "orders", "3": "writes", "4": "copies", "answer": "orders", "question": "Ms. Hu will check the storage closet before she ___ more office supplies."}, "3450": {"1": "participate", "2": "participates", "3": "participated", "4": "participation", "answer": "participation", "question": "All sales staff are asked to acknowledge their ___ in Monday's workshop."}, "3451": {"1": "easy", "2": "ease", "3": "easiest", "4": "easily", "answer": "easily", "question": "The commercial for Zhou's Caf was ___ Sunn Agency's best advertisement of the year."}, "3452": {"1": "any", "2": "few", "3": "single", "4": "many", "answer": "any", "question": "Use coupon code SAVE20 to purchase ___ perfume or cologne for 20 percent off."}, "3453": {"1": "competitor", "2": "competing", "3": "competitive", "4": "competitively", "answer": "competitor", "question": "Talk-Talk Cell Phone Company will soon be merging with its main ___ ."}, "3454": {"1": "create", "2": "creation", "3": "creative", "4": "creatively", "answer": "creative", "question": "Ms. Ellis designed one of the most ___ marketing campaigns the department had seen."}, "3455": {"1": "eventual", "2": "probable", "3": "close", "4": "positive", "answer": "positive", "question": "Last month we received numerous ___ comments from customers on our blog."}, "3456": {"1": "inside", "2": "after", "3": "where", "4": "whenever", "answer": "after", "question": "Beginning on August 1, patients will be asked to complete a short survey ___ each visit."}, "3457": {"1": "continually", "2": "continue", "3": "continual", "4": "continued", "answer": "continually", "question": "Viewing the beautiful landscape outside her door ___ inspires Elia Colao to paint."}, "3458": {"1": "vision", "2": "meeting", "3": "approach", "4": "assembly", "answer": "assembly", "question": "Although the parts are made in China, the ___ of Jamy bicycles is done in Canada."}, "3459": {"1": "is prevented", "2": "prevent", "3": "to prevent", "4": "prevented", "answer": "to prevent", "question": "Many businesses promote carpooling ___ traffic congestion."}, "3460": {"1": "Despite", "2": "Finally", "3": "Until", "4": "During", "answer": "Until", "question": "___ the repairs are complete, only essential personnel are allowed in the building."}, "3461": {"1": "replacing", "2": "replaces", "3": "replaced", "4": "replacements", "answer": "replacements", "question": "We apologize for having used the wrong colors on the Slarott Architecture brochures and will deliver ___ on Friday."}, "3462": {"1": "properly", "2": "restfully", "3": "truly", "4": "finely", "answer": "properly", "question": "Employees must store all tools ___ at the end of the shift."}, "3463": {"1": "application", "2": "establishment", "3": "experience", "4": "accomplishment", "answer": "application", "question": "An ___ to renovate the old factory was submitted to the city council."}, "3464": {"1": "whose", "2": "who", "3": "which", "4": "whichever", "answer": "who", "question": "Customers ___ wish to return a defective item may do so within twenty days of the date of purchase."}, "3465": {"1": "from", "2": "around", "3": "for", "4": "by", "answer": "for", "question": "The Golubovich House will be open ___ a special living-history program on Sunday."}, "3466": {"1": "qualify", "2": "qualifications", "3": "qualifying", "4": "qualified", "answer": "qualified", "question": "Mr. Wijaya is reviewing the resumes to select the candidate best ___ for the position."}, "3467": {"1": "destinations", "2": "ambitions", "3": "purposes", "4": "intentions", "answer": "destinations", "question": "Laura Gless promotes faculty-led study programs in ___ such as France and Italy."}, "3468": {"1": "so", "2": "about", "3": "whether", "4": "of", "answer": "whether", "question": "Mr. Stafford e-mailed the clients to ask ___ there is a train station near their office."}, "3469": {"1": "regarded", "2": "issued", "3": "performed", "4": "constructed", "answer": "issued", "question": "Last year, the city ___ nearly  building permits to small-business owners."}, "3470": {"1": "theirs", "2": "them", "3": "their", "4": "themselves", "answer": "theirs", "question": "Local merchants are hopeful that if this new business succeeds, ___ will also benefit."}, "3471": {"1": "connected", "2": "launched", "3": "persuaded", "4": "treated", "answer": "treated", "question": "Following the retirement of Mr. Whalen, the company ___ a search for a new CEO."}, "3472": {"1": "beyond", "2": "over", "3": "past", "4": "through", "answer": "through", "question": "Ms. Travaglini filed the paperwork with the facilities department ___ a week ago."}, "3473": {"1": "expired", "2": "is expiring", "3": "will be expiring", "4": "expires", "answer": "is expiring", "question": "After the lease ___ , customers have the option of purchasing the car or returning it to their local dealer."}, "3474": {"1": "instinctively", "2": "simultaneously", "3": "collectively", "4": "mutually", "answer": "mutually", "question": "The Jones News Hour is broadcast ___ on radio and television."}, "3475": {"1": "arrives", "2": "will arrive", "3": "had arrived", "4": "arriving", "answer": "had arrived", "question": "Ms. Choi would have been at the keynote address if her train ___ on time."}, "3476": {"1": "You", "2": "Yours", "3": "Your", "4": "Yourself", "answer": "Your", "question": "___ account will be credited after we receive the returned merchandise."}, "3477": {"1": "solved", "2": "accepted", "3": "decided", "4": "earned", "answer": "accepted", "question": "Late entries for the cake decoration contest will not be ___ ."}, "3478": {"1": "increase", "2": "increases", "3": "increasingly", "4": "increased", "answer": "increase", "question": "The newspaper has seen an ___ in the number of subscribers who read the online version."}, "3479": {"1": "at", "2": "for", "3": "on", "4": "by", "answer": "for", "question": "Every attorney at the firm of Duncan and Hulce has practiced law ___ more than ten years."}, "3480": {"1": "powerful", "2": "powers", "3": "powerfully", "4": "power", "answer": "powerful", "question": "Prethart Tool Company has created a more ___ drill than its previous models."}, "3481": {"1": "mostly", "2": "simply", "3": "enough", "4": "quite", "answer": "simply", "question": "To find out if an item on this Web site is in stock, ___ highlight the item and click the Check on it button."}, "3482": {"1": "will assist", "2": "assisted", "3": "to assist", "4": "is assisted", "answer": "will assist", "question": "Mr. Jones ___ Ms. Cheng's clients while she is on a business trip to Hong Kong."}, "3483": {"1": "ready", "2": "strong", "3": "available", "4": "agreeable", "answer": "available", "question": "The Jossty Company offers insurance policies to renters at the lowest rates ___ ."}, "3484": {"1": "As soon as", "2": "Still", "3": "In the meantime", "4": "For example", "answer": "As soon as", "question": "___ the Editorial Department receives the author's final approval, the manuscript should be sent to the printer."}, "3485": {"1": "general", "2": "generally", "3": "generalize", "4": "generalization", "answer": "generally", "question": "Sidewalks in the town of Newburgh are ___ one meter wide."}, "3486": {"1": "member", "2": "building", "3": "frontier", "4": "committee", "answer": "committee", "question": "The housing authority has formed a ___ to look for new construction locations."}, "3487": {"1": "what", "2": "where", "3": "who", "4": "when", "answer": "who", "question": "A recent study has found that those ___ regularly read food labels tend to be healthier."}, "3488": {"1": "satisfaction", "2": "satisfying", "3": "satisfied", "4": "satisfy", "answer": "satisfied", "question": "If you are not ___ with your Electoshine toothbrush, you may return it for a full refund."}, "3489": {"1": "among", "2": "into", "3": "around", "4": "between", "answer": "into", "question": "DG Feed Supply has shown strong growth heading ___ the end of the fiscal year."}, "3490": {"1": "arise", "2": "arises", "3": "had arisen", "4": "arising", "answer": "arises", "question": "Book fair volunteers may be asked to work longer shifts if the need ___ ."}, "3491": {"1": "under", "2": "past", "3": "until", "4": "since", "answer": "since", "question": "On Tuesday, Mr. Molina will visit the Seoul office for the first time ___ becoming vice-president of operations."}, "3492": {"1": "impression", "2": "impressive", "3": "impresses", "4": "impressed", "answer": "impressive", "question": "Attendees said the fireworks were the most ___ part of the festival."}, "3493": {"1": "perfectly", "2": "recently", "3": "routinely", "4": "occasionally", "answer": "perfectly", "question": "The interview panel felt that Dinah Ong's education fit the job description of junior accountant ___ ."}, "3494": {"1": "rely", "2": "reliable", "3": "reliant", "4": "reliably", "answer": "reliably", "question": "The new software makes it possible to track purchases ___ at multiple points-of-sale."}, "3495": {"1": "Provided", "2": "Applying", "3": "Toward", "4": "Over", "answer": "Over", "question": "___ the next few months, Camion Vehicles will add more features to its sedans."}, "3496": {"1": "considerable", "2": "wide", "3": "central", "4": "dominant", "answer": "considerable", "question": "Altona Printing is expecting a ___ upturn in holiday card orders in the next few weeks."}, "3497": {"1": "designed", "2": "designs", "3": "designing", "4": "designers", "answer": "designs", "question": "By creating innovative packaging ___ , EK2 Beverages hopes consumers will reuse their water bottles."}, "3498": {"1": "excelled", "2": "organized", "3": "instructed", "4": "simplified", "answer": "excelled", "question": "Throughout her tenure at LPID Systems, Ms. Patterson has ___ at defining complex concepts in simple terms."}, "3499": {"1": "promptly", "2": "before", "3": "although", "4": "promised", "answer": "promised", "question": "Winslet Food Service has ___ to expand the cafeteria's menu offerings."}, "3500": {"1": "Because", "2": "Depending on", "3": "Whereas", "4": "In order for", "answer": "Depending on", "question": "___ the results of the customer survey, we may consider extending the store's evening hours until 9 P.M."}, "3501": {"1": "exceptions", "2": "exception", "3": "excepting", "4": "exceptionally", "answer": "exceptionally", "question": "Yerrow Cameras' lenses have a long telephoto reach yet an ___ lightweight casing."}, "3502": {"1": "thoroughly", "2": "distinctly", "3": "eventually", "4": "already", "answer": "eventually", "question": "After postponing her studies for many years, Ms. Ruiz ___ earned a degree in law."}, "3503": {"1": "profitability", "2": "profitable", "3": "profited", "4": "profitably", "answer": "profitability", "question": "A favorable report on the ___ of Seesom Eyewear convinced the partners to invest in the company."}, "3504": {"1": "hesitated", "2": "emphasized", "3": "dominated", "4": "launched", "answer": "emphasized", "question": "In Monday's meeting, Mr. Ito ___ the need to hire enough workers for the peak season."}, "3505": {"1": "routine", "2": "accessory", "3": "incorporation", "4": "submission", "answer": "incorporation", "question": "Pugh Tower won the Best New Building Award for its creative ___ of sustainable materials."}, "3506": {"1": "requests", "2": "behaves", "3": "uses", "4": "visits", "answer": "requests", "question": "The custodial staff ___ that we clean our dishes before leaving the kitchen."}, "3507": {"1": "certify", "2": "certificate", "3": "certifiable", "4": "certifiably", "answer": "certificate", "question": "If customers lose their original warranty ___ , they can download a new one from the Web site."}, "3508": {"1": "on", "2": "t0", "3": "for", "4": "in", "answer": "in", "question": "Our Portview branch is located ___ the central business district, between Burnside Avenue and Everett street."}, "3509": {"1": "knowingly", "2": "known", "3": "knew", "4": "to know", "answer": "knew", "question": "None of the employees ___ that Mr. Annan planned to retire at the end of the year."}, "3510": {"1": "you", "2": "your", "3": "yours", "4": "yourself", "answer": "your", "question": "Apply to Joneston Stores today so as not to miss ___ chance to join a great sales team."}, "3511": {"1": "possible", "2": "frequent", "3": "closed", "4": "higher", "answer": "higher", "question": "Employees are eligible to receive a ___ salary if they complete a special marketing course."}, "3512": {"1": "successfully", "2": "successful", "3": "succeed", "4": "success", "answer": "successful", "question": "Keeping the Deal, Jan Butler's latest volume on management style, is her most commercially ___ book to date."}, "3513": {"1": "accessory", "2": "associate", "3": "faculty", "4": "formula", "answer": "associate", "question": "Present this postcard to a sales ___ at any of our stores and receive a 5.00 gift card."}, "3514": {"1": "multiple", "2": "multiply", "3": "multiples", "4": "multiplied", "answer": "multiple", "question": "Lakeside Shopping Center has undergone ___ renovations in the last decade."}, "3515": {"1": "staplers", "2": "volunteers", "3": "devices", "4": "headquarters", "answer": "volunteers", "question": "There is a mandatory meeting today for everyone involved in managing or recruiting ___ ."}, "3516": {"1": "now", "2": "from", "3": "while", "4": "when", "answer": "from", "question": "The Smeeville bus system will accept only Rove Fare cards ___ May 1 onward."}, "3517": {"1": "understandably", "2": "understanding", "3": "understood", "4": "understand", "answer": "understandably", "question": "Relocating for work is ___ a difficult decision, but it can be rewarding."}, "3518": {"1": "settling", "2": "settler", "3": "settle", "4": "settled", "answer": "settled", "question": "Last week Parmax Corporation ___ a disagreement with its main competitor concerning.patent infringement. ."}, "3519": {"1": "consistency", "2": "consistencies .", "3": "consistent", "4": "consistently", "answer": "consistently", "question": "Khoury Dairy's upgraded milk-bottling system has ___ increased productivity in the Tallahassee plant."}, "3520": {"1": "complained", "2": "complaint", "3": "complaining", "4": "complain", "answer": "complaint", "question": "The Rinka  blender has not received a single ___ in the New Products Web forum."}, "3521": {"1": "into", "2": "over", "3": "among", "4": "across", "answer": "among", "question": "After raising $45 million last year, Yamamoto Technologies is now ___ Seattle's best-funded companies."}, "3522": {"1": "allowable", "2": "additional", "3": "uninterested", "4": "inclusive", "answer": "additional", "question": "Deangelo's Delights was so popular that the owner opened two ___ bakeries."}, "3523": {"1": "unless", "2": "rather than", "3": "as if", "4": "after", "answer": "after", "question": "Chef Octavia Farina took over Fratelli's Restaurant ___ the previous chef left to open a new restaurant."}, "3524": {"1": "produced", "2": "producing", "3": "production", "4": "productive", "answer": "production", "question": "The director of Wingstom Foods commended Ms. Weiss for increasing ___ in the bakery division."}, "3525": {"1": "he", "2": "his", "3": "himself", "4": "his own", "answer": "himself", "question": "Greg Owens, founder of multi-national Hermes Taxi Service, used to drive a taxi ___ ."}, "3526": {"1": "adjustments", "2": "endorsements", "3": "computations", "4": "expectations", "answer": "expectations", "question": "Starlight Theaters is proud to announce record earnings for the third quarter, far exceeding ___ ."}, "3527": {"1": "whichever", "2": "however", "3": "everyone", "4": "much", "answer": "whichever", "question": "Employees can attend one of the many workshops offered, ___ seems most interesting."}, "3528": {"1": "Given", "2": "Deciding", "3": "Finding", "4": "Because", "answer": "Given", "question": "___ her strong negotiation skills, Marie Russel was made Sanwa, Inc.'s lead sales contact."}, "3529": {"1": "anonymously", "2": "approximately", "3": "expressly", "4": "patiently", "answer": "anonymously", "question": "A locked suggestion box will allow employees to submit feedback to management ___ ."}, "3530": {"1": "invest", "2": "compete", "3": "participate", "4": "market", "answer": "market", "question": "A new strategy is under development to ___ our products more aggressively overseas."}, "3531": {"1": "Comment", "2": "Comments", "3": "Commented", "4": "Commenting", "answer": "Commenting", "question": "___ on the city's ongoing revitalization project, Mayor Owen promised that residents would be pleased with the results."}, "3532": {"1": "Tremendously", "2": "Unfortunately", "3": "Casually", "4": "Enormously", "answer": "Unfortunately", "question": "___ , repairs to the plumbing pipes in the Moffett Building will be costly."}, "3533": {"1": "entirety", "2": "system", "3": "perception", "4": "estimation", "answer": "entirety", "question": "The CEO's speech will be recorded in its ___ and made available to employees who could not attend the meeting."}, "3534": {"1": "accidentally", "2": "coincidentally", "3": "steeply", "4": "unexpectedly", "answer": "unexpectedly", "question": "Trails on the southeast side of the mountain are often closed ___ because storms tend to occur without warning."}, "3535": {"1": "as well as", "2": "above all", "3": "in addition", "4": "in case that", "answer": "as well as", "question": "Please submit your hours ___ any work-related expense reports by Friday."}, "3536": {"1": "she", "2": "her", "3": "hers", "4": "herself", "answer": "her", "question": "While the director of communications is away, all e-mails and calls will be forwarded to ___ assistant."}, "3537": {"1": "so", "2": "ever", "3": "too", "4": "already", "answer": "too", "question": "Mr. Srour's flight arrived ___ late for him to attend the reception."}, "3538": {"1": "opening", "2": "openness", "3": "openly", "4": "opens", "answer": "opening", "question": "Mr. Wagner will arrange the schedule of events for the ___ of the flagship store."}, "3539": {"1": "During", "2": "Then", "3": "After", "4": "Next", "answer": "After", "question": "___ the final award had been presented, Ms. Ryu acknowledged the support of the event's sponsors."}, "3540": {"1": "succeed", "2": "success", "3": "successful", "4": "successfully", "answer": "successful", "question": "Chunto Consultancy Service recommended a ___ way of balancing the annual budget."}, "3541": {"1": "up", "2": "on", "3": "of", "4": "in", "answer": "on", "question": "Press lightly ___ the pedal with your left foot to release the vehicle's parking brake."}, "3542": {"1": "visiting", "2": "to visit", "3": "visits", "4": "having visited", "answer": "to visit", "question": "___ Hikers are invited the information center for trail maps of Far Valley Park."}, "3543": {"1": "unmistakable", "2": "incomplete", "3": "unused", "4": "inexperienced", "answer": "inexperienced", "question": "Danton Estate Brokerage offers an online educational program to help ___ home buyers choose a property."}, "3544": {"1": "how", "2": "that", "3": "since", "4": "about", "answer": "how", "question": "lolana Dance Troupe stands out because the group knows ___ to integrate a variety of dance styles."}, "3545": {"1": "use", "2": "model", "3": "time", "4": "call", "answer": "use", "question": "The Lafayette Hill Public Library requires that the ___ of mobile phones be restricted to the conversation rooms."}, "3546": {"1": "increases", "2": "increasing", "3": "increased", "4": "increasingly", "answer": "increasingly", "question": "Major airlines have ___ been using self-serve ticketing systems to reduce wait times."}, "3547": {"1": "from", "2": "to", "3": "off", "4": "for", "answer": "for", "question": "A book of songs written by Pakistani singer Ayesha Saad was sold at auction yesterday ___ an undisclosed amount."}, "3548": {"1": "other", "2": "neither", "3": "nothing", "4": "whatever", "answer": "nothing", "question": "There is ___ more important to maintaining dental health than brushing your teeth twice a day."}, "3549": {"1": "find", "2": "feel", "3": "take", "4": "like", "answer": "find", "question": "Taste tests suggest that most people ___ Dairysmooth's red-bean-flavored ice cream very appetizing."}, "3550": {"1": "even", "2": "whether", "3": "although", "4": "including", "answer": "whether", "question": "Regardless of ___ a candidate is offered a job, all applications are kept on file for six months."}, "3551": {"1": "Not only", "2": "In case of", "3": "As though", "4": "According to", "answer": "According to", "question": "___ the Nye Research Center, performing assigned duties for 30 minutes while standing increases productivity."}, "3552": {"1": "restricts", "2": "restricting", "3": "restrictive", "4": "restrictions", "answer": "restrictions", "question": "This booklet is intended to inform drivers of ___ on bridge travel for oversized vehicles."}, "3553": {"1": "exceptional", "2": "surpassing", "3": "effective", "4": "dominant", "answer": "exceptional", "question": "Customers can now enjoy ___ food seven days a week at the recently renovated Novani Grill."}, "3554": {"1": "energetic", "2": "most energetic", "3": "energetically", "4": "more energetically", "answer": "more energetically", "question": "No one at the Anshelt Corporation campaigned ___ for expansion of the internship program than Melody Ahn."}, "3555": {"1": "cover", "2": "prepare", "3": "progress", "4": "evaluate", "answer": "evaluate", "question": "Monday's workshop will help restaurant owners ___ their ability to effectively recruit, train, and retain staff."}, "3556": {"1": "substance", "2": "substances", "3": "substantial", "4": "substantially", "answer": "substantial", "question": "The digital advertising campaign has generated ___ interest in the clothing line."}, "3557": {"1": "consistently", "2": "largely", "3": "hugely", "4": "identically", "answer": "consistently", "question": "The seminar leader stated that addressing customer concerns ___ was one crucial element for financial success."}, "3558": {"1": "function", "2": "functional", "3": "functionally", "4": "functioned", "answer": "functional", "question": "Although the desk was slightly damaged during assembly, it is still ___ ."}, "3559": {"1": "Far from", "2": "Despite", "3": "Among", "4": "Instead of", "answer": "Despite", "question": "___ its discounts for new customers, Teratran Phone's service plans are considered inferior by many."}, "3560": {"1": "has transferred", "2": "transferring", "3": "transfer", "4": "to transfer", "answer": "has transferred", "question": "Now that Ms. Nakamura ___ to the London headquarters, a new manager is running our Tokyo office."}, "3561": {"1": "Even though", "2": "Instead of", "3": "In addition to", "4": "On top of", "answer": "Even though", "question": "___ the kitchen cabinets arrived late, the contractor installed them without putting the job behind schedule."}, "3562": {"1": "expecting", "2": "if not", "3": "unlike", "4": "as long as", "answer": "as long as", "question": "The proposal for the Seascape project will be ready tomorrow ___ we receive the budget analysis today."}, "3563": {"1": "closely", "2": "sparsely", "3": "reasonably", "4": "absolutely", "answer": "reasonably", "question": "The Ortimate 3 home theater system is Hyong Electronics' most ___ priced configuration."}, "3564": {"1": "is offering", "2": "has been offering", "3": "will be offering", "4": "would have been offering", "answer": "has been offering", "question": "The Oakwood Restaurant ___ a special dinner menu on Saturdays for the past decade."}, "3565": {"1": "engagement", "2": "term", "3": "subject", "4": "employment", "answer": "engagement", "question": "Mr. de Tonnancour has a speaking ___ on Tuesday, November 15."}, "3566": {"1": "consults", "2": "is consulting", "3": "to consult", "4": "consulted", "answer": "consulted", "question": "Mr. Guo ___ with an electrician yesterday about the rewiring project."}, "3567": {"1": "she", "2": "her", "3": "hers", "4": "herself", "answer": "her", "question": "Ms. Lan Le will complete ___ internship at the George Cake Shop next week."}, "3568": {"1": "create", "2": "discuss", "3": "perform", "4": "dictate", "answer": "discuss", "question": "Every Thursday the Lifelong Reading Club meets to ___ novels written by local authors."}, "3569": {"1": "quick", "2": "quickly", "3": "quicker", "4": "quickest", "answer": "quickly", "question": "Skymills Insurance ___ grew from a small business to a midsize company with  employees."}, "3570": {"1": "open", "2": "opened", "3": "opening", "4": "openly", "answer": "opening", "question": "Local shop owners are invited to the ___ of Clyde Bank's downtown branch."}, "3571": {"1": "stored", "2": "escaped", "3": "served", "4": "determined", "answer": "stored", "question": "All e-mail messages regarding legal issues should be ___ in a separate folder."}, "3572": {"1": "assist", "2": "assistant", "3": "assisted", "4": "assistance", "answer": "assistant", "question": "Hiring an ___ for Ms. Tsai must be our top priority, as her workload has increased."}, "3573": {"1": "origin", "2": "originated", "3": "originally", "4": "original", "answer": "original", "question": "The ___ Ladoff Building was constructed in  and stood two stories tall."}, "3574": {"1": "central", "2": "consecutive", "3": "actual", "4": "recent", "answer": "recent", "question": "If you have questions about your most ___ credit card statement, call Mr. Hassan."}, "3575": {"1": "to", "2": "past", "3": "than", "4": "by", "answer": "than", "question": "The Rinzlite dishwasher was ranked higher ___ all other dishwashers in its class."}, "3576": {"1": "will sell", "2": "was sold", "3": "has sold", "4": "are selling", "answer": "has sold", "question": "So far, the Grantley store ___ 20 percent more mobile phones than it did last year."}, "3577": {"1": "fully", "2": "fullness", "3": "fullest", "4": "full", "answer": "fully", "question": "In the event of a power failure, unplug computers until power is ___ restored."}, "3578": {"1": "next", "2": "yet", "3": "still", "4": "finally", "answer": "still", "question": "Although Mr. Akiyama retired last year, he ___ visits the office each week."}, "3579": {"1": "convince", "2": "convincing", "3": "convinced", "4": "convincingly", "answer": "convincing", "question": "At the panel discussion, Ms. Yang made a ___ argument for environmentally responsible business practices."}, "3580": {"1": "attention", "2": "investigations", "3": "motivation", "4": "auditions", "answer": "auditions", "question": "The Hokodo Orchestra will hold ___ for new string musicians next Tuesday."}, "3581": {"1": "themselves", "2": "they", "3": "theirs", "4": "them", "answer": "themselves", "question": "Although the team members ___ were not available after the game, the coach was happy to be interviewed."}, "3582": {"1": "relatively", "2": "occasionally", "3": "completely", "4": "enormously", "answer": "completely", "question": "Ms. Schwimmer's application was not ___ reviewed until November 5."}, "3583": {"1": "construction", "2": "constructively", "3": "constructive", "4": "constructing", "answer": "constructive", "question": "Managers are encouraged to give their staff ___ feedback during the annual performance-review meetings."}, "3584": {"1": "statements", "2": "exchanges", "3": "precautions", "4": "options", "answer": "options", "question": "Deckermark Enterprises offers employees flexible scheduling and telecommuting ___ ."}, "3585": {"1": "even", "2": "some", "3": "such", "4": "else", "answer": "even", "question": "Ms. Summer can estimate the cost for the land-clearing project in Fosterville, ___ before the details are finalized."}, "3586": {"1": "impressive", "2": "impression", "3": "impressively", "4": "impress", "answer": "impressively", "question": "The company's transition from paper paychecks to electronic paychecks was ___ smooth."}, "3587": {"1": "combine", "2": "obtain", "3": "gather", "4": "approach", "answer": "obtain", "question": "All temporary workers should contact Ms. Fierro to ___ an identification badge."}, "3588": {"1": "once", "2": "since", "3": "like", "4": "except", "answer": "once", "question": "We will pay your insurance claim ___ we receive the official damage report."}, "3589": {"1": "politicians", "2": "politicize", "3": "political", "4": "politically", "answer": "politicians", "question": "Neither of the ___ in the debate was willing to take a stand on the riverfront development controversy."}, "3590": {"1": "Over", "2": "On", "3": "At", "4": "With", "answer": "With", "question": "___ the additional funding, Central City Medical School expects to double the size of its research team."}, "3591": {"1": "sufficient", "2": "flexible", "3": "capable", "4": "calculating", "answer": "sufficient", "question": "The clients have indicated that a reception area of 60 square meters will be ___ in the new building."}, "3592": {"1": "whatever", "2": "while", "3": "why", "4": "who", "answer": "why", "question": "Ms. Lau would like to know ___ Mr. Cole called the main office yesterday."}, "3593": {"1": "consequently", "2": "in order to", "3": "in any case", "4": "additionally", "answer": "in order to", "question": "Koffler Law hired more paralegals ___ meet its commitment to clients."}, "3594": {"1": "familiarity", "2": "persistence", "3": "durability", "4": "replacement", "answer": "durability", "question": "The newest edition of the Biltmire Road Atlas has plastic-coated pages for extra ___"}, "3595": {"1": "prior to", "2": "outside of", "3": "in front of", "4": "according to", "answer": "prior to", "question": "Job seekers should prepare a list of professional references ___ applying for positions."}, "3596": {"1": "increased", "2": "increasing", "3": "increases", "4": "increase", "answer": "increase", "question": "Kanelek Limited and Evensohn LLC have entered a strategic partnership to ___ their market share."}, "3597": {"1": "exposed", "2": "communal", "3": "friendly", "4": "considerable", "answer": "friendly", "question": "Glenwick Organic Farm stands out from other farms for its environmentally ___ practices."}, "3598": {"1": "divided", "2": "division", "3": "divisive", "4": "dividing", "answer": "division", "question": "Our ___ is responsible for performing quality-control reviews during production."}, "3599": {"1": "around", "2": "through", "3": "except", "4": "until", "answer": "until", "question": "Because of a mechanical failure in the production facility, Fizzy Bottlers will be closed ___ further notice."}, "3600": {"1": "themselves", "2": "theirs", "3": "them", "4": "their", "answer": "themselves", "question": "Interviewees are asked not to talk among ___ while waiting in the reception area."}, "3601": {"1": "very", "2": "enough", "3": "rather", "4": "soon", "answer": "soon", "question": "The accounting department reminds all staff to submit expense reports ___ after returning from a trip."}, "3602": {"1": "occasion", "2": "occasions", "3": "occasional", "4": "occasionally", "answer": "occasionally", "question": "Olayinka Boutique ___ hosts special shopping events for members of its loyalty club."}, "3603": {"1": "lengthy", "2": "immediate", "3": "helpful", "4": "perceptive", "answer": "helpful", "question": "For homeowners seeking to reduce their electricity bills, the energy-saving ideas in this brochure should be ___ ."}, "3604": {"1": "maintenance", "2": "maintains", "3": "maintaining", "4": "is maintained", "answer": "maintains", "question": "The Delmar Highway Department ___ an online list of current road closures."}, "3605": {"1": "Rather than", "2": "Whether", "3": "Just as", "4": "Namely", "answer": "Rather than", "question": "___ reducing staff, management made the decision to decrease administrative bonuses."}, "3606": {"1": "graceful", "2": "grace", "3": "gracefully", "4": "graces", "answer": "gracefully", "question": "The doorways, which arch so ___ , were left intact during the renovation of the historic Dersten Building."}, "3607": {"1": "performed", "2": "flattered", "3": "welcomed", "4": "challenged", "answer": "flattered", "question": "Ms. Maeda was ___ that her art submission was used on the cover of the firm's annual report."}, "3608": {"1": "method", "2": "relation", "3": "concern", "4": "source", "answer": "concern", "question": "The primary ___ is whether the cost of the car repair is reasonable considering the amount of labor involved."}, "3609": {"1": "impressive", "2": "impress", "3": "impressively", "4": "impresses", "answer": "impressive", "question": "Norvo Financial has built an ___ client base in a short period of time."}, "3610": {"1": "monitor", "2": "require", "3": "confirm", "4": "include", "answer": "require", "question": "We ___ all employees to wear formal business attire when meeting with clients in the office."}, "3611": {"1": "Both", "2": "None", "3": "Neither", "4": "Whoever", "answer": "Neither", "question": "___ Ms. Chang nor Mr. Kao received the e-mail outlining the project proposal."}, "3612": {"1": "carefully", "2": "remotely", "3": "eventually", "4": "closely", "answer": "remotely", "question": "In case of inclement weather, employees are encouraged to work ___ rather than travel to the office."}, "3613": {"1": "copy", "2": "repair", "3": "support", "4": "vary", "answer": "vary", "question": "Long-term maintenance fees ___ according to the type of industrial printing machine purchased."}, "3614": {"1": "clearing", "2": "clear", "3": "clearly", "4": "cleared", "answer": "clear", "question": "Ms. Kwon made it absolutely ___ that hiring decisions require her approval."}, "3615": {"1": "illustrating", "2": "illustrated", "3": "illustration", "4": "illustrates", "answer": "illustrated", "question": "Sookie Choi's latest children's book is being ___ by Chung-He Park."}, "3616": {"1": "scene !", "2": "society", "3": "formality", "4": "reception", "answer": "reception", "question": "The Stoneport Gallery is hosting a ___ next week to showcase the works of sculptor Fabrice Pepin."}, "3617": {"1": "translate", "2": "listen", "3": "wait", "4": "train", "answer": "train", "question": "Mr. Soto will run 5 kilometers every other day in order to ___ for the Leesburg Corporate Challenge half marathon."}, "3618": {"1": "responsible", "2": "responsibly", "3": "responsibility", "4": "responsibleness", "answer": "responsibly", "question": "All employees are expected to behave ___ when they are traveling on company business."}, "3619": {"1": "During", "2": "Therefore", "3": "When", "4": "Because", "answer": "Because", "question": "___ he is now retired, Mr. Matilia is able to pursue his hobby of woodworking."}, "3620": {"1": "Applies", "2": "Application", "3": "Applicants", "4": "Applying", "answer": "Applicants", "question": "___ for press coverage of the music festival will receive official responses by June 30."}, "3621": {"1": "before", "2": "of", "3": "what", "4": "so", "answer": "before", "question": "All employees should back up crucial data ___ switching over to the new software system on August 5."}, "3622": {"1": "importance", "2": "safety", "3": "foundation", "4": "origin", "answer": "origin", "question": "A label on each box should indicate the production date as well as the place of ___ of the contents."}, "3623": {"1": "her", "2": "she", "3": "hers", "4": "herself", "answer": "she", "question": "Ms. Jha assured the client that ___ would deliver the contract that afternoon."}, "3624": {"1": "agree", "2": "agreement", "3": "agreeable", "4": "agrees", "answer": "agreeable", "question": "During negotiations, management appeared ___ to the idea of increasing the staff's wages."}, "3625": {"1": "across", "2": "into", "3": "between", "4": "despite", "answer": "across", "question": "Employees ___ several departments have been encouraged to minimize costs."}, "3626": {"question": "Sunwirth Sneakers has several ___ in the greater metropolitan area.", "1": "locations", "2": "locate", "3": "located", "4": "location", "answer": "locations"}, "3627": {"question": "Cimber CPAs offers clients the convenience of ___ their invoices online and by mail.", "1": "buying", "2": "paying", "3": "going", "4": "eating", "answer": "paying"}, "3628": {"question": "The new software at Patel Industries has been working ___ since it was installed last year.", "1": "reliable", "2": "to rely", "3": "more reliable", "4": "reliably", "answer": "reliably"}, "3629": {"question": "Best practices in customer service are outlined ___ the training handbook.", "1": "along", "2": "toward", "3": "over", "4": "throughout", "answer": "throughout"}, "3630": {"question": "The Scratch software will help us migrate our client records ___.", "1": "simple", "2": "simpler", "3": "simply", "4": "simplicity", "answer": "simply"}, "3631": {"question": "The comedian said that ___ sense of humor was inherited from a grandparent.", "1": "herself", "2": "her", "3": "she", "4": "hers", "answer": "her"}, "3632": {"question": "Starting this August, Gavelton Bike Tours will be leading group cycling trips ___ Paris to Berlin.", "1": "from", "2": "beside", "3": "along", "4": "after", "answer": "from"}, "3633": {"question": "We hope to ___ an agreement with Mason Cooper, Inc., within the next week.", "1": "reach", "2": "talk", "3": "reason", "4": "put", "answer": "reach"}, "3634": {"question": "Factory-floor managers must submit an inspection report at the end ___ their shift.", "1": "if", "2": "to", "3": "of", "4": "as", "answer": "of"}, "3635": {"question": "___ a retail store, Seedum International will now sell merchandise only through its Web site.", "1": "Sometimes", "2": "Later", "3": "Formerly", "4": "Frequently", "answer": "Formerly"}, "3636": {"question": "Remarkably, neither Ms. Chen ___ Mr. Gillespie had been notified that the board meeting was canceled.", "1": "or", "2": "and", "3": "with", "4": "nor", "answer": "nor"}, "3637": {"question": "The new microwave soup containers are ___ than the previous ones.", "1": "rigid", "2": "most rigidly", "3": "rigidly", "4": "more rigid", "answer": "more rigid"}, "3638": {"question": "The Banly Tourism Society is ___ to present the first issue of its publication, The Banly Quarterly.", "1": "regular", "2": "general", "3": "proud", "4": "favorite", "answer": "proud"}, "3639": {"question": "Konixer Printers is conducting a thorough ___ of current requests for equipment upgrades.", "1": "evaluate", "2": "evaluation", "3": "evaluator", "4": "evaluative", "answer": "evaluation"}, "3640": {"question": "___ the addition of 300 spaces, the ferry terminals parking area is still full by 9:00 A.M. every day.", "1": "Despite", "2": "Across", "3": "Besides", "4": "Inside", "answer": "Despite"}, "3641": {"question": "Justlox, Inc., is planning to ___ redesign Model 543Q with its partners in Britain to ensure a better product.", "1": "collaboration", "2": "collaborative", "3": "collaboratively", "4": "collaborate", "answer": "collaboratively"}, "3642": {"question": "Each box of Lane Permanent Markers contains an ___ of surprising colors.", "1": "assortment", "2": "excitement", "3": "account", "4": "industry", "answer": "assortment"}, "3643": {"question": "We were pleased by the ___ and courteous reply we received from Astella Airlines concerning the change in itinerary.", "1": "safe", "2": "close", "3": "clean", "4": "prompt", "answer": "prompt"}, "3644": {"question": "The rising employment rate is one factor contributing to ___ in the housing construction trade.", "1": "grow", "2": "growth", "3": "grew", "4": "grown", "answer": "growth"}, "3645": {"question": "The color of the new chairs was not ___ on the invoice", "1": "specify", "2": "specified", "3": "specifying", "4": "specification", "answer": "specified"}, "3646": {"question": "Two hours is the ___ amount of time needed to complete the assignment.", "1": "minimum", "2": "temporary", "3": "bottom", "4": "durab", "answer": "minimum"}, "3647": {"question": "A successful digital marketing campaign has helped Fossler Electronics ___ its profit margins.", "1": "stabilized", "2": "stability", "3": "stabilizing", "4": "stabilize", "answer": "stabilize"}, "3648": {"question": "Applicants for the position of data manager are expected to have a minimum of three years ___ experience.", "1": "supervisors", "2": "supervisory", "3": "supervise", "4": "supervises", "answer": "supervisory"}, "3649": {"question": "The mayors speech at Mondays business breakfast ___ and will be broadcast later this week.", "1": "record", "2": "recording", "3": "being recorded", "4": "was recorded", "answer": "was recorded"}, "3650": {"question": "The researchers ___ tested different formulas until the desired results were achieved.", "1": "soon", "2": "suddenly", "3": "well", "4": "repeatedly", "answer": "repeatedly"}, "3651": {"question": "Loan specialists at Newton Bank can help your company ___ equipment purchases.", "1": "commit", "2": "associate", "3": "reserve", "4": "finance", "answer": "finance"}, "3652": {"question": "___ our partnership with Shox Gym, we are able to provide employees with a free membership to the fitness center.", "1": "After all", "2": "Because of", "3": "For this reason", "4": "As long as", "answer": "Because of"}, "3653": {"question": "Mr. Tran asked the department whether ___ could work overtime on Friday.", "1": "anyone", "2": "anywhere", "3": "anyway", "4": "anyhow", "answer": "anyone"}, "3654": {"question": "Canyonland Corporation will research the potential ___ of expanding its overseas market to East Africa.", "1": "deadline", "2": "availability", "3": "profitability", "4": "emphasis", "answer": "profitability"}, "3655": {"question": "Chef Linds cookbook, ___ will be available next week, contains only dessert recipes.", "1": "who", "2": "what", "3": "which", "4": "whose", "answer": "which"}, "3656": {"question": "Mr. Guo ___ with an electrician yesterday about the rewriting project.", "1": "consults", "2": "is consulting", "3": "to consults", "4": "consulted", "answer": "consulted"}, "3657": {"question": "Skymills Insurance ___ grew from a small business to a midsize company with 350 employees.", "1": "quick", "2": "quickly", "3": "quicker", "4": "quickest", "answer": "quickly"}, "3658": {"question": "Local shop owners are invited to the ___ of Clyde Banks downtown branch.", "1": "open", "2": "opened", "3": "opening", "4": "openly", "answer": "opening"}, "3659": {"question": "The ___ Ladoff Building was constructed in 1923 and stood two stories tall", "1": "origin", "2": "originated", "3": "originally", "4": "original", "answer": "original"}, "3660": {"question": "If you have questions about your most ___ credit card statement, call Mr. Hassan", "1": "central", "2": "consecutive", "3": "actual", "4": "recent", "answer": "recent"}, "3661": {"question": "Ms. Schwimmers application was not ___ reviewed until November 5.", "1": "relatively", "2": "occasionally", "3": "completely", "4": "enormously", "answer": "completely"}, "3662": {"question": "Deckermark Enterprises offers employees flexible scheduling and telecommuting ___.", "1": "statements", "2": "exchanges", "3": "precautions", "4": "options", "answer": "options"}, "3663": {"question": "he companys transition from paper paychecks to electronic paychecks was ___ smooth.", "1": "impressive", "2": "impression", "3": "impressively", "4": "impress", "answer": "impressively"}, "3664": {"question": "The client have indicated that a reception area of 60 square meters will be ------ in the new building.", "1": "sufficient", "2": "flexible", "3": "capable", "4": "calculating", "answer": "sufficient"}, "3665": {"question": "Ms. Lau would like to know ___ Mr. Cole called the main office yesterday", "1": "whatever", "2": "while", "3": "why", "4": "who", "answer": "why"}, "3666": {"question": "The newest edition of the Biltmire Road Atlas has plastic-coated pages for extra ___.", "1": "familiarity", "2": "persistence", "3": "durability", "4": "replacement", "answer": "durability"}, "3667": {"question": "- account will be credited after we receive the returned merchandise.", "1": "You", "2": "Yours", "3": "Your", "4": "Yourself", "answer": "Your"}, "3668": {"question": "The newspaper has seen an  in the number of subscribers who read the online version.", "1": "increase", "2": "increases", "3": "increasingly", "4": "increased", "answer": "increase"}, "3669": {"question": "Every attorney at the firm of Duncan and Hulce has practiced law  more than ten years.", "1": "at", "2": "for", "3": "on", "4": "by", "answer": "for"}, "3670": {"question": "Prethart Tool Company has created a more  drill than its previous models.", "1": "powerful", "2": "powers", "3": "powerfully", "4": "power", "answer": "powerful"}, "3671": {"question": "To find out if an item on this Web site is in stock, highlight the item and click the Check on it button.", "1": "mostly", "2": "simply", "3": "enough", "4": "quite", "answer": "simply"}, "3672": {"question": "Mr. JonesMs. Chengs clients while she is on a business trip to Hong Kong.", "1": "will assist", "2": "assisted", "3": "to assist", "4": "is assisted", "answer": "will assist"}, "3673": {"question": "The Jossty Company offers insurance policies to renters at the lowest rat es .", "1": "ready", "2": "strong", "3": "available", "4": "agreeable", "answer": "available"}, "3674": {"question": " the Editorial Department receives the authors final approval, the manuscript should be sent to the printer.", "1": "As soon as", "2": "Still", "3": "In the meantime", "4": "For example", "answer": "As soon as"}, "3675": {"question": "Sidewalks in the town of Newburgh a re - one meter wide.", "1": "general", "2": "generally", "3": "generalize", "4": "generalization", "answer": "generalization"}, "3676": {"question": "The housing authority has formed a - to look for new construction locations.", "1": "member", "2": "building", "3": "frontier", "4": "committee", "answer": "committee"}, "3677": {"question": "A recent study has found that those - regularly read food labels tend to be healthier.", "1": "what", "2": "where", "3": "who", "4": "when", "answer": "who"}, "3678": {"question": "If you are not - with your Electoshine toothbrush, you may return it for a full refund.", "1": "satisfaction", "2": "satisfying", "3": "satisfied", "4": "satisfy", "answer": "satisfied"}, "3679": {"question": "DG Feed Supply has shown strong growth heading  the end of the fiscal year.", "1": "among", "2": "into", "3": "around", "4": "between", "answer": "into"}, "3680": {"question": "Book fair volunteers may be asked to work longer shifts if the need  .", "1": "arise", "2": "arises", "3": "had arisen", "4": "arising", "answer": "arises"}, "3681": {"question": "On Tuesday, Mr. Molina will visit the Seoul office for the first time - becoming vice-president of operations.", "1": "under", "2": "past", "3": "until", "4": "since", "answer": "since"}, "3682": {"question": "Attendees said the fireworks were the most  part of the festival.", "1": "impression", "2": "impressive", "3": "impresses", "4": "impressed", "answer": "impressive"}, "3683": {"question": "The interview panel felt that Dinah Ongs education fit the job description of junior accountant- .", "1": "perfectly", "2": "recently", "3": "routinely", "4": "occasionally", "answer": "perfectly"}, "3684": {"question": "The new software makes it possible to track purchases  at multiple points-of-sale.", "1": "rely", "2": "reliable", "3": "reliant", "4": "reliably", "answer": "reliably"}, "3685": {"question": " the next few months, Camion Vehicles will add more features to its sedans.", "1": "Provided", "2": "Applying", "3": "Toward", "4": "Over", "answer": "Over"}, "3686": {"question": "Altona Printing is expecting a  upturn in holiday card orders in the next few weeks.", "1": "considerable", "2": "wide", "3": "central", "4": "dominant", "answer": "considerable"}, "3687": {"question": "By creating innovative packaging, EK2 Beverages hopes consumers will reuse their water bottles.", "1": "designed", "2": "designs", "3": "designing", "4": "designers", "answer": "designs"}, "3688": {"question": "Throughout her tenure at LPID Systems, Ms. Patterson has  at defining complex concepts in simple terms.", "1": "excelled", "2": "organized", "3": "instructed", "4": "simplified", "answer": "excelled"}, "3689": {"question": "Winslet Food Service has - to expand the cafeterias menu offerings.", "1": "promptly", "2": "before", "3": "although", "4": "promised", "answer": "promised"}, "3690": {"question": "- the results of the customer survey, we may consider extending the stores evening hours until 9 P.M.", "1": "Because", "2": "Depending on", "3": "Whereas", "4": "In order for", "answer": "Depending on"}, "3691": {"question": "Yerrow Cameras lenses have a long telephoto reach yet a n - lightweight casing.", "1": "exceptions", "2": "exception", "3": "excepting", "4": "exceptionally", "answer": "exceptionally"}, "3692": {"question": "After postponing her studies for many years, Ms.Ruiz - earned a degree in law.", "1": "thoroughly", "2": "distinctly", "3": "eventually", "4": "already", "answer": "eventually"}, "3693": {"question": "A favorable report on the  of Seesom Eyewear convinced the partners to invest in the company.", "1": "profitability", "2": "profitable", "3": "profited", "4": "profitably", "answer": "profitability"}, "3694": {"question": "In Mondays meeting, Mr.Ito - the need to hire enough workers for the peak season.", "1": "hesitated", "2": "emphasized", "3": "dominated", "4": "launched", "answer": "emphasized"}, "3695": {"question": "Pugh Tower won the Best New Building Award for its creative  of sustainable materials.", "1": "routine", "2": "accessory", "3": "incorporation", "4": "submission", "answer": "incorporation"}, "3696": {"question": "Departmental restructuring will be discussed at the ___ monthly meeting", "1": "next", "2": "always", "3": "soon", "4": "like", "answer": "next"}, "3697": {"question": "To keep ___ park beautiful, please place your nonrecyclables in the available trash cans", "1": "our", "2": "we", "3": "us", "4": "ours", "answer": "our"}, "3698": {"question": "Mr. Hardin ___ additional images of the office building he is interested in leasing", "1": "informed", "2": "asked", "3": "advised", "4": "requested", "answer": "requested"}, "3699": {"question": "A team of agricultural experts will be brought ___ to try to improve crop harvests", "1": "because", "2": "either", "3": "between", "4": "together", "answer": "together"}, "3700": {"question": "The board of Galaxipharm ___ Mr. Kwon's successor at yesterday's meeting", "1": "named", "2": "granted", "3": "founded", "4": "proved", "answer": "named"}, "3701": {"question": "If your parking permit is damaged, bring it to the entrance station for a ___", "1": "replacement", "2": "replacing", "3": "replace", "4": "replaces", "answer": "replacement"}, "3702": {"question": "Mr. Ahmad decided to reserve a private room for the awards dinner ___ the restaurant was noisy", "1": "rather than", "2": "in case", "3": "such as", "4": "unless", "answer": "in case"}, "3703": {"question": "Ms. Jones has provided a ___ estimate of the costs of expanding distribution statewide", "1": "conserve", "2": "conserves", "3": "conservative", "4": "conservatively", "answer": "conservative"}, "3704": {"question": "Each quarter, Acaba Exports sets ___ sales goals for its staff", "1": "compact", "2": "wealthy", "3": "faithful", "4": "realistic", "answer": "realistic"}, "3705": {"question": "Ms. Garcia was delighted to receive ___ that her company soon will be featured in the In Town Times magazine", "1": "notify", "2": "notification", "3": "notifying", "4": "notifies", "answer": "notification"}, "3706": {"question": "Children under five years of age are eligible ___ free vision tests", "1": "over", "2": "down", "3": "for", "4": "out", "answer": "for"}, "3707": {"question": "Drivers on the Partan Expressway are reminded to drive ___ throughout July because of the ongoing construction work", "1": "caution", "2": "cautiously", "3": "cautious", "4": "cautiousness", "answer": "cautiously"}, "3708": {"question": "The committee will resume its weekly meetings ___ Ms. Cheon returns from Scotland on September 17", "1": "that", "2": "once", "3": "as well", "4": "then", "answer": "once"}, "3709": {"question": "The ___ initiative aims to provide public transportation for commuters living in the outer suburbs", "1": "proposed", "2": "proposing", "3": "proposal", "4": "propose", "answer": "proposed"}, "3710": {"question": "Yesterday's storm ___ interrupted the services of the Duddula, Inc, satellite communications system", "1": "annually", "2": "anytime", "3": "whenever", "4": "temporarily", "answer": "temporarily"}, "3711": {"question": "Even though Cabrera Pictures and Marcella Images make very different films, ___ are successful movie studios", "1": "serveral", "2": "everybody", "3": "some", "4": "both", "answer": "both"}, "3712": {"question": "___ of tasks can make a manager's job easier and help other employees learn new skills", "1": "Reputation", "2": "Foundation", "3": "Delegation", "4": "Permission", "answer": "Delegation"}, "3713": {"question": "Proceeds from the sale of Delcrest Corporation were equally ___ among the founder's three daughters", "1": "divisions", "2": "dividing", "3": "divide", "4": "divided", "answer": "divided"}, "3714": {"question": "___ higher than average ticket prices, every performance of Aiden North's new play is sold out for the next six months", "1": "Throughout", "2": "Except for", "3": "Despite", "4": "Prior to", "answer": "Despite"}, "3715": {"question": "Ricardo Sosa, executive chef at Restaurant Ninal, responds to guests' suggestions ___", "1": "respect", "2": "respects", "3": "respectfully", "4": "respected", "answer": "respectfully"}, "3716": {"question": "Mr. Koster is negotiating the ___ of the new contract with Arban, Inc", "1": "scope", "2": "turn", "3": "grip", "4": "drive", "answer": "scope"}, "3717": {"question": "The equiment-use guidelines ___ on our internal corporate Website", "1": "may find", "2": "can be found", "3": "have found", "4": "have to find", "answer": "can be found"}, "3718": {"question": "Professor Han created spreadsheets to calculate the farm's irrigation needs ___", "1": "dominantly", "2": "precisely", "3": "relatively", "4": "widely", "answer": "precisely"}, "3719": {"question": "For hiring purposes, five years of professional experience is ___ to having achieved certification", "1": "reasonable", "2": "appropriate", "3": "equivalent", "4": "significant", "answer": "equivalent"}, "3720": {"question": "South Regent Aviation is adopting measures to reduce fuel expenses by ___", "1": "light", "2": "lighten", "3": "lightly", "4": "lightening", "answer": "lightening"}, "3721": {"question": "___ the most challenging aspect of accepting a new position is negotiating a salary that is both fair and satisfying", "1": "Perhaps", "2": "Outside", "3": "Every", "4": "While", "answer": "Perhaps"}, "3722": {"question": "Complaints about its new line of kitchen appliances led Loxevo, Inc., to adopt higher ___ for assessing quality", "1": "standards", "2": "features", "3": "risks", "4": "institutions", "answer": "standards"}, "3723": {"question": "The chief engineer noted that constructing another bridge would be more ___ than repairing the existing structure", "1": "economy", "2": "economics", "3": "economically", "4": "economical", "answer": "economical"}, "3724": {"question": "Jansen Bus Company drivers are expected to complete regular trainings ___ maintaining their state licenses", "1": "in addition to", "2": "according to", "3": "inside", "4": "within", "answer": "in addition to"}, "3725": {"question": "Ms. Desoto ___ all employees to come to last week's budget meeting even though only officers were obligated to attend", "1": "to have urged", "2": "had urged", "3": "will have urged", "4": "was urged", "answer": "had urged"}, "3726": {"question": "Ms. Villanueva has extensive experience in corporate ___ and budgeting", "1": "financially", "2": "financed", "3": "financial", "4": "finance", "answer": "finance"}, "3727": {"question": "Because Mr. Lewis works so ___ , he was given a pay raise", "1": "bright", "2": "hard", "3": "tight", "4": "sharp", "answer": "hard"}, "3728": {"question": "Full of old-fashioned charm, the Bronstad Inn ___ offers modern conveniences", "1": "plus", "2": "else", "3": "also", "4": "less", "answer": "also"}, "3729": {"question": "Franklin Bookstore will be moving next month ___ a larger location on Queen Street", "1": "to", "2": "at", "3": "out", "4": "over", "answer": "to"}, "3730": {"question": "Marina Hou ___ considered becoming an actor before deciding to write plays instead", "1": "briefly", "2": "briefs", "3": "briefing", "4": "briefed", "answer": "briefly"}, "3731": {"question": "On Fixit Time's Web site, homeowners will find economical solutions for ___ repairs", "1": "dark", "2": "broken", "3": "cleaning", "4": "common", "answer": "common"}, "3732": {"question": "Walter Keegan was ___ hired as a salesperson, but he soon became head of the marketing department", "1": "originality", "2": "original", "3": "originals", "4": "originally", "answer": "originally"}, "3733": {"question": "Durr Island has become popular with tourists ___ its rich culture of art and music", "1": "provided that", "2": "because of", "3": "even", "4": "how", "answer": "because of"}, "3734": {"question": "While he is not enthusiastic about the suggestions, Mr. Shang ___ them", "1": "considering", "2": "to consider", "3": "will consider", "4": "consider", "answer": "will consider"}, "3735": {"question": "The design ___ of Tavalyo Toys has been relocated to the company's headquarter", "1": "division", "2": "specification", "3": "allowance", "4": "construction", "answer": "division"}, "3736": {"question": "The Merrick Travel Agency organizes tours of national monuments and other ___ sites in the St. Petersburg area", "1": "historian", "2": "historic", "3": "historically", "4": "histories", "answer": "historic"}, "3737": {"question": "The MHS wireless speaker not only works with smartphones ___ is waterproof as well", "1": "but", "2": "and", "3": "however", "4": "besides", "answer": "but"}, "3738": {"question": "Assistant managers are largely responsible for the day-to-day operations in ___ departments", "1": "theirs", "2": "them", "3": "their", "4": "they", "answer": "their"}, "3739": {"question": "Customers must ___ review the terms of the fitness center's membership agreement before they sign it", "1": "smoothly", "2": "probably", "3": "legibly", "4": "thoroughly", "answer": "thoroughly"}, "3740": {"question": "We made a ___ estimate of how many tourists to expect in the coming month", "1": "conservative", "2": "conservation", "3": "conservatism", "4": "conservatively", "answer": "conservative"}, "3741": {"question": "Once they have completed three years of employment, the workers at Loruja ___ additional vacation time", "1": "reserve", "2": "earn", "3": "continue", "4": "find", "answer": "earn"}, "3742": {"question": "___ has time at the end of the day should make sure that all of the file cabinets are locked", "1": "Whom", "2": "Who", "3": "Whoever", "4": "Whose", "answer": "Whoever"}, "3743": {"question": "North River Linens promises next-day shipping ___ Asia", "1": "without", "2": "between", "3": "throughout", "4": "along", "answer": "throughout"}, "3744": {"question": "___ last year, the unpublished novel by Martin Sim has attracted intense interest from several publishing companies", "1": "Discover", "2": "Discovery", "3": "Discovered", "4": "Discovering", "answer": "Discovered"}, "3745": {"question": "Hoonton Realty clients can search property listings in ___ neighborhood by using a special online database", "1": "other", "2": "several", "3": "all", "4": "any", "answer": "any"}, "3746": {"question": "Exceptional service is what sets our hotels apart from those of our ___", "1": "compete", "2": "competing", "3": "competitive", "4": "competition", "answer": "competition"}, "3747": {"question": "The Internet connection will be closely monitored ___ the source of the slowdown can be confirmed", "1": "why", "2": "until", "3": "due to", "4": "just as", "answer": "until"}, "3748": {"question": "Thank you for being one of Danton Transportation's most ___ customers over the past ten years", "1": "valuation", "2": "valued", "3": "value", "4": "values", "answer": "valued"}, "3749": {"question": "Mr. Tang is a successful recruiter because he can quickly ___ talented sales agents from the rest", "1": "distinguish", "2": "persuade", "3": "alter", "4": "assist", "answer": "distinguish"}, "3750": {"question": "Ms. Penner assured us that ___ work stopped during the power failure, production targets would be met", "1": "although", "2": "at", "3": "her", "4": "never", "answer": "although"}, "3751": {"question": "Please provide the exact dimensions of the custom fence you would like built, and your quote will be adjusted ___", "1": "namely", "2": "accordingly", "3": "frequently", "4": "supposedly", "answer": "accordingly"}, "3752": {"question": "The vice president of Chestonville Bank believes that ___ employees is vital to the company's success", "1": "empowered", "2": "empower", "3": "empowering", "4": "empowers", "answer": "empowering"}, "3753": {"question": "The ___ for the city council's Monday meeting is posted on the municipal Web site by 3:00 P.M. on the preceding Friday", "1": "catalog", "2": "inventory", "3": "agenda", "4": "record", "answer": "agenda"}, "3754": {"question": "The building inspector declared the new facility ___ sound and ready to open", "1": "structured", "2": "structuring", "3": "structural", "4": "structurally", "answer": "structurally"}, "3755": {"question": "Dr. Huertas received the ___ Brighton Award for her groundbreaking work in plant biology", "1": "overwhelmed", "2": "intentional", "3": "prestigious", "4": "deserving", "answer": "prestigious"}, "3756": {"question": "Ms. Tillinghast has received several awards ___ her innovative ideas", "1": "away", "2": "for", "3": "often", "4": "across", "answer": "for"}, "3757": {"question": "Using proper techniques to ___ items drastically reduces the risk of back injury", "1": "select", "2": "lift", "3": "damage", "4": "attract", "answer": "lift"}, "3758": {"question": "Restaurants in Rondale must follow all ___ health guidelines", "1": "local", "2": "locals", "3": "locally", "4": "localize", "answer": "local"}, "3759": {"question": "Sinee's Catering is always ___ to deliver outstanding food to your special events", "1": "ready", "2": "skillful", "3": "complete", "4": "delicious", "answer": "ready"}, "3760": {"question": "A ___ way to support economic growth in Ludlow City is to shop at area businesses", "1": "practice", "2": "practicing", "3": "practical", "4": "practically", "answer": "practical"}, "3761": {"question": "A record number of appliance ___ came into the Port of Reece last month", "1": "shipments", "2": "shipping", "3": "shipment", "4": "shipped", "answer": "shipments"}, "3762": {"question": "At Sloat Publishing, interns are assigned to a ___ of positions with increasing responsibility", "1": "frequency", "2": "length", "3": "shortage", "4": "series", "answer": "series"}, "3763": {"question": "The conference fee ___ admittance to more than twenty workshops and seminars", "1": "include", "2": "includes", "3": "is included", "4": "including", "answer": "includes"}, "3764": {"question": "Cabinetmaker Finley Orcheta uses the finest woodworking machines imported ___ Denmark", "1": "from", "2": "against", "3": "about", "4": "before", "answer": "from"}, "3765": {"question": "Senior hotel manager salaries differ ___ by company, location, and experience", "1": "great", "2": "greater", "3": "greatly", "4": "greatest", "answer": "greatly"}, "3766": {"question": "Pantep, Inc., works ___ with customers to establish long-term partnerships", "1": "nearly", "2": "closely", "3": "recently", "4": "newly", "answer": "closely"}, "3767": {"question": "Adalet Farm's unique method of irrigating vegetables has proved to be ___ effective", "1": "far", "2": "correctly", "3": "highly", "4": "much", "answer": "highly"}, "3768": {"question": "Customers who submit payments ___ March 10 will be charged a late fee", "1": "after", "2": "behind", "3": "quite", "4": "almost", "answer": "after"}, "3769": {"question": "The poll shows how often company executives make financial decisions that are ___ by employee opinions", "1": "acted", "2": "trained", "3": "reminded", "4": "influenced", "answer": "influenced"}, "3770": {"question": "Prices at Taylor City Books are ___ lower than at other online bookstores", "1": "more significant", "2": "significant", "3": "significance", "4": "significantly", "answer": "significantly"}, "3771": {"question": "The ___ of this workshop is to equip business leaders with the tools to make prudent financial decisions", "1": "guide", "2": "experience", "3": "aim", "4": "solution", "answer": "aim"}, "3772": {"question": "A marketing campaign was designed to target ___ of the three demographics we identified", "1": "which", "2": "other", "3": "either", "4": "each", "answer": "each"}, "3773": {"question": "___ food critics recommend ZJ's Bistro as the best restaurant in the area, most local residents prefer Dree's Cafe", "1": "Whenever", "2": "Although", "3": "So that", "4": "Among", "answer": "Although"}, "3774": {"question": "Green Grocer customers should request assistance from staff instead of removing products from the top shelves ___", "1": "themselves", "2": "their own", "3": "them", "4": "their", "answer": "themselves"}, "3775": {"question": "Skovent Products' sales revenue showed a ___ improvement at the end of last quarter", "1": "respective", "2": "crowded", "3": "marked", "4": "diverse", "answer": "marked"}, "3776": {"question": "Before work can begin at the construction site, the ___ permit applications must be processed", "1": "relevant", "2": "relevantly", "3": "relevance", "4": "relevancies", "answer": "relevant"}, "3777": {"question": "During negotiations, Mr. DuPont insisted that price ___ be implemented without delay", "1": "expectations", "2": "institutions", "3": "sensations", "4": "reductions", "answer": "reductions"}, "3778": {"question": "After the team meeting next week, Ms. Li ___ whether the project deadline needs to be changed", "1": "to decide", "2": "deciding", "3": "will decide", "4": "has decided", "answer": "will decide"}, "3779": {"question": "___ the proposal for the Southside Library garden was incomplete and had an unclear timetable, it was rejected", "1": "Until", "2": "Because", "3": "While", "4": "Unless", "answer": "Because"}, "3780": {"question": "As the rental agreement with the Smith Group is set ___ soon, the available office space can be advertised", "1": "expired", "2": "to expire", "3": "will have expired", "4": "expiring", "answer": "to expire"}, "3781": {"question": "Any furniture purchased at Marty's Superstore throughout February will be delivered ___ five business days", "1": "since", "2": "between", "3": "within", "4": "above", "answer": "within"}, "3782": {"question": "The manager presented data on employee performance with ___ on measurable achievements", "1": "emphatic", "2": "emphasis", "3": "emphasize", "4": "emphasized", "answer": "emphasis"}, "3783": {"question": "Even employees who ___ were not familiar with the new software program have found it easy to use", "1": "initially", "2": "annually", "3": "successfully", "4": "inadvertently", "answer": "initially"}, "3784": {"question": "Supervisors will not ___ approve time off for employees during peak operational months", "1": "generalization", "2": "generalize", "3": "generally", "4": "general", "answer": "generally"}, "3785": {"question": "Toronto is one of three cities being ___ as the host for the next convention of the Global Society of Accountants", "1": "found", "2": "categorized", "3": "known", "4": "considered", "answer": "considered"}, "3786": {"question": "Ms. Carpenter will be attending the conference with ___ marketing team", "1": "she", "2": "her", "3": "hers", "4": "herself", "answer": "her"}, "3787": {"question": "___ the last ten years, Bay City's population has grown by about 27 percent", "1": "As", "2": "Against", "3": "During", "4": "Below", "answer": "Below"}, "3788": {"question": "Please congratulate Alan Schmit, ___ of the Leadership Award in Nursing at Knoll Hospital", "1": "won", "2": "wins", "3": "winning", "4": "winner", "answer": "winner"}, "3789": {"question": "Ireland's largest software producer will ___ be opening a large facility in Cork", "1": "soon", "2": "such", "3": "ever", "4": "like", "answer": "soon"}, "3790": {"question": "Ashburn Bank's online service has been in high demand ___", "1": "lateness", "2": "later", "3": "lately", "4": "latest", "answer": "lately"}, "3791": {"question": "The ___ of videos to electronic press releases can help companies showcase their products", "1": "content", "2": "addition", "3": "pictures", "4": "promotion", "answer": "addition"}, "3792": {"question": "Ms. Hyun is reviewing the training manual to see if updates ___", "1": "have need", "2": "needing", "3": "are needed", "4": "to be needed", "answer": "are needed"}, "3793": {"question": "When leaving the auditorium, please exit ___ the doors on the lower level", "1": "except", "2": "inside", "3": "without", "4": "through", "answer": "through"}, "3794": {"question": "The judges for this year's screenplay competition include ___ from Hanovi Studios", "1": "represents", "2": "representatives", "3": "represented", "4": "represent", "answer": "representatives"}, "3795": {"question": "I have attached my resume detailing my ___ experience in the hotel industry", "1": "extensive", "2": "punctual", "3": "prospective", "4": "accepted", "answer": "extensive"}, "3796": {"question": "Remember to check the spelling of Mr. Kamashi 's name when ___ the document", "1": "revising", "2": "revises", "3": "revised", "4": "revise", "answer": "revising"}, "3797": {"question": "Residents visited City Hall to ask ___ developers will preserve the historic properties", "1": "although", "2": "since", "3": "whether", "4": "both", "answer": "whether"}, "3798": {"question": "The Ford Group's proposed advertising campaign is by far the most ___ we have seen so far", "1": "innovate", "2": "innovative", "3": "innovations", "4": "innovatively", "answer": "innovative"}, "3799": {"question": "Solei Landscaping announced that the design for the Cherry Hill building complex is ___ complete", "1": "almost", "2": "nearby", "3": "anytime", "4": "yet", "answer": "almost"}, "3800": {"question": "Daniel Nishida, the chief supply officer, asked that ___ be given full responsibility for approving all invoices", "1": "he", "2": "him", "3": "his", "4": "himself", "answer": "he"}, "3801": {"question": "In preparation for Mr. Kumar's retirement at the end of March, the Carolex Corporation will need to ___ a new facilities director", "1": "resume", "2": "compete", "3": "recruit", "4": "conduct", "answer": "recruit"}, "3802": {"question": "The team's contributions to the Ripton Group's marketing plan were very ___ acknowledged", "1": "favor", "2": "favorably", "3": "favorable", "4": "favored", "answer": "favorably"}, "3803": {"question": "___ receiving the engineering award, Ms. Kwon made a point of thanking longtime mentors", "1": "Onto", "2": "Unlike", "3": "About", "4": "Upon", "answer": "Upon"}, "3804": {"question": "Please read the list of ___ qualifications to ensure that you have the necessary education and experience for the position", "1": "slight", "2": "equal", "3": "obliged", "4": "essential", "answer": "essential"}, "3805": {"question": "Choosing the best software tool to eliminate computer viruses is rarely simple, ___ it is important to seek expert advice", "1": "why", "2": "then", "3": "nor", "4": "so", "answer": "so"}, "3806": {"question": "Ms. Delgado would like to meet with all loan officers ___ reviewing any more loan applications", "1": "now that", "2": "as though", "3": "before", "4": "often", "answer": "before"}, "3807": {"question": "Cedar Branch Hill has a ___ as a business-friendly environment that provides efficient licensing and other legal processes", "1": "prediction", "2": "courtesy", "3": "reputation", "4": "statement", "answer": "reputation"}, "3808": {"question": "The actors held an additional rehearsal ___ perfect their performance in the final scene", "1": "considerably", "2": "in order to", "3": "nevertheless", "4": "as a result of", "answer": "in order to"}, "3809": {"question": "RZT Technology will double the size of its Toronto laboratory to ___ the organization's rapid growth", "1": "assign", "2": "investigate", "3": "experience", "4": "accommodate", "answer": "accommodate"}, "3810": {"question": "Even though Smithton Electronics' second quarter was not ___ , the company plans to invest large sums on research", "1": "profitable", "2": "profiting", "3": "profitability", "4": "profitably", "answer": "profitable"}, "3811": {"question": "The Williamsport Hotel is an ideal venue for the conference because of its ___ to the airport", "1": "achievement", "2": "proximity", "3": "competence", "4": "exception", "answer": "proximity"}, "3812": {"question": "The second training session is for employees ___ responsibilities include processing payroll forms", "1": "whose", "2": "which", "3": "what", "4": "who", "answer": "whose"}, "3813": {"question": "___ poorly the high-speed printer may be functioning, it is still making copies that are adequate for our purposes", "1": "Rather", "2": "Seldom", "3": "However", "4": "Thoroughly", "answer": "However"}, "3814": {"question": "The long-awaited Weka 2XG digital camera will finally be ___ at a product exhibition on August 16", "1": "reduced", "2": "unveiled", "3": "consulted", "4": "resolved", "answer": "unveiled"}, "3815": {"question": "Northeast Community Finance ___ an online system in order to shorten service lines at branch locations", "1": "has implemented", "2": "to be implementing", "3": "to have been implementing", "4": "is implemented", "answer": "has implemented"}, "3816": {"question": "The review board published a list of companies ___ considers to be the most charitable.", "1": "it", "2": "its", "3": "itself", "4": "its own", "answer": "it"}, "3817": {"question": "Anyone who was unable to ___ yesterdays budget meeting may contact Mr. Kwon for his notes.", "1": "recognize", "2": "achieve", "3": "attend", "4": "inform", "answer": "attend"}, "3818": {"question": "The evenings dance ___ was made possible with support from Taglets Emporium.", "1": "presented", "2": "presents", "3": "presenting", "4": "presentation", "answer": "presentation"}, "3819": {"question": "All ___ candidates for the marketing position should submit a cover letter and rsum", "1": "increasing", "2": "qualified", "3": "beneficial", "4": "modified", "answer": "qualified"}, "3820": {"question": "Because experts ___ a strong allergy season, Chowlan Pharmacy has increased its stock of preventative medicine.", "1": "predict", "2": "prediction", "3": "are predicted", "4": "edictably", "answer": "predict"}, "3821": {"question": "The mayor applauded the Wilton Clinic ___ its leadership in promoting the citys public health programs.", "1": "at", "2": "for", "3": "of", "4": "to", "answer": "for"}, "3822": {"question": "Liao Uniform Services has been a leading ___ of medical apparel for more than 30 years.", "1": "supplies", "2": "supplying", "3": "supplier", "4": "supplied", "answer": "supplier"}, "3823": {"question": "Please adjust the budget to include the ___ of a fountain in the garden.", "1": "schedule", "2": "determination", "3": "result", "4": "installation", "answer": "installation"}, "3824": {"question": "The speed limit on all ___ streets in Benton has been changed to 40 kilometers per hour.", "1": "residential", "2": "residing", "3": "residences", "4": "residentially", "answer": "residential"}, "3825": {"question": "___ visitors generally prefer to set their own pace, the aquarium now offers user-friendly audio tours.", "1": "Except", "2": "Since", "3": "How", "4": "That", "answer": "Since"}, "3826": {"question": "The salmon dish at Salias Caf ___ with a brown sugar, mustard, and pepper glaze.", "1": "to serve", "2": "will serve", "3": "is served", "4": "was serving", "answer": "is served"}, "3827": {"question": "Due to the uneven terrain of the Chilman Trail, proper hiking footwear is ___ recommended.", "1": "closely", "2": "highly", "3": "nearly", "4": "roughly", "answer": "highly"}, "3828": {"question": "Visitors may tour the new printing plant facilities ___ the hours of 4 P.M. and 6 P.M.", "1": "always", "2": "between", "3": "in", "4": "only", "answer": "between"}, "3829": {"question": "Given the current economic climate, Playablanca Financial is ___ to make new acquisitions.", "1": "hesitant", "2": "delinquent", "3": "worthy", "4": "empty", "answer": "hesitant"}, "3830": {"question": "Mr. Fitzpatrick memorized his lines ___ weeks before the filming of the movie began.", "1": "perfectly", "2": "perfected", "3": "perfect", "4": "perfecting", "answer": "perfectly"}, "3831": {"question": "Ms. Amari has scanned the grant applications, and they will be submitted ___ the deadline.", "1": "along", "2": "over", "3": "during", "4": "before", "answer": "before"}, "3832": {"question": "Good design and quality material are ___ important to Krasner Laboratorys product development team.", "1": "gradually", "2": "enough", "3": "equally", "4": "well", "answer": "equally"}, "3833": {"question": "We make our ___ of pet treats with only the best ingredients.", "1": "usage", "2": "line", "3": "result", "4": "addition", "answer": "line"}, "3834": {"question": "Dr. Wu provides patients with exceptional dental care at an ___ price.", "1": "affords", "2": "affordable", "3": "affordably", "4": "affordability", "answer": "affordable"}, "3835": {"question": "___ two additional designers are hired, current staffers will not need to work overtime to complete projects on time.", "1": "Whether", "2": "Already", "3": "Instead", "4": "If", "answer": "If"}, "3836": {"question": "All safety policies will be ___ reviewed by the Human Resources Department before publication.", "1": "extensively", "2": "extensive", "3": "extension", "4": "extending", "answer": "extensively"}, "3837": {"question": "Some roadside farmers markets in Dublin run year-round, while others ___ only in the summer and fall.", "1": "grow", "2": "operate", "3": "raise", "4": "promise", "answer": "operate"}, "3838": {"question": "We do not have enough fabric samples, so please promptly return ___ ones you borrowed.", "1": "what", "2": "whomever", "3": "whichever", "4": "whose", "answer": "whichever"}, "3839": {"question": "___ it does not rain tomorrow, tents will be set up for any scheduled outdoor events", "1": "Though", "2": "Even if", "3": "Almost", "4": "Besides that", "answer": "Even if"}, "3840": {"question": "The network is expected to be unavailable for ___ two hours.", "1": "no more than", "2": "hardly any", "3": "as far as", "4": "that many", "answer": "no more than"}, "3841": {"question": "Consumer advocates advise against blindly accepting ___ opinions about a product.", "1": "total", "2": "biased", "3": "profitable", "4": "competitive", "answer": "biased"}, "3842": {"question": "___ of tasks makes a supervisors job easier and helps team members learn new skills", "1": "Promotion", "2": "Commission", "3": "Provision", "4": "Delegation", "answer": "Delegation"}, "3843": {"question": "Scientists at Lipkin Pharmaceuticals described findings similar to those reported ___.", "1": "elsewhere", "2": "beyond", "3": "furthermore", "4": "wherever", "answer": "elsewhere"}, "3844": {"question": "All four walls of the greenhouse ___ of fully tempered glass.", "1": "construct", "2": "constructing", "3": "have constructed", "4": "will be constructed", "answer": "will be constructed"}, "3845": {"question": "The increase in tourism in Mariondale can be ___ to the various attractions the city has added in recent years.", "1": "deducted", "2": "deducted", "3": "attributed", "4": "amplified", "answer": "attributed"}, "3846": {"question": "Mr. Srours flight arrived ___ late for him to attend the reception.", "1": "so", "2": "ever", "3": "too", "4": "already", "answer": "too"}, "3847": {"question": "___ the final award had been presented, Ms. Ryu acknowledged the support of the events sponsors.", "1": "During", "2": "Then", "3": "After", "4": "Next", "answer": "After"}, "3848": {"question": "Press lightly ___ the pedal with your left foot to release the vehicles parking brake.", "1": "up", "2": "on", "3": "of", "4": "in", "answer": "on"}, "3849": {"question": "Hikers are invited ___ the information center for trail maps of Far Valley Park.", "1": "visiting", "2": "to visit", "3": "visits", "4": "having visited", "answer": "to visit"}, "3850": {"question": "Iolana Dance Troupe stands out because the group knows ___ to integrate a variety of dance styles.", "1": "how", "2": "that", "3": "since", "4": "about", "answer": "how"}, "3851": {"question": "Taste tests suggest that most people ___ Dairysmooths red-bean-flavored ice cream very appetizing.", "1": "find", "2": "feel", "3": "take", "4": "like", "answer": "find"}, "3852": {"question": "___ the Nye Research Center, performing assigned duties for 30 minutes while standing increases productivity", "1": "Not only", "2": "In case of", "3": "As though", "4": "According to", "answer": "According to"}, "3853": {"question": "Mondays workshop will help restaurant owners ___ their ability to effectively recruit, train, and retain staff", "1": "cover", "2": "prepare", "3": "progress", "4": "evaluate", "answer": "evaluate"}, "3854": {"question": "Although the desk was slightly damaged during assembly, it is still ___.", "1": "function", "2": "functional", "3": "functionally", "4": "functioned", "answer": "functional"}, "3855": {"question": "___ its discounts for new customers, Teratran Phones service plans are considered inferior by many.", "1": "Far from", "2": "Despite", "3": "Among", "4": "Instead of", "answer": "Despite"}, "3856": {"question": "The Ortimate 3 home theater system is Hyong Electronics most ___ priced configuration.", "1": "closely", "2": "sparsely", "3": "reasonably", "4": "absolutely", "answer": "reasonably"}, "3857": {"question": "The Oamwood Restaurant ___ a special dinner menu on Saturdays for the past decade.", "1": "is offering", "2": "has been offering", "3": "will be offering", "4": "would have been offering", "answer": "has been offering"}, "3858": {"question": "Mr. de Tonnancour has a speaking ___ on Tuesday, November 15", "1": "engagement", "2": "term", "3": "subject", "4": "employment", "answer": "engagement"}, "3859": {"question": "The event planner determined that Tuesdays forum will require ___ chairs.", "1": "addition", "2": "additions", "3": "additional", "4": "additionally", "answer": "additional"}, "3860": {"question": "All sales staff are asked to acknowledge their -- ----- in Mondays workshop.", "1": "participate", "2": "participates", "3": "participated", "4": "participation", "answer": "participation"}, "3861": {"question": "The commercial for Zhous Caf was ___ Sunn Agencys best advertisement of the year.", "1": "easy", "2": "ease", "3": "easiest", "4": "easily", "answer": "easily"}, "3862": {"question": "Use coupon code SAVE20 to purchase --- ---- perfume or cologne for 20 percent off.", "1": "any", "2": "few", "3": "single", "4": "many", "answer": "any"}, "3863": {"question": "Talk-Talk Cell Phone Company will soon be merging with its main ___.", "1": "competitor", "2": "competing", "3": "competitive", "4": "competitively", "answer": "competitor"}, "3864": {"question": "Last month we received numerous ---- --- comments from customers on our blog.", "1": "eventual", "2": "probable", "3": "close", "4": "positive", "answer": "positive"}, "3865": {"question": "Beginning on August 1, patients will be asked to complete a short survey ___ each visit", "1": "inside", "2": "after", "3": "where", "4": "whenever", "answer": "after"}, "3866": {"question": "Although the parts are made in China, the ----- -- of Jamy bicycles is done in Canada.", "1": "vision", "2": "meeting", "3": "approach", "4": "assembly", "answer": "assembly"}, "3867": {"question": "Many businesses promote carpooling ___ traffic", "1": "is prevented", "2": "prevent", "3": "to prevent", "4": "prevented", "answer": "to prevent"}, "3868": {"question": "------ the repairs are complete, only essential personnel are allowed in the building", "1": "Despite", "2": "Finally", "3": "Until", "4": "During", "answer": "Until"}, "3869": {"question": "An ------ to renovate the old factory was submitted to the city council.", "1": "application", "2": "establishment", "3": "experience", "4": "accomplishment", "answer": "application"}, "3870": {"question": "Mr. Wijaya is reviewing the rsum to select the candidate best ----- -- for the position.", "1": "qualify", "2": "qualifications", "3": "qualifying", "4": "qualified", "answer": "qualified"}, "3871": {"question": "Tourists praise Navala Citys world-class beaches ___ its historical attractions", "1": "as well as", "2": "yet", "3": "so that", "4": "when", "answer": "as well as"}, "3872": {"question": "Mr. Chandling will cover any timesensitive work ___ Mr. Tan is on vacation.", "1": "along", "2": "besides", "3": "while", "4": "then", "answer": "while"}, "3873": {"question": "Last year, the city ___ nearly 500 building permits to smallbusiness owners.", "1": "regarded", "2": "issued", "3": "performed", "4": "constructed", "answer": "issued"}, "3874": {"question": "Local merchants are hopeful that if this new business succeeds, ----- will also benefit.", "1": "theirs", "2": "them", "3": "their", "4": "themselves", "answer": "theirs"}, "3875": {"question": "Following the retirement of Mr. Whalen, the company - ------ a search for a new CEO", "1": "connected", "2": "launched", "3": "persuaded", "4": "treated", "answer": "launched"}, "3876": {"question": "Ms. Travaglini filed the paperwork with the facilities department -- ----- a week ago.", "1": "beyond", "2": "over", "3": "past", "4": "through", "answer": "over"}, "3877": {"question": "After the lease ___, customers have the option of purchasing the car or returning it to their local dealer.", "1": "expired", "2": "is expiring", "3": "will be expiring", "4": "expires", "answer": "expires"}, "3878": {"question": "Please contact the product distributor, not the retail store, if ___ need replacement parts", "1": "your", "2": "you", "3": "yourself", "4": "yours", "answer": "you"}, "3879": {"question": "AGU Group's insurance rates have remained steady ___ the last three years", "1": "at", "2": "by", "3": "to", "4": "for", "answer": "for"}, "3880": {"question": "Sage Bistro's menu features a ___ variety of seafood items than Almaner Pavilion's", "1": "wide", "2": "widest", "3": "wider", "4": "widely", "answer": "wider"}, "3881": {"question": "Frequent training enables our technicians to resolve most computer problems ___", "1": "swiftly", "2": "avoidably", "3": "doubtfully", "4": "rigidly", "answer": "swiftly"}, "3882": {"question": "Most of the manufacturing sector has reported higher profits as a result of the trade ___", "1": "agreement", "2": "agreeing", "3": "agreeably", "4": "agrees", "answer": "agreement"}, "3883": {"question": "The cooking instructions call for reducing the heat and letting the sauce simmer ___ it thickens", "1": "whereas", "2": "likewise", "3": "instead", "4": "until", "answer": "until"}, "3884": {"question": "The Cullingford Bridge took a ___ short amount of time to be repaired", "1": "surprise", "2": "surprisingly", "3": "surprising", "4": "surprised", "answer": "surprisingly"}, "3885": {"question": "The company's summer picnic is ___ held outside town, in Warren County Lakeside Park", "1": "apart", "2": "always", "3": "much", "4": "far", "answer": "always"}, "3886": {"question": "Ms. Navarro wants to fill the administrative assistant ___ as soon as possible", "1": "worker", "2": "employment", "3": "position", "4": "experience", "answer": "position"}, "3887": {"question": "The item that Ms. Bak ordered from our catalog is ___ until 16 October", "1": "unavailable", "2": "occupied", "3": "uneventful", "4": "delivered", "answer": "unavailable"}, "3888": {"question": "Kespi Brand cookies, delicious by ___ , are even better when paired with a glass of milk", "1": "they", "2": "theirs", "3": "them", "4": "themselves", "answer": "themselves"}, "3889": {"question": "The North India Electricians Association ___ various online courses covering licensure, safety, and technology", "1": "offers", "2": "takes", "3": "pays", "4": "allows", "answer": "offers"}, "3890": {"question": "The latest survey shows that our downtown store is more ___ for local shoppers than our suburban location", "1": "conveniences", "2": "conveniently", "3": "convenience", "4": "convenient", "answer": "convenient"}, "3891": {"question": "Weaving Fire is the most popular television show ___ women ages 18 - 34", "1": "among", "2": "toward", "3": "within", "4": "along", "answer": "among"}, "3892": {"question": "___ a designer has completed a prototype product, the rest of the team will be invited to critique it", "1": "So that", "2": "Whether", "3": "From", "4": "After", "answer": "After"}, "3893": {"question": "Rather than archiving routine e-mails, please delete them ___", "1": "especially", "2": "likewise", "3": "quite", "4": "instead", "answer": "instead"}, "3894": {"question": "Mr. Khana made a phone call yesterday during which he ___ for the delay in the shipment of the clothing order", "1": "to apologize", "2": "apologized", "3": "apologize", "4": "will be apologizing", "answer": "apologized"}, "3895": {"question": "Following many months of research, the marketing team finally decided on a ___ for the new perfume bottle", "1": "force", "2": "style", "3": "belief", "4": "request", "answer": "style"}, "3896": {"question": "For more information about product warranties or ___ your new appliance, please contact customer service", "1": "to register", "2": "registered", "3": "registers", "4": "registration", "answer": "to register"}, "3897": {"question": "There will be a software upgrade tomorrow, ___ please back up any important files you have stored on the server", "1": "rather", "2": "while", "3": "so", "4": "because", "answer": "so"}, "3898": {"question": "Ambassador Chaturvedi wrote in his memoir that his parents taught him to do each job well, ___ it was", "1": "whoever", "2": "anyone", "3": "everything", "4": "whatever", "answer": "whatever"}, "3899": {"question": "Yields from your garden will ___ rise as you add Natrium Compost to the soil", "1": "steady", "2": "steadying", "3": "steadily", "4": "steadier", "answer": "steadily"}, "3900": {"question": "The Tokyo division handles product ___ and customer service for the company", "1": "distribute", "2": "distributor", "3": "distribution", "4": "distributed", "answer": "distribution"}, "3901": {"question": "Our newest executive assistant will be responsible for ___ between the marketing and accounting departments", "1": "coordination", "2": "attention", "3": "appreciation", "4": "consideration", "answer": "coordination"}, "3902": {"question": "Hemlin Corporation is looking for a sales representative ___ primary role will be expanding business in the northwest region", "1": "that", "2": "whose", "3": "who", "4": "which", "answer": "whose"}, "3903": {"question": "To eliminate ___ inventory of winter outerwear, Ashley Fashions has cut prices on all coats, hats, and scarves", "1": "chilly", "2": "adequate", "3": "excess", "4": "revised", "answer": "excess"}, "3904": {"question": "Search the Labesse Financial Web site for the most current and detailed ___ of investment options", "1": "explain", "2": "explanation", "3": "to explain", "4": "explainable", "answer": "explanation"}, "3905": {"question": "The last paragraph ___ to have been added to the contract as an afterthought", "1": "arranged", "2": "permitted", "3": "transferred", "4": "appeared", "answer": "appeared"}, "3906": {"question": "Unless the shipment of tiles arrives early, work on the lobby floor ___ after the holiday", "1": "has commenced", "2": "commencing", "3": "will commence", "4": "commenced", "answer": "will commence"}, "3907": {"question": "Neeson Progarments are made of a synthetic blend that is ___ to staining", "1": "exposed", "2": "automatic", "3": "limited", "4": "vulnerable", "answer": "vulnerable"}, "3908": {"question": "If ___ are not satisfied with an item, return it for a full refund within 30 days of purchase", "1": "you", "2": "your", "3": "yours", "4": "yourself", "answer": "you"}, "3909": {"question": "The location of next month's online gaming forum is yet to be ___", "1": "concluded", "2": "prevented", "3": "invited", "4": "decided", "answer": "decided"}, "3910": {"question": "Guests were ___ with the table decorations for the company banquet", "1": "impressive", "2": "impressed", "3": "impressing", "4": "impressively", "answer": "impressed"}, "3911": {"question": "The Shubert Company is ___ effective at helping power plants reduce their carbon dioxide emissions", "1": "once", "2": "far", "3": "early", "4": "very", "answer": "very"}, "3912": {"question": "Mr. Hodges ___ that volunteers sign up to assist with the Hannock River cleanup by Friday", "1": "requesting", "2": "to be requested", "3": "requests", "4": "to request", "answer": "requests"}, "3913": {"question": "Last year, the Daejeon English News ___ the number of readers by adding a digital subscription option", "1": "needed", "2": "increased", "3": "joined", "4": "asked", "answer": "increased"}, "3914": {"question": "Before the updated design can go into ___ , it must be approved by management", "1": "product", "2": "producer", "3": "productive", "4": "production", "answer": "production"}, "3915": {"question": "The economic development summit will be held ___ the Xi'an Trade Tower on September 22", "1": "to", "2": "at", "3": "down", "4": "of", "answer": "at"}, "3916": {"question": "Inclement weather was ___ responsible for the low turnout at Saturday's Exton Music Festival", "1": "largely", "2": "large", "3": "largest", "4": "larger", "answer": "largely"}, "3917": {"question": "Our most recent survey was sent to clients just last week, ___ it is too soon to send another one", "1": "when", "2": "since", "3": "so", "4": "finally", "answer": "so"}, "3918": {"question": "___ necklace that is shipped from Gillis Designers is given a thorough quality check", "1": "Whenever", "2": "Also", "3": "All", "4": "Each", "answer": "Each"}, "3919": {"question": "Ms. Valdez' sales numbers are good ___ for her to be considered for the employee-of-the-month award", "1": "forward", "2": "even", "3": "ahead", "4": "enough", "answer": "enough"}, "3920": {"question": "Aaron Park's new book features photographs of homes designed and built by the homeowners ___", "1": "itself", "2": "himself", "3": "themselves", "4": "ourselves", "answer": "themselves"}, "3921": {"question": "It is ___ for the audience to hold its applause until the speaker has finished", "1": "enthusiastic", "2": "casual", "3": "exclusive", "4": "customary", "answer": "customary"}, "3922": {"question": "Despite ___ that Legend Air would perform poorly with the entry of cheaper competition, it posted strong second-quarter earnings", "1": "predicted", "2": "predictable", "3": "predicts", "4": "predictions", "answer": "predictions"}, "3923": {"question": "Mr. Nigam was ___ retirement when his boss asked him to be the head of security at the new facility", "1": "under", "2": "ahead of", "3": "nearby", "4": "close to", "answer": "close to"}, "3924": {"question": "Main Street Restaurant offers a menu of ___ prepared lunch and dinner meals", "1": "thought", "2": "thoughtfulness", "3": "thoughts", "4": "thoughtfully", "answer": "thoughtfully"}, "3925": {"question": "___ our public relations manager, Ms. Ghazarian has just been appointed vice president of media relations", "1": "Sincerely", "2": "Immediately", "3": "Solely", "4": "Formerly", "answer": "Formerly"}, "3926": {"question": "Videos of Korean pop music have become very popular ___ adolescents worldwide", "1": "including", "2": "whereas", "3": "among", "4": "within", "answer": "among"}, "3927": {"question": "Milante Shoes ___ altered the firm's marketing strategy after a recent economic shift", "1": "quick", "2": "quickest", "3": "quickly", "4": "quicken", "answer": "quickly"}, "3928": {"question": "The annual report has been posted online, ___ the director's office has not yet received a printed copy", "1": "but", "2": "why", "3": "with", "4": "once", "answer": "but"}, "3929": {"question": "Hasin Fariz turned a study on the ___ effects of sleep into a best-selling book", "1": "favorable", "2": "favor", "3": "favors", "4": "favorably", "answer": "favorable"}, "3930": {"question": "Wynston Containers is ___ a yearly shutdown of its factory so that it can be evaluated for safety and efficiency", "1": "involving", "2": "participating", "3": "implementing", "4": "producing", "answer": "implementing"}, "3931": {"question": "The Girard Botanical Archive has almost 300,000 plant ___ , all neatly pressed onto archival paper", "1": "authorities", "2": "specimens", "3": "founders", "4": "specifics", "answer": "specimens"}, "3932": {"question": "Hotels and universities are ___ to recycle their used mattresses through the city's recycling program", "1": "systematic", "2": "eligible", "3": "familiar", "4": "successful", "answer": "eligible"}, "3933": {"question": "The ___ to review plans to replace the Tronton Bridge will be scheduled soon", "1": "heard", "2": "hears", "3": "hearing", "4": "hear", "answer": "hearing"}, "3934": {"question": "Kovox Ltd. aims to optimize quality ___ reducing the impact on the environment", "1": "which", "2": "while", "3": "because", "4": "unless", "answer": "while"}, "3935": {"question": "The grocery store ___ vegetables from out of town until local prices went down last month", "1": "is buying", "2": "will be buying", "3": "has been buying", "4": "had been buying", "answer": "had been buying"}, "3936": {"question": "All Hershel Industries employees must have a valid ID card ___ enter the building", "1": "in order to", "2": "as long as", "3": "regarding", "4": "always", "answer": "in order to"}, "3937": {"question": "___ and cost factored equally in choosing Cantavox as our main supplier", "1": "Reliability", "2": "Allowance", "3": "Dependence", "4": "Estimation", "answer": "Reliability"}, "3938": {"question": "The regional manager will arrive tomorrow, so please ensure that all ___ documents are ready", "1": "she", "2": "her", "3": "hers", "4": "herself", "answer": "her"}, "3939": {"question": "The historic Waldridge Building was constructed nearly 200 years ___", "1": "away", "2": "enough", "3": "ago", "4": "still", "answer": "ago"}, "3940": {"question": "Consumers ___ enthusiastically to the new colors developed by Sanwell Paint", "1": "responding", "2": "response", "3": "responsively", "4": "responded", "answer": "responded"}, "3941": {"question": "The ___ files contain your employment contract and information about our company", "1": "directed", "2": "attached", "3": "interested", "4": "connected", "answer": "attached"}, "3942": {"question": "Please submit each reimbursement request ___ according to its category, as outlined in last month's memo", "1": "separately", "2": "separateness", "3": "separates", "4": "separate", "answer": "separately"}, "3943": {"question": "Customers can wait in the reception area ___ our mechanics complete the car repairs", "1": "whether", "2": "except", "3": "while", "4": "during", "answer": "while"}, "3944": {"question": "No one without a pass will be granted ___ to the conference", "1": "admission", "2": "is admitting", "3": "admitted", "4": "to admit", "answer": "admission"}, "3945": {"question": "To receive an electronic reminder when payment is due, set up an online account ___ Albright Bank", "1": "of", "2": "about", "3": "over", "4": "with", "answer": "with"}, "3946": {"question": "The registration fee is ___ refundable up to two weeks prior to the conference date", "1": "fullest", "2": "fuller", "3": "fully", "4": "full", "answer": "fully"}, "3947": {"question": "All identifying information has been ___ from this letter of complaint so that it can be used for training purposes", "1": "produced", "2": "extended", "3": "removed", "4": "resolved", "answer": "removed"}, "3948": {"question": "___ this time next year, Larkview Technology will have acquired two new subsidiaries", "1": "To", "2": "By", "3": "Quite", "4": "Begin", "answer": "By"}, "3949": {"question": "Table reservations for ___ greater than ten must be made at least one day in advance", "1": "plates", "2": "meals", "3": "sizes", "4": "parties", "answer": "parties"}, "3950": {"question": "Because of ___ weather conditions, tonight's concert in Harbin Park has been canceled", "1": "worsening", "2": "worsens", "3": "worsen", "4": "worst", "answer": "worsening"}, "3951": {"question": "Ms. AI-Omani will rely ___ team leaders to develop employee incentive programs", "1": "onto", "2": "into", "3": "within", "4": "upon", "answer": "upon"}, "3952": {"question": "Survey ___ analyze the layout of a land area above and below ground level", "1": "technicians", "2": "technically", "3": "technical", "4": "technicality", "answer": "technicians"}, "3953": {"question": "___ assemble your Gessen product, first read all instructions and gather all required tools", "1": "For the purpose of", "2": "To be sure", "3": "In order to", "4": "For example", "answer": "In order to"}, "3954": {"question": "Online shoppers who experience long waits for their orders tend ___ the business low ratings", "1": "have given", "2": "gave", "3": "to give", "4": "giving", "answer": "to give"}, "3955": {"question": "___ of the new Delran train station will begin in late September", "1": "Association", "2": "Construction", "3": "Violation", "4": "Comprehension", "answer": "Construction"}, "3956": {"question": "The computing power of the new laptop is ___ to any desktop computer in the same price range", "1": "compare", "2": "comparing", "3": "comparison", "4": "comparable", "answer": "comparable"}, "3957": {"question": "Dr. Yuina Hashimoto recently added another doctor to her practice, ___ allowing more patients to be seen", "1": "that", "2": "thus", "3": "which", "4": "so that", "answer": "thus"}, "3958": {"question": "Graden Hotel ___ its superior reputation thanks to the leadership of its president, Marcia Clemente", "1": "practiced", "2": "treated", "3": "heard", "4": "earned", "answer": "earned"}, "3959": {"question": "Aki Katsuro's latest novel is his most exciting ___ and is sure to make Radin Books' best-seller list", "1": "just", "2": "later", "3": "yet", "4": "very", "answer": "yet"}, "3960": {"question": "Thanks ___ to pastry chef Ana Villagra, Lauducci's Restaurant has become a favorite with local patrons", "1": "largely", "2": "larger", "3": "large", "4": "largest", "answer": "largely"}, "3961": {"question": "At Crintack Manufacturing, we acknowledge our ___ to provide a safe workplace for our employees", "1": "assumption", "2": "valuation", "3": "perception", "4": "obligation", "answer": "obligation"}, "3962": {"question": "Mr. Do___ novan had expected the charity event to be a success, the response from the community still overwhelmed him", "1": "Whenever", "2": "Although", "3": "Even so", "4": "In spite of", "answer": "Although"}, "3963": {"question": "This free mobile app provides ___ calendar updates , so salespeople will never miss an appointment", "1": "casual", "2": "equal", "3": "continual", "4": "eventual", "answer": "continual"}, "3964": {"question": "Most senior managers approved the architect's proposal for the office layout, although ___ expressed concerns about the cost", "1": "one", "2": "one another", "3": "each other", "4": "other", "answer": "one"}, "3965": {"question": "Greenville Library has hired an office assistant not only to perform general office duties ___ to support an ongoing special project", "1": "but also", "2": "only if", "3": "other than", "4": "as for", "answer": "but also"}, "3966": {"question": "The lease with The Pawlicki Group ___ if modifications to the existing offices are made", "1": "had continued", "2": "will be continued", "3": "was continuing", "4": "has been continuing", "answer": "will be continued"}, "3967": {"question": "Wrazen Associates ___ a summary with a list of recommendations as a routine part of any audit", "1": "realizes", "2": "induces", "3": "causes", "4": "issues", "answer": "issues"}, "3968": {"question": "Ms. Durkin asked for volunteers to help ___ with the employee fitness program", "1": "she", "2": "her", "3": "hers", "4": "herself", "answer": "her"}, "3969": {"question": "Lasner Electronics' staff have extensive ___ of current hardware systems", "1": "know", "2": "known", "3": "knowledge", "4": "knowledgeable", "answer": "knowledge"}, "3970": {"question": "___ a year, Tarrin Industrial Supply aud its the accounts of all of its factories", "1": "Once", "2": "Immediately", "3": "Directly", "4": "Yet", "answer": "Once"}, "3971": {"question": "Ms. Pham requested a refund ___ the coffeemaker she received was damaged", "1": "despite", "2": "why", "3": "concerning", "4": "because", "answer": "because"}, "3972": {"question": "Information ___ the artwork in the lobby is available at the reception desk", "1": "across", "2": "about", "3": "upon", "4": "except", "answer": "about"}, "3973": {"question": "With the Gema XTI binoculars, users can ___ see objects that are more than 100 meters away", "1": "ease", "2": "easy", "3": "easily", "4": "easier", "answer": "easily"}, "3974": {"question": "The Physical Therapy Association is committed to keeping costs ___ for its certification programs", "1": "affordable", "2": "permitted", "3": "cutting", "4": "necessary", "answer": "affordable"}, "3975": {"question": "Mr. Brennel ___ positions in various areas of the company before he became president", "1": "occupation", "2": "occupational", "3": "occupying", "4": "occupied", "answer": "occupied"}, "3976": {"question": "To remain on schedule, editors must submit all ___ to the book to the authors by Friday", "1": "ideas", "2": "essays", "3": "revisions", "4": "suggestions", "answer": "revisions"}, "3977": {"question": "___ industry professionals are allowed to purchase tickets to the Kuo Photography Fair", "1": "Only", "2": "Until", "3": "Unless", "4": "Quite", "answer": "Only"}, "3978": {"question": "At Pharmbeck's banquet, Mr. Jones ___ a trophy for his performance in this year's quality-improvement initiative", "1": "accepted", "2": "congratulated", "3": "nominated", "4": "hoped", "answer": "accepted"}, "3979": {"question": "Ms. Suto claims that important market trends become ___ with the use of data analysis", "1": "predict", "2": "prediction", "3": "predictable", "4": "predictably", "answer": "predictable"}, "3980": {"question": "One of Grommer Consulting's goals is to enhance the relationship ___ salespeople and their customers", "1": "inside", "2": "within", "3": "around", "4": "between", "answer": "between"}, "3981": {"question": "Depending on your answers to the survey, we ___ you to collect additional information", "1": "may call", "2": "are calling", "3": "have been called", "4": "must be calling", "answer": "may call"}, "3982": {"question": "___ Jemburger opened its newest franchise, the first 100 customers were given free hamburgers", "1": "Now", "2": "When", "3": "As if", "4": "After all", "answer": "When"}, "3983": {"question": "Please include the serial number of your product in any ___ with the customer service department", "1": "corresponds", "2": "correspondence", "3": "correspondingly", "4": "correspondent", "answer": "correspondence"}, "3984": {"question": "The award-winning film UnderWater Secrets promotes awareness ___ ocean pollution and its effects on our planet", "1": "of", "2": "to", "3": "from", "4": "with", "answer": "of"}, "3985": {"question": "BYF Company specializes in ___ promotional items to help companies advertise their brand", "1": "personally", "2": "personalized", "3": "personality", "4": "personalizes", "answer": "personalized"}, "3986": {"question": "___ the rent increase is less than 2 percent, Selwin Electrical Supply will continue to lease the space", "1": "As long as", "2": "Along with", "3": "Not only", "4": "Otherwise", "answer": "As long as"}, "3987": {"question": "Belden Hospital's chief of staff meets regularly with the staff to ensure that procedures ___ correctly", "1": "to be performed", "2": "would have performed", "3": "had been performed", "4": "are being performed", "answer": "are being performed"}, "3988": {"question": "Any requests for time off should be addressed to the ___ department supervisor", "1": "urgent", "2": "appropriate", "3": "subsequent", "4": "deliverable", "answer": "appropriate"}, "3989": {"question": "World Fish Supply delivers the freshest fish possible thanks to innovative ___ and shipping methods", "1": "preserves", "2": "preserved", "3": "preserve", "4": "preservation", "answer": "preservation"}, "3990": {"question": "Company executives are currently reviewing the annual budget ___ submitted to them by the Financial Planning department", "1": "requirements", "2": "deliveries", "3": "developers", "4": "qualities", "answer": "requirements"}, "3991": {"question": "Even the CEO had to admit that Prasma Designs' win was ___ the result of fortunate timing", "1": "parts", "2": "parted", "3": "partly", "4": "parting", "answer": "partly"}, "3992": {"question": "Mr. Singh took notes on ___ the focus group discussed during the morning session", "1": "each", "2": "several", "3": "another", "4": "everything", "answer": "everything"}, "3993": {"question": "Last year, Tadaka Computer Solutions ranked third ___ in regional earnings", "1": "together", "2": "overall", "3": "consecutively", "4": "generally", "answer": "overall"}, "3994": {"question": "___ the popularity of the BPT39 wireless speaker, production will be increased fivefold starting next month", "1": "On behalf of", "2": "Whether", "3": "Moreover", "4": "As a result of", "answer": "As a result of"}, "3995": {"question": "Zypo Properties has just signed a lease agreement with the law firm ___ offices are on the third floor", "1": "how", "2": "what", "3": "whose", "4": "wherever", "answer": "whose"}, "3996": {"question": "___ events this year caused profits in the second and third quarters to differ significantly from original projections", "1": "Total", "2": "Marginal", "3": "Representative", "4": "Unforeseen", "answer": "Unforeseen"}, "3997": {"question": "The timeline for the pathway lighting project was extended to ___ input from the environmental commission", "1": "use up", "2": "believe in", "3": "make into", "4": "allow for", "answer": "allow for"}, "3998": {"question": "For homeowners seeking to reduce their electricity bills, the energy-saving ideas in this brochure should be ___.", "1": "lengthy", "2": "immediate", "3": "helpful", "4": "perceptive", "answer": "helpful"}, "3999": {"question": "i vi cc ch nh ang tm cch gim ha n tin in, cc  tng tit kim nng lng trong ti liu ny s hu ch.", "1": "maintenance", "2": "maintains", "3": "maintaining", "4": "is maintained", "answer": "maintains"}, "4000": {"question": "The doorways, which arch so ___, were left intact during the renovation of the historic Dersten Building.", "1": "graceful", "2": "grace", "3": "gracefully", "4": "graces", "answer": "gracefully"}, "4001": {"question": "Ms. Meada was ___ that her art submission was used on the cover of the firms annual report.", "1": "performed", "2": "flattered", "3": "welcomed", "4": "challenged", "answer": "flattered"}, "4002": {"question": "Long-term maintenances fees ------ according to the type of industrial printing machine purchased.", "1": "copy", "2": "repair", "3": "support", "4": "vary", "answer": "vary"}, "4003": {"question": "Sookie Chois latest childrens book is being ___ by Chung-He P", "1": "illustrating", "2": "illustrated", "3": "illustration", "4": "illustrates", "answer": "illustrated"}, "4004": {"question": "___ he is now retired, Mr. Matilla is able to pursue his hobby of woodworking.", "1": "During", "2": "Therefore", "3": "When", "4": "Because", "answer": "Because"}, "4005": {"question": "A lable on each box should indicate the production date as well as the place of ___ of the contents.", "1": "importance", "2": "safety", "3": "foundation", "4": "origin", "answer": "origin"}, "4006": {"question": "During negotiations, management appeared ___ to the idea of increasing the staffs wages.", "1": "agree", "2": "agreement", "3": "agreement", "4": "agrees", "answer": "agreement"}, "4007": {"question": "The custodial staff that we clean our dishes before leaving the kitchen.", "1": "requests", "2": "behaves", "3": "uses", "4": "visits", "answer": "requests"}, "4008": {"question": "If customers lose their original warranty , they can download a new one from the Web site.", "1": "certify", "2": "certificate", "3": "certifiable", "4": "certifiably", "answer": "certificate"}, "4009": {"question": "Our Portview branch is located the central business district, between Burnside Avenue and Everett street.", "1": "on", "2": "to", "3": "for", "4": "in", "answer": "in"}, "4010": {"question": "None of the employees  that Mr. Annan planned to retire at the end of the year.", "1": "knowingly", "2": "known", "3": "knew", "4": "to know", "answer": "knew"}, "4011": {"question": "Apply to Joneston Stores today so as not to miss -chance to join a great sales team.", "1": "you", "2": "your", "3": "yours", "4": "yourself", "answer": "your"}, "4012": {"question": "Employees are eligible to receive a - sala ry if they complete a special marketing course.", "1": "possible", "2": "frequent", "3": "closed", "4": "higher", "answer": "higher"}, "4013": {"question": "Keeping the Deal, Jan Butlers latest volume on management style, is her most commercially  book to date.", "1": "successfully", "2": "successful", "3": "succeed", "4": "success", "answer": "successful"}, "4014": {"question": "Present this postcard to a sales  at any of our stores and receive a 5.00 gift card.", "1": "accessory", "2": "associate", "3": "faculty", "4": "formula", "answer": "associate"}, "4015": {"question": "Lakeside Shopping Center has undergone  renovations in the last decade.", "1": "multiple", "2": "multiply", "3": "multiples", "4": "multiplied", "answer": "multiple"}, "4016": {"question": "There is a mandatory meeting today for everyone involved in managing or recruiting", "1": "staplers", "2": "volunteers", "3": "devices", "4": "headquarters", "answer": "volunteers"}, "4017": {"question": "The Smeeville bus system will accept only Rove Fare cardsMay 1 onward.", "1": "now", "2": "from", "3": "while", "4": "when", "answer": "from"}, "4018": {"question": "Relocating for work is  a difficult decision, but it can be reward", "1": "understandably", "2": "understanding", "3": "understood", "4": "understand", "answer": "understandably"}, "4019": {"question": "Last week Parmax Corporation  a disagreement with its main competitor concerning patent infringement.", "1": "settling", "2": "settler", "3": "settle", "4": "settled", "answer": "settled"}, "4020": {"question": "Khoury Dairys upgraded milk bottling system has increased productivity in the Tallahassee plant.", "1": "consistency", "2": "consistencies", "3": "consistent", "4": "consistently", "answer": "consistently"}, "4021": {"question": "The Rinka 2000 blender has not received a single - in the New Products Web forum.", "1": "complained", "2": "complaint", "3": "complaining", "4": "complain", "answer": "complaint"}, "4022": {"question": "After raising $45 million last year, Yamamoto Technologies is nowSeattles best-funded companies.", "1": "into", "2": "over", "3": "among", "4": "across", "answer": "among"}, "4023": {"question": "Deangelos Delights was so popular that the owner opened two bakeries.", "1": "allowable", "2": "additional", "3": "uninterested", "4": "inclusive", "answer": "additional"}, "4024": {"question": "Chef Octavia Farina took over Fratellis Restaurant  the previous chef left to open a new restaurant.", "1": "unless", "2": "rather than", "3": "as if", "4": "after", "answer": "after"}, "4025": {"question": "The director of Wingstom Foods commended Ms. Weiss for increasingin the bakery division.", "1": "produced", "2": "producing", "3": "production", "4": "productive", "answer": "production"}, "4026": {"question": "Greg Owens, founder of multi  national Hermes Taxi Service, used to drive a taxi .", "1": "he", "2": "his", "3": "himself", "4": "his own", "answer": "himself"}, "4027": {"question": "Starlight Theaters is proud to announce record earnings for the third quarter, far exceeding .", "1": "adjustments", "2": "endorsements", "3": "computations", "4": "expectations", "answer": "expectations"}, "4028": {"question": "Employees can attend one of the many workshops offered, - seem s most interesting.", "1": "whichever", "2": "however", "3": "everyone", "4": "much", "answer": "whichever"}, "4029": {"question": "- her strong negotiation skills, Marie Russel was made Sanwa, Inc.s lead sales contact.", "1": "Given", "2": "Deciding", "3": "Finding", "4": "Because", "answer": "Given"}, "4030": {"question": "A locked suggestion box will allow employees to submit feedback to management  .", "1": "anonymously", "2": "approximately", "3": "expressly", "4": "patiently", "answer": "anonymously"}, "4031": {"question": "A new strategy is under development to - our products more aggressively overseas.", "1": "invest", "2": "compete", "3": "participate", "4": "market", "answer": "market"}, "4032": {"question": "- on the citys ongoing revitalization project, Mayor Owen promised that residents would be pleased with the results.", "1": "Comment", "2": "Comments", "3": "Commented", "4": "Commenting", "answer": "Commenting"}, "4033": {"question": " , repairs to the plumbing pipes in the Moffett Building will be costly.", "1": "Tremendously", "2": "Unfortunately", "3": "Casually", "4": "Enormously", "answer": "Unfortunately"}, "4034": {"question": "The CEOs speech will be recorded in its - and made available to employees who could not attend the meeting.", "1": "entirety", "2": "system", "3": "perception", "4": "estimation", "answer": "entirety"}, "4035": {"question": "Trails on the southeast side of the mountain are often closed - because storms tend to occur without warning.", "1": "accidentally", "2": "coincidentally", "3": "steeply", "4": "unexpectedly", "answer": "unexpectedly"}, "4036": {"question": "Please submit your hours - any work-related expense reports by Friday.", "1": "as well as", "2": "above all", "3": "in addition", "4": "in case that", "answer": "as well as"}, "4037": {"question": "The new interns have been very mindful of ___ parking regulations", "1": "theirs", "2": "ours", "3": "our", "4": "they", "answer": "our"}, "4038": {"question": "To help the arts center improve its programming, please indicate which aspect of the workshop was most ___", "1": "informative", "2": "primary", "3": "enthusiastic", "4": "financial", "answer": "informative"}, "4039": {"question": "Mr. Gupta explained the ___ of the upgraded customer database to the sales team", "1": "beneficial", "2": "benefits", "3": "benefited", "4": "benefiting", "answer": "benefits"}, "4040": {"question": "Buses leaving the city terminal were delayed due to icy conditions ___ the roads", "1": "on", "2": "out", "3": "from", "4": "until", "answer": "on"}, "4041": {"question": "If you have recently ___ a digital camera and want to learn how to use it, this course is for you", "1": "purchased", "2": "purchase", "3": "purchasing", "4": "to purchase", "answer": "purchased"}, "4042": {"question": "The upcoming ___ of Tantino Airport will ease congestion and modernize guest accommodations", "1": "performance", "2": "supplement", "3": "deadline", "4": "renovation", "answer": "renovation"}, "4043": {"question": "The study showed that customers aged 35 to 44 paid with a Sonoka credit card ___ than customers in any other age-group", "1": "frequently", "2": "frequent", "3": "more frequently", "4": "frequency", "answer": "more frequently"}, "4044": {"question": "You need to ___ a business plan before your loan application can be processed", "1": "donate", "2": "request", "3": "confess", "4": "submit", "answer": "submit"}, "4045": {"question": "The hotel's ___ shuttle bus will take guests to Hong Kong's major landmarks", "1": "compliments", "2": "complimentary", "3": "compliment", "4": "complimenting", "answer": "complimentary"}, "4046": {"question": "___ months of work to sell the Apton Building, the realtor finally succeeded last week", "1": "Besides", "2": "After", "3": "Still", "4": "For", "answer": "After"}, "4047": {"question": "We will review all four custodial-service bids and choose ___ that suits our needs", "1": "some", "2": "one", "3": "others", "4": "either", "answer": "one"}, "4048": {"question": "The client asked for ___ to the images in the advertising text", "1": "standards", "2": "drawings", "3": "revisions", "4": "duplications", "answer": "revisions"}, "4049": {"question": "Please be advised ___ we have had to cancel your order because of a difficulty with our shipping agent", "1": "that", "2": "of", "3": "whether", "4": "between", "answer": "that"}, "4050": {"question": "Tin Creek Corporation ___ that its paper towels are the most absorbent on the market", "1": "obtains", "2": "competes", "3": "inquires", "4": "claims", "answer": "claims"}, "4051": {"question": "KCLN Associates will enter into to a business ___ with the contractor as soon as some of the teams are renegotiated", "1": "agreed", "2": "agreement", "3": "agreeable", "4": "agreeing", "answer": "agreement"}, "4052": {"question": "___ registering for online banking is not required, we strongly recommend it to all of our customers", "1": "Although", "2": "Instead", "3": "Regardless", "4": "Despite", "answer": "Although"}, "4053": {"question": "Viewers can easily ___ to the main character in the popular television series Autumn Mystery", "1": "related", "2": "relatable", "3": "relating", "4": "relate", "answer": "relate"}, "4054": {"question": "Fairlawn Medical Clinic offers a full ___ of services as part of its community wellness programs", "1": "center", "2": "surplus", "3": "range", "4": "type", "answer": "range"}, "4055": {"question": "The rear entrance to RC Bank will be closed for repairs and not ___ next Monday", "1": "accessible", "2": "accessing", "3": "access", "4": "accesses", "answer": "accessible"}, "4056": {"question": "Mr. Carson wants to see Carson audio products ___ , even in remote regions of the world", "1": "decidedly", "2": "furthermore", "3": "rather", "4": "everywhere", "answer": "everywhere"}, "4057": {"question": "We can buy office ___ such as desks and printers from any of our company's approved vendors", "1": "equip", "2": "equipping", "3": "equipment", "4": "equipped", "answer": "equipment"}, "4058": {"question": "When taking a book order, agents must record the customer's name and the ___ price of each item", "1": "assembled", "2": "listed", "3": "addressed", "4": "earned", "answer": "listed"}, "4059": {"question": "The building will be furnished ___ the supervisors do their inspection", "1": "with", "2": "these", "3": "once", "4": "just", "answer": "once"}, "4060": {"question": "In a strong display of confidence, the firm's board of directors ___ approved the merge", "1": "superficially", "2": "regularly", "3": "magnificently", "4": "unanimously", "answer": "unanimously"}, "4061": {"question": "When recently ___ , residents of Mill Creek Park said that street disrepair is the issue that concerns them most", "1": "poll", "2": "polls", "3": "pollster", "4": "polled", "answer": "polled"}, "4062": {"question": "Ms. Rivera agreed to work on the holiday ___ Mr. Grant could attend the conference", "1": "considering", "2": "so that", "3": "as if", "4": "wherever", "answer": "so that"}, "4063": {"question": "The clerk collects packages from each department twice a day and takes them to the mail room ___", "1": "throughout", "2": "all along", "3": "too much", "4": "downstairs", "answer": "downstairs"}, "4064": {"question": "Please inform Ms. Erwin of any complaints ___ those already discussed in today's meeting", "1": "beyond", "2": "between", "3": "during", "4": "against", "answer": "beyond"}, "4065": {"question": "The Tonsin Writers League is a reputable organization with highly ___ members", "1": "accomplishes", "2": "accomplishment", "3": "accomplished", "4": "accomplish", "answer": "accomplished"}, "4066": {"question": "As Mr. Naketa's assistant, Ms. Bain is in charge of ___ him on the last financial news", "1": "discussing", "2": "briefing", "3": "resuming", "4": "narrating", "answer": "briefing"}, "4067": {"question": "Every batch of sauce at Generita's Bistro is processed meticulously by ___ expert chefs", "1": "they", "2": "their", "3": "them", "4": "themselves", "answer": "their"}, "4068": {"question": "Computerization of medical records ___ increases a physician's ability to diagnose and treat patients", "1": "great", "2": "greatly", "3": "greatness", "4": "greatest", "answer": "greatly"}, "4069": {"question": "At Rojelle's Fine Dining, we use the freshest ___ available to make our salads", "1": "applications", "2": "subjects", "3": "ingredients", "4": "factors", "answer": "ingredients"}, "4070": {"question": "Professor Benguigui will present his paper ___ the natural history conference tomorrow", "1": "by", "2": "at", "3": "of", "4": "on", "answer": "at"}, "4071": {"question": "The chefs are still waiting for a ___ date for the new convection oven that was ordered two weeks ago", "1": "shipper", "2": "ships", "3": "shipments", "4": "shipping", "answer": "shipping"}, "4072": {"question": "Mr. Kang works ___ with our internal team members as well as various regional sales representatives", "1": "mildly", "2": "nearly", "3": "closely", "4": "narrowly", "answer": "closely"}, "4073": {"question": "Fashion designer Hye-Ja Pak knows ___ to update her line in response to changing tastes", "1": "and", "2": "when", "3": "need", "4": "for", "answer": "when"}, "4074": {"question": "The samba class was so well ___ that the Yulara Dance School decided to make the course a permanent offering", "1": "attended", "2": "educated", "3": "gathered", "4": "protected", "answer": "attended"}, "4075": {"question": "The factory will be situated away ___ the city's residential area to reduce complaints about noise and emissions", "1": "from", "2": "about", "3": "with", "4": "out", "answer": "from"}, "4076": {"question": "Ms. Kuramoto selected the most ___ mailing option available", "1": "economical", "2": "economy", "3": "economize", "4": "economized", "answer": "economical"}, "4077": {"question": "Companies without information technology specialists can ___ on Vyber Software Advisers for assistance with online services", "1": "reliable", "2": "reliably", "3": "rely", "4": "relying", "answer": "rely"}, "4078": {"question": "Next year, our team will have a new task, ___ is to review design portfolios", "1": "although", "2": "which", "3": "after", "4": "because", "answer": "which"}, "4079": {"question": "Cook the meat for 30 minutes to ensure ___ readiness to be eaten", "1": "both", "2": "this", "3": "its", "4": "that", "answer": "its"}, "4080": {"question": "Amoxitron's research team will hire ___ interns to assist with laboratory duties", "1": "given", "2": "several", "3": "whole", "4": "natural", "answer": "several"}, "4081": {"question": "___ the new acai juice blend has proved so popular, we should move quickly to increase our production volume", "1": "If", "2": "Whether", "3": "Since", "4": "Unless", "answer": "Since"}, "4082": {"question": "New emissions standards have forced Rider Auto to modify the process of engine ___", "1": "construction", "2": "constructed", "3": "constructive", "4": "construct", "answer": "construction"}, "4083": {"question": "Maki Kayano's book offers techniques for ___ business tasks with speed and precision", "1": "executing", "2": "equipping", "3": "returning", "4": "involving", "answer": "executing"}, "4084": {"question": "To control costs, updated credit card readers will be installed in branch stores ___", "1": "gradual", "2": "gradually", "3": "more gradual", "4": "most gradual", "answer": "gradually"}, "4085": {"question": "In this quarter, the Mantel Beverage Company is expecting sales ___ 160,000 and 180,000", "1": "without", "2": "among", "3": "throughout", "4": "between", "answer": "between"}, "4086": {"question": "Because Mount Akoyola is so challenging for climbers , ___ have reached its peak", "1": "any", "2": "either", "3": "other", "4": "few", "answer": "few"}, "4087": {"question": "King Street Bridge will be closed in the month of September ___ repair work", "1": "because of", "2": "so that", "3": "as if", "4": "rather than", "answer": "because of"}, "4088": {"question": "Ms. Taniguchi's supervisor commended her for negotiating ___ with Furuyama Corporation", "1": "effective", "2": "effecting", "3": "effected", "4": "effectively", "answer": "effectively"}, "4089": {"question": "Staff members may reserve the conference room ___ they need it", "1": "somewhere", "2": "whatever", "3": "everything", "4": "anytime", "answer": "anytime"}, "4090": {"question": "The public relations director must have a high level of ___ in English and Spanish", "1": "proficiency", "2": "advancement", "3": "routine", "4": "strength", "answer": "proficiency"}, "4091": {"question": "Patterson Products ___ seeks innovative ways of meeting changing consumer demand", "1": "dually", "2": "favorably", "3": "continually", "4": "generically", "answer": "continually"}, "4092": {"question": "Mr. Volante is working at home tomorrow so he ___ the technical report without any distractions", "1": "can finish", "2": "would finish", "3": "finished", "4": "has been finishing", "answer": "can finish"}, "4093": {"question": "All of the billing procedures remain the same, ___ new payment codes need to be inserted into the invoice documents", "1": "in order that", "2": "during", "3": "across from", "4": "except that", "answer": "except that"}, "4094": {"question": "The lightweight design of the new sedan is ___ because it can cause the vehicle to slide on icy roads", "1": "possible", "2": "mechanical", "3": "questionable", "4": "multiple", "answer": "questionable"}, "4095": {"question": "When the bank president retired, the common ___ was that the vice president would take over", "1": "assume", "2": "assumption", "3": "assuming", "4": "assumable", "answer": "assumption"}, "4096": {"question": "West Bengali Airlines ___ fees for oversized items that are still within weight limitations", "1": "invites", "2": "cooperates", "3": "transports", "4": "waives", "answer": "waives"}, "4097": {"question": "York Development Corporation marked the ___ of the Ford Road office complex with a ribbon-cutting ceremony", "1": "opens", "2": "opening", "3": "opened", "4": "openly", "answer": "opening"}, "4098": {"question": "Staff at the Bismarck Hotel were ___ helpful to us during our stay", "1": "quite", "2": "enough", "3": "far", "4": "early", "answer": "quite"}, "4099": {"question": "Ms . Luo will explain some possible consequences of the ___ merger with the Wilson-Peek Corporation", "1": "proposed", "2": "proposal", "3": "proposition", "4": "proposing", "answer": "proposed"}, "4100": {"question": "The Springdale supermarket survey ___ will be released a week after they are evaluated", "1": "events", "2": "stores", "3": "results", "4": "coupons", "answer": "results"}, "4101": {"question": "The new printer operates more ___ than the previous model did", "1": "quickest", "2": "quickness", "3": "quick", "4": "quickly", "answer": "quickly"}, "4102": {"question": "Here at Vanguard Buying Club, ___ help members find quality merchandise at the lowest possible prices", "1": "us", "2": "our", "3": "we", "4": "ourselves", "answer": "we"}, "4103": {"question": "Management announced that all salespeople would be receiving a bonus this year, ___ in time for summer vacations", "1": "just", "2": "as", "3": "only", "4": "by", "answer": "just"}, "4104": {"question": "According to Florida Digital Designer Magazine, many graphic designers do not consider ___ to be traditional artists", "1": "it", "2": "their", "3": "themselves", "4": "itself", "answer": "themselves"}, "4105": {"question": "A wooden bridge crossing the wading pond ___ to the hotel's nine-hole golf course", "1": "prepares", "2": "leads", "3": "presents", "4": "takes", "answer": "leads"}, "4106": {"question": "A special sale on stationery ___ on the Write Things Web site yesterday", "1": "was announced", "2": "announced", "3": "was announcing", "4": "to announce", "answer": "was announced"}, "4107": {"question": "All produce transported by Gocargo Trucking is refrigerated ___ upon pickup to prevent spoilage", "1": "lately", "2": "promptly", "3": "potentially", "4": "clearly", "answer": "promptly"}, "4108": {"question": "The Ferrera Museum plans to exhibit a collection of Lucia Almeida's most ___ sculptures", "1": "innovative", "2": "innovation", "3": "innovatively", "4": "innovate", "answer": "innovative"}, "4109": {"question": "The bank's cashier windows are open daily from 8:00A.M. to 4:00 P.M . ___ on Sundays", "1": "except", "2": "until", "3": "nor", "4": "yet", "answer": "except"}, "4110": {"question": "Inventory control and warehousing strategies ___ within the responsibilities of the supply chain manager", "1": "have", "2": "cover", "3": "mark", "4": "fall", "answer": "fall"}, "4111": {"question": "Of all the truck models available today, it can be difficult to figure out ___ would best suit your company's needs", "1": "when", "2": "why", "3": "which", "4": "where", "answer": "which"}, "4112": {"question": "CEO Yoshiro Kasai has expressed complete faith in Fairway Maritime's ___ to deliver the product on time", "1": "belief", "2": "measure", "3": "problem", "4": "ability", "answer": "ability"}, "4113": {"question": "At Derwin Securities, trainees alternate ___ attending information sessions and working closely with assigned mentors", "1": "along", "2": "against", "3": "between", "4": "near", "answer": "between"}, "4114": {"question": "Company Vice President Astrid Barretto had no ___ to being considered for the position of CEO", "1": "objected", "2": "objecting", "3": "objects", "4": "objection", "answer": "objection"}, "4115": {"question": "Belinda McKay fans who are ___ to the author's formal writing style will be surprised by her latest biography", "1": "fortunate", "2": "readable", "3": "comparable", "4": "accustomed", "answer": "accustomed"}, "4116": {"question": "The Southeast Asia Business Convention will feature ___ known and respected leaders from countries across the region", "1": "widen", "2": "wider", "3": "widely", "4": "wide", "answer": "widely"}, "4117": {"question": "___ the high cost of fuel, customers are buying smaller, more efficient cars", "1": "Together with", "2": "Instead of", "3": "As well as", "4": "Because of", "answer": "Because of"}, "4118": {"question": "Over the past ten years, Bellworth Medical Clinic ___ Atlan Protection officers for all security needs", "1": "is hiring", "2": "were hiring", "3": "has hired", "4": "was hired", "answer": "has hired"}, "4119": {"question": "The driver will make three ___ to deliver the package before it is returned to our warehouse", "1": "attempts", "2": "pursuits", "3": "aims", "4": "experiences", "answer": "attempts"}, "4120": {"question": "We congratulate all Riverside employees, whose ___ effort has resulted in a 20 percent reduction in waste disposal costs", "1": "collect", "2": "collective", "3": "collects", "4": "collector", "answer": "collective"}, "4121": {"question": "Andrzej Ptak's photography Web site will be available online ___ we have finished organizing and cataloging his work", "1": "how", "2": "once", "3": "so too", "4": "not only", "answer": "once"}, "4122": {"question": "The initial feedback from early buyers of the Sunbell XC2 mobile phone indicates that they found it ___ to use", "1": "conveniences", "2": "conveniently", "3": "convenience", "4": "convenient", "answer": "convenient"}, "4123": {"question": "___ space in the bathroom was limited, the contractor managed to fit in two sinks and a shower", "1": "Both", "2": "So that", "3": "Whether", "4": "Even though", "answer": "Even though"}, "4124": {"question": "The staff must ___ as much market-research data as possible before planning the advertising campaign", "1": "equip", "2": "compile", "3": "endorse", "4": "compose", "answer": "compile"}, "4125": {"question": "___ a national holiday falls on a Thursday, the Barstow Company allows employees to take off Friday as well", "1": "Even", "2": "For", "3": "Nearly", "4": "Whenever", "answer": "Whenever"}, "4126": {"question": "___ materials for the advanced Farsi course include an audio CD and a DVD", "1": "Supplementary", "2": "Consequential", "3": "Persistent", "4": "Cooperative", "answer": "Supplementary"}, "4127": {"question": "Jesper Associates currently has ___ with 26 different food suppliers", "1": "contracting", "2": "contracts", "3": "contractor", "4": "contract", "answer": "contracts"}, "4128": {"question": "Passengers must be at the gate ___ 25 minutes prior to boarding their flight", "1": "at least", "2": "as much", "3": "in case", "4": "by then", "answer": "at least"}, "4129": {"question": "Deltran analytics software can help ___ identify issues, predict trends, and improve business", "1": "you", "2": "your", "3": "yours", "4": "yourself", "answer": "you"}, "4130": {"question": "The technology department ___ to purchase three new servers next year", "1": "announces", "2": "thinks", "3": "predicts", "4": "plans", "answer": "plans"}, "4131": {"question": "Jennson Motors hired an ___ new efficiency expert last month", "1": "approximate", "2": "angular", "3": "exceptional", "4": "eventual", "answer": "exceptional"}, "4132": {"question": "Mr. Winkel's ___ responsibilities include auditing and financial review of large clients", "1": "accounts", "2": "accounted", "3": "accounting", "4": "accountable", "answer": "accounting"}, "4133": {"question": "The prime minister greeted foreign diplomats ___ a luncheon today in London", "1": "at", "2": "had", "3": "such", "4": "where", "answer": "at"}, "4134": {"question": "The management team at Otto Corporation offers incentives ___ employee productivity", "1": "stimulate", "2": "to stimulate", "3": "will stimulate", "4": "are stimulating", "answer": "to stimulate"}, "4135": {"question": "In response to customer ___, Lopez Naturals will release a line of organic soaps", "1": "demand", "2": "permit", "3": "arrival", "4": "account", "answer": "demand"}, "4136": {"question": "Before the computers leave the factory, they are ___ thoroughly to ensure they have no defects", "1": "selected", "2": "inspected", "3": "attached", "4": "managed", "answer": "inspected"}, "4137": {"question": "WRUZ Radio will broadcast a new show ___ to business news and economic analysis", "1": "allowed", "2": "prepared", "3": "dedicated", "4": "introduced", "answer": "dedicated"}, "4138": {"question": "Mr. Okada met ___ with the building manager to discuss the demolition project", "1": "frequent", "2": "frequenting", "3": "frequently", "4": "frequented", "answer": "frequently"}, "4139": {"question": "Mr. Montri politely ___ the job offer from Barranca Shipping Company", "1": "declined", "2": "decreased", "3": "prevented", "4": "converted", "answer": "declined"}, "4140": {"question": "Written permission must ___ before using Thavor Corporation's logo", "1": "to obtain", "2": "obtained", "3": "be obtained", "4": "obtaining", "answer": "be obtained"}, "4141": {"question": "___ it is relatively small, the fitness center at Ginder Apartments is very popular with residents", "1": "Reasoning", "2": "Essentially", "3": "Although", "4": "Throughout", "answer": "Although"}, "4142": {"question": "All communications must be approved by the public relations director before they can be shared ___", "1": "certainly", "2": "externally", "3": "deeply", "4": "utterly", "answer": "externally"}, "4143": {"question": "Providing precision welding to a ___ array of industries, Mistone Metalworks recently celebrated a century of service in Quebec", "1": "widely", "2": "widen", "3": "width", "4": "wide", "answer": "wide"}, "4144": {"question": "Mr. Kim considers punctuality a crucial ___ for all his assistants to have", "1": "device", "2": "type", "3": "action", "4": "trait", "answer": "trait"}, "4145": {"question": "The chief financial officer has ___ the importance of attracting new customers next quarter", "1": "applied", "2": "demanded", "3": "administered", "4": "emphasized", "answer": "emphasized"}, "4146": {"question": "Sewerd Furnishings is closing some of its showrooms because customers are ___ ordering furniture online", "1": "increasing", "2": "increase", "3": "increasingly", "4": "increased", "answer": "increasingly"}, "4147": {"question": "___ construction in progress at the old town hall building, tourist groups will not be allowed to enter the site", "1": "Now that", "2": "While", "3": "Even if", "4": "Due to", "answer": "Due to"}, "4148": {"question": "Several drilling-technology experts will present the results of their ___ on June 23", "1": "comprehension", "2": "resolution", "3": "investigation", "4": "specification", "answer": "investigation"}, "4149": {"question": "The store had a ___ display to promote the newest book from the best-selling mystery author", "1": "default", "2": "grateful", "3": "talented", "4": "massive", "answer": "massive"}, "4150": {"question": "Most of the people ___ attended yesterday's workshop have already submitted their feedback", "1": "who", "2": "those", "3": "whose", "4": "some", "answer": "who"}, "4151": {"question": "Both tasty and healthy, the tomato salad at Alfredi's Bistro is also large ___ to be served as a main dish", "1": "enough", "2": "fully", "3": "nearly", "4": "well", "answer": "enough"}, "4152": {"question": "The Klassin Group's booth at the Liberty Architecture Expo has garnered much ___", "1": "interest", "2": "interests", "3": "interested", "4": "interesting", "answer": "interest"}, "4153": {"question": "Save 25 percent on any printer ___ you buy a laptop computer at Diego's Electronics", "1": "whereas", "2": "whenever", "3": "such as", "4": "seeing that", "answer": "whenever"}, "4154": {"question": "The recently adopted policy restructures the company's debt according to a ___ five-step plan", "1": "managing", "2": "manageably", "3": "manages", "4": "manageable", "answer": "manageable"}, "4155": {"question": "The quality assurance department needs to hire additional staff ___ production has increased by 50 percent", "1": "even though", "2": "since", "3": "because of", "4": "therefore", "answer": "since"}, "4156": {"question": "Your order cannot ___ until we have received full payment", "1": "to process", "2": "be processed", "3": "being processed", "4": "has processed", "answer": "be processed"}}